const EGuessedCorrectly = {
  UNQUIZZED: "unquizzed",
  CORRECT: "correct",
  INCORRECT: "incorrect",
};

var flashCardsSets = [
  {
    id: "K79EOUInQE",
    title: "Unit 1",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "agua",
        back: "Water",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SoCJ9qp3gp",
      },
      {
        front: "bebe",
        back: "baby",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6WcT8ecUfh",
      },
      {
        front: "bebes",
        back: "babies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZipC59OoUf",
      },
      {
        front: "bebo",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q21by9QTMy",
      },
      {
        front: "come",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0J855l3Q0F",
      },
      {
        front: "comes",
        back: "you eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "keI0qsmBep",
      },
      {
        front: "como",
        back: "What",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g0CC9vyFEy",
      },
      {
        front: "el",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X2iINhoteF",
      },
      {
        front: "ella",
        back: "she",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PtQ9Coa4mq",
      },
      {
        front: "eres",
        back: "are you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ugVZOad5C0",
      },
      {
        front: "es",
        back: "is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FJJ2AxZTkk",
      },
      {
        front: "hombre",
        back: "men",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LNuGiByb39",
      },
      {
        front: "la",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4ZMqG38NAb",
      },
      {
        front: "leche",
        back: "milk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9qsxW6XNSa",
      },
      {
        front: "manzana",
        back: "apple",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FxIexHzl5j",
      },
      {
        front: "manzanas",
        back: "apples",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JVUYoeQECg",
      },
      {
        front: "mujer",
        back: "woman",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zqY0OESSMY",
      },
      {
        front: "niña",
        back: "girl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tu18x7Ul0V",
      },
      {
        front: "niño",
        back: "infant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9RbKfJ4Tdp",
      },
      {
        front: "pan",
        back: "bread",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ofY7MlDMaO",
      },
      {
        front: "soy",
        back: "I am",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WpYpprYX3J",
      },
      {
        front: "tú",
        back: "your",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q2dcVnq36n",
      },
      {
        front: "un",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j7pntUZkya",
      },
      {
        front: "una",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uTlFGkLRCU",
      },
      {
        front: "yo",
        back: "I",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ODWOPHQKJu",
      },
      {
        front: "él",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mQwMflB0sX",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tPoO8EsfT9",
    title: "Unit 1",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adiós",
        back: "goodbye",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g74XrhfXlf",
      },
      {
        front: "buenas noches",
        back: "good evening",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fUYnlfKLjW",
      },
      {
        front: "buenos días",
        back: "Good Morning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9GQIE4M9jV",
      },
      {
        front: "de nada",
        back: "you are welcome",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oo0lgOWosg",
      },
      {
        front: "disculpe",
        back: "excuse me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BSk1XnlD8U",
      },
      {
        front: "español",
        back: "Spanish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qzFwmoRQwu",
      },
      {
        front: "gracias",
        back: "thank you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ppRXbvDvKI",
      },
      {
        front: "hablas",
        back: "speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jkanbh3KuK",
      },
      {
        front: "hablo",
        back: "I speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XXJLTXfKqv",
      },
      {
        front: "hola",
        back: "hello",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "21WukqP8er",
      },
      {
        front: "inglés",
        back: "English",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nQUxzLGbQw",
      },
      {
        front: "lo siento",
        back: "I'm sorry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nlHGFQOLJB",
      },
      {
        front: "mucho gusto",
        back: "pleased to meet you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lahI78SdxH",
      },
      {
        front: "no",
        back: "not",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I3fq7Pl4iW",
      },
      {
        front: "perdón",
        back: "forgiveness",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZooaP6Eg3e",
      },
      {
        front: "por favor",
        back: "please",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QJNU6x7n5s",
      },
      {
        front: "sí",
        back: "Yeah",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tk44oKUUID",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0KydqJ18J8",
    title: "Unit 2",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qbfwBsVEME",
      },
      {
        front: "aeropuerto",
        back: "airport",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "411IzioYww",
      },
      {
        front: "aquí",
        back: "here",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5gXiUQVRsN",
      },
      {
        front: "autobús",
        back: "bus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eD9Hxwpdww",
      },
      {
        front: "banco",
        back: "bank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HEM7bMLEml",
      },
      {
        front: "baño",
        back: "bathroom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tNC3SbQTFG",
      },
      {
        front: "boleto",
        back: "ticket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BJ3LAVL5Y8",
      },
      {
        front: "calle",
        back: "street",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "79tSd9pVLa",
      },
      {
        front: "cerrado",
        back: "closed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "phWfF3EInU",
      },
      {
        front: "dinero",
        back: "money",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wa7yKrFawS",
      },
      {
        front: "dónde",
        back: "where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xho2tUEtk7",
      },
      {
        front: "en",
        back: "in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qSOsngqqQZ",
      },
      {
        front: "está",
        back: "is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "diZBljx4sy",
      },
      {
        front: "hospital",
        back: "hospital",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wLeGLST7cz",
      },
      {
        front: "hotel",
        back: "hotel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nBzUAiW5gT",
      },
      {
        front: "maleta",
        back: "bag",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X5iAnJ9ZIV",
      },
      {
        front: "mi",
        back: "me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LE1nIPEVkS",
      },
      {
        front: "museo",
        back: "museum",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I4fDnSqR7K",
      },
      {
        front: "necesito",
        back: "needed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5wyeyEcaSv",
      },
      {
        front: "pasaporte",
        back: "passport",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uFKpqwqUFM",
      },
      {
        front: "por favor",
        back: "please",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8oqBCNcigQ",
      },
      {
        front: "reserva",
        back: "booking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h9lx0U9vrS",
      },
      {
        front: "supermercado",
        back: "Supermarket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a4Z8dd8SDJ",
      },
      {
        front: "taxi",
        back: "cab",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lTtZQqhNNB",
      },
      {
        front: "teléfono",
        back: "telephone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WAjeHTugIg",
      },
      {
        front: "tengo",
        back: "I've got",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pe4N3N5qBO",
      },
      {
        front: "tren",
        back: "train",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BQAs6CceRm",
      },
      {
        front: "tu",
        back: "your",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zya286BnR8",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "qPSglPhSX2",
    title: "Unit 3",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "azúcar",
        back: "sugar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9hAZ0zGs5a",
      },
      {
        front: "café",
        back: "coffee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rhC46jp4ps",
      },
      {
        front: "carne",
        back: "meat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WlG2AUkfTB",
      },
      {
        front: "con",
        back: "with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SycLwMc8TP",
      },
      {
        front: "cuenta",
        back: "bill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tnZxhhxKJF",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        back: "from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ilLNFC1wiI",
      },
      {
        front: "dos",
        back: "two",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ddUrDogWFG",
      },
      {
        front: "ensalada",
        back: "salad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QFAIDl1JZl",
      },
      {
        front: "hamburguesa",
        back: "Burger",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bBLAsiF8Y1",
      },
      {
        front: "jugo",
        back: "juice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Klut6CXPEr",
      },
      {
        front: "mesa",
        back: "desk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "umhix7t6RN",
      },
      {
        front: "naranja",
        back: "orange",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fafXTt0d6h",
      },
      {
        front: "o",
        back: "either",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0dgkihg7Lm",
      },
      {
        front: "pagar",
        back: "to pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3fgvKNXdHk",
      },
      {
        front: "para",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w7utxNKmxC",
      },
      {
        front: "personas",
        back: "people",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7rZZch7wwB",
      },
      {
        front: "pescado",
        back: "fish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aqVL8FXdTM",
      },
      {
        front: "queso",
        back: "cheese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tmUKwhxKIo",
      },
      {
        front: "quiero",
        back: "I love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aFNryj8Z0K",
      },
      {
        front: "restaurante",
        back: "restaurant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F95k9BHVij",
      },
      {
        front: "sal",
        back: "Salt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "91MEbJ6KeT",
      },
      {
        front: "sin",
        back: "without",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pRpFmcZii3",
      },
      {
        front: "sándwich",
        back: "sandwich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Va4CBMqoZh",
      },
      {
        front: "taza",
        back: "Bowl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5EI7Qvw9cA",
      },
      {
        front: "tomate",
        back: "tomatoes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7SzOr3Ny6f",
      },
      {
        front: "tres",
        back: "three",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JcZ1hFlCTf",
      },
      {
        front: "uno",
        back: "one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0W7R5yWpMg",
      },
      {
        front: "vaso",
        back: "glass",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HgPtghsAEP",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "RY0n6dvUYw",
    title: "Unit 4",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abuela",
        back: "Grandma",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e25sfABtYK",
      },
      {
        front: "abuelo",
        back: "grandfather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1c1ZW95nkC",
      },
      {
        front: "apartamento",
        back: "apartment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nCgBICmPbW",
      },
      {
        front: "bicicleta",
        back: "bike",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g54mjmdVH3",
      },
      {
        front: "bonito",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NZRGBKoWpU",
      },
      {
        front: "carro",
        back: "car",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3h2vQxuscz",
      },
      {
        front: "casa",
        back: "House",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gyOjjFmtM5",
      },
      {
        front: "elegante",
        back: "Elegant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q7471CIIP8",
      },
      {
        front: "esposa",
        back: "wife",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iYJEYUco6y",
      },
      {
        front: "esposo",
        back: "husband",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5m3HugHtzu",
      },
      {
        front: "familia",
        back: "family",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wnOfkTA2Vg",
      },
      {
        front: "gato",
        back: "cat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tehiGki1dw",
      },
      {
        front: "grande",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PXCThxgWus",
      },
      {
        front: "hermana",
        back: "sister",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hGUtEikHea",
      },
      {
        front: "hermano",
        back: "brother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MJ72W1Qjto",
      },
      {
        front: "hija",
        back: "daughter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aRimcajTDP",
      },
      {
        front: "hijo",
        back: "child",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F4wF7KntDV",
      },
      {
        front: "inteligente",
        back: "intelligent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nFQ0mehqAS",
      },
      {
        front: "interesante",
        back: "interesting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z24Nmzb1GE",
      },
      {
        front: "madre",
        back: "mother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u5P1uC5E4I",
      },
      {
        front: "muy",
        back: "very",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uk4Q9OxA9T",
      },
      {
        front: "padre",
        back: "dad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VfNdWT4jCW",
      },
      {
        front: "perfecto",
        back: "perfect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hrbrOKWIvN",
      },
      {
        front: "perro",
        back: "dog",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qV6Jl98aq6",
      },
      {
        front: "tiene",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IxuagIcSi0",
      },
      {
        front: "tienes",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fYI8mY8qmT",
      },
      {
        front: "vivo",
        back: "alive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4lDEfbN2xc",
      },
      {
        front: "y",
        back: "Y",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T5irMbrYan",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "3F7LrMI9eP",
    title: "Unit 5",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrigo",
        back: "coat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CTo3B2HHH7",
      },
      {
        front: "azul",
        back: "blue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DtUDlF0gPW",
      },
      {
        front: "barato",
        back: "cheap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hP9o1nAqEU",
      },
      {
        front: "camisa",
        back: "shirt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d1zEElRdgj",
      },
      {
        front: "camiseta",
        back: "T shirt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4Wil0ppOXW",
      },
      {
        front: "caro",
        back: "expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d2c5Zs157X",
      },
      {
        front: "cartera",
        back: "briefcase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xI5oQCgopX",
      },
      {
        front: "chaqueta",
        back: "jacket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KtYBTQ64hc",
      },
      {
        front: "cinturón",
        back: "belt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DtRTlP9S3U",
      },
      {
        front: "comprar",
        back: "purchase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SXGTGMpL90",
      },
      {
        front: "cómoda",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8LopuZ2gms",
      },
      {
        front: "demasiado",
        back: "too",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p3j0fArzec",
      },
      {
        front: "diferente",
        back: "different",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gESiREOC1Z",
      },
      {
        front: "ese",
        back: "that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cxc9XV1Gxx",
      },
      {
        front: "este",
        back: "East",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dKq3xpkljr",
      },
      {
        front: "falda",
        back: "skirt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zBSgjjSzLa",
      },
      {
        front: "favorita",
        back: "favorite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J44Voyz2LF",
      },
      {
        front: "gris",
        back: "grey",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x3xSM0A6og",
      },
      {
        front: "marrón",
        back: "Brown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EJIQL2hpsG",
      },
      {
        front: "quiero",
        back: "I love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ShkG2nfZuo",
      },
      {
        front: "regalo",
        back: "present",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yJ6WOVb1th",
      },
      {
        front: "reloj",
        back: "watch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0IBRUNktvp",
      },
      {
        front: "rojo",
        back: "red",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GmdcJVZwSZ",
      },
      {
        front: "ropa",
        back: "clothes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SjWRIyf6il",
      },
      {
        front: "sombrero",
        back: "hat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o5npXusSr7",
      },
      {
        front: "tienda",
        back: "shop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B3astDNxGL",
      },
      {
        front: "verde",
        back: "green",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iliOSDWkHP",
      },
      {
        front: "vestido",
        back: "dress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ody8SPabcJ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "M76OLKR543",
    title: "Unit 6",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "prestense11",
        back: "borrow11",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1QocsuZa3E",
      },
      {
        front: "prestense12",
        back: "borrow12",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xa5TnBJ3Zl",
      },
      {
        front: "prestense13",
        back: "borrow13",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EaOFAtRThj",
      },
      {
        front: "prestense",
        back: "lend yourself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OYj7KEXWtK",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "9hJMqSVrTE",
    title: "Unit 7",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bolígrafo",
        back: "ballpoint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8SgVFE6zp7",
      },
      {
        front: "clase",
        back: "class",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ghIYuFaVe6",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendo",
        back: "understand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "moHQjkePA7",
      },
      {
        front: "computadora",
        back: "computer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TSCEqa7gcS",
      },
      {
        front: "difícil",
        back: "hard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K4USLClJCH",
      },
      {
        front: "escribes",
        back: "you write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pyJ6gp6p4c",
      },
      {
        front: "escribir",
        back: "to write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KxmXZ1uKwr",
      },
      {
        front: "escribo",
        back: "I write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kcgZXJre1f",
      },
      {
        front: "escuela",
        back: "school",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zKaehqI5RI",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiante",
        back: "student",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "prbqLRevVW",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiar",
        back: "to study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wrmagd6mua",
      },
      {
        front: "estudias",
        back: "do you study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1ZU4cxX2ZG",
      },
      {
        front: "estudio",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aC1VizUE3e",
      },
      {
        front: "examen",
        back: "test",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XkVhKSgpMA",
      },
      {
        front: "fácil",
        back: "easy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RUSNFLiZcX",
      },
      {
        front: "importante",
        back: "important",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7Ulq6QXnzU",
      },
      {
        front: "leer",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pfk3JZJQmT",
      },
      {
        front: "lees",
        back: "you read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LegeJe6xjO",
      },
      {
        front: "leo",
        back: "I read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BFyIxb5HPW",
      },
      {
        front: "libro",
        back: "book",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UtyJYAm2n3",
      },
      {
        front: "maestro",
        back: "teacher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KehSb0hADK",
      },
      {
        front: "medicina",
        back: "medicine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "igQoBrKeQ9",
      },
      {
        front: "mucho",
        back: "a lot of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NbbiHT2biG",
      },
      {
        front: "no",
        back: "not",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BGlI5LeFmX",
      },
      {
        front: "pregunta",
        back: "Question",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BiCtZf79lq",
      },
      {
        front: "problema",
        back: "issue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XSnuBSnBLx",
      },
      {
        front: "profesor",
        back: "professor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wXkrPYFDh5",
      },
      {
        front: "universidad",
        back: "college",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ky7b0Qkz4p",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "mi1WjZz87N",
    title: "Unit 8",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "China",
        back: "China",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T1fIjBCcCR",
      },
      {
        front: "España",
        back: "Spain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5aQmLxAR3A",
      },
      {
        front: "americana",
        back: "american",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uduo757Wxn",
      },
      {
        front: "americano",
        back: "American",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2dkPC6bLeZ",
      },
      {
        front: "china",
        back: "China",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "68tVTYyRzT",
      },
      {
        front: "cuba",
        back: "Cuba",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lOPIOdIUEJ",
      },
      {
        front: "cubana",
        back: "Cuban",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nu39rN9y8k",
      },
      {
        front: "cubano",
        back: "Cuban",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KhzCXsfnPk",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        back: "from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TT4nwJmRLt",
      },
      {
        front: "dónde",
        back: "where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qqktfKwYQR",
      },
      {
        front: "en",
        back: "in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LjsPYXOUlq",
      },
      {
        front: "españa",
        back: "Spain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6EDFQmHLf3",
      },
      {
        front: "estados unidos",
        back: "United States",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5MsnnXJ46k",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiante",
        back: "student",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5NSc6UcZfb",
      },
      {
        front: "interesante",
        back: "interesting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1DQO6HIGDU",
      },
      {
        front: "me llamo",
        back: "my name is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "14Y1oEfdXB",
      },
      {
        front: "mexicana",
        back: "mexican",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l0XG0txvg9",
      },
      {
        front: "mexicano",
        back: "Mexican",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G9VPLoqRLF",
      },
      {
        front: "mi",
        back: "me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1zqjyMu1HY",
      },
      {
        front: "méxico",
        back: "Mexico",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fKpG2JOxvR",
      },
      {
        front: "nombre",
        back: "Name",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pi7sVHmqRq",
      },
      {
        front: "vivo",
        back: "alive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cdkeVnj6E2",
      },
      {
        front: "y",
        back: "Y",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2PVFQ96qK6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0ZKRHeLaWN",
    title: "Unit 9",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bien",
        back: "good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LFiELnxBwh",
      },
      {
        front: "buenas tardes",
        back: "good evening",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S9Gj8p9Bya",
      },
      {
        front: "cansada",
        back: "tired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s5u392YreT",
      },
      {
        front: "cansado",
        back: "tired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EoPoexdk9l",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo",
        back: "What",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LomTs2O1JT",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo está",
        back: "How is it going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yJg7ADQKCX",
      },
      {
        front: "estoy",
        back: "I am",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IJ0QL2Acis",
      },
      {
        front: "está",
        back: "is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gjU9gZqKJq",
      },
      {
        front: "estás",
        back: "these",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "or5D81uOzk",
      },
      {
        front: "feliz",
        back: "Merry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dpYZ9oFnhz",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta luego",
        back: "bye",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BK8F8WT0L6",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta mañana",
        back: "until tomorrow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Ipil1S3nJ",
      },
      {
        front: "mal",
        back: "wrong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pYHs0ceNPk",
      },
      {
        front: "muy",
        back: "very",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xXoewS17mj",
      },
      {
        front: "ocupada",
        back: "busy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1DtMAezjjw",
      },
      {
        front: "ocupado",
        back: "occupied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "esDCMOxBiS",
      },
      {
        front: "se llama",
        back: "is named",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BYnY7akDkM",
      },
      {
        front: "señor",
        back: "Sir",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OFOib87ADI",
      },
      {
        front: "señora",
        back: "madam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zr7eeuW952",
      },
      {
        front: "señorita",
        back: "miss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b4hE6VKcB3",
      },
      {
        front: "te llamas",
        back: "your name is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iTdB6ITn1N",
      },
      {
        front: "usted",
        back: "you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tjtyk5WpY0",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "5bS1Eegtmk",
    title: "Unit 9",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ayuda",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HPMPORseh0",
      },
      {
        front: "banana",
        back: "banana",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r38d4lhQhw",
      },
      {
        front: "boleto",
        back: "ticket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yFj7zR0NAG",
      },
      {
        front: "bolígrafo",
        back: "ballpoint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1vJXbFk6zt",
      },
      {
        front: "café",
        back: "coffee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pOOgUiqioT",
      },
      {
        front: "carro",
        back: "car",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rR4epSsmE0",
      },
      {
        front: "cartera",
        back: "briefcase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mSGlHqJ9cZ",
      },
      {
        front: "computadora",
        back: "computer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ajifU4wFJy",
      },
      {
        front: "dinero",
        back: "money",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CL91ZaZt30",
      },
      {
        front: "maleta",
        back: "bag",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Pr1woyhTNZ",
      },
      {
        front: "más",
        back: "plus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e4FWPqvwsg",
      },
      {
        front: "necesita",
        back: "needs to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u3TGPWXruc",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitas",
        back: "you need",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8zJB1gNhME",
      },
      {
        front: "necesito",
        back: "needed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2fQqatSdTT",
      },
      {
        front: "pasaporte",
        back: "passport",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N1lgwexKtr",
      },
      {
        front: "quiere",
        back: "wants",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yersDd9ecv",
      },
      {
        front: "quieres",
        back: "you want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZcZBW1rDjQ",
      },
      {
        front: "quiero",
        back: "I love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tdXBYCCkLB",
      },
      {
        front: "taxi",
        back: "cab",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QaFUmQWntY",
      },
      {
        front: "teléfono",
        back: "telephone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oHlSiqWRdJ",
      },
      {
        front: "tengo",
        back: "I've got",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BXKcFmEh9A",
      },
      {
        front: "tiene",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9uldQIP0PU",
      },
      {
        front: "tienes",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "krLYCtUqHS",
      },
      {
        front: "té",
        back: "tea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ahuVGAVDgc",
      },
      {
        front: "usa",
        back: "uses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vqp6yHeHet",
      },
      {
        front: "usar",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yYA7UhNRpD",
      },
      {
        front: "usas",
        back: "you use",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lGsgDZ3TfO",
      },
      {
        front: "uso",
        back: "use",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AzONECrp1F",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0LD4BZP39o",
    title: "Unit 10",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "baile",
        back: "dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OoWLDK4adR",
      },
      {
        front: "béisbol",
        back: "baseball",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yUmyuRYsOr",
      },
      {
        front: "concierto",
        back: "concert",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JYQCVUmOxi",
      },
      {
        front: "cumpleaños",
        back: "birthday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "otaWqlbdBb",
      },
      {
        front: "cuándo",
        back: "when",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A0n44qD7MA",
      },
      {
        front: "disfruta",
        back: "enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T5wrIZ555h",
      },
      {
        front: "divertida",
        back: "fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jyNgQ3pRJX",
      },
      {
        front: "divertido",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ya9FdFeRDX",
      },
      {
        front: "domingo",
        back: "Sunday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fQkxv7nEH2",
      },
      {
        front: "día",
        back: "day",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NqfKC0PYQd",
      },
      {
        front: "favorita",
        back: "favorite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mtss2NnHbN",
      },
      {
        front: "favorito",
        back: "favorite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IbOUV5qmgt",
      },
      {
        front: "fiesta",
        back: "party",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pW2P6JO5CD",
      },
      {
        front: "fin de semana",
        back: "Weekend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "noNzrRDee7",
      },
      {
        front: "fútbol",
        back: "football",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zonAg4ujOL",
      },
      {
        front: "hoy",
        back: "today",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4K6L9l4Udk",
      },
      {
        front: "jueves",
        back: "Thursday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v1G67a2yyZ",
      },
      {
        front: "lunes",
        back: "Monday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0orB4KCkRO",
      },
      {
        front: "martes",
        back: "Tuesday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vHTHil6Wrt",
      },
      {
        front: "mañana",
        back: "morning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LaijIlLofD",
      },
      {
        front: "miércoles",
        back: "Wednesday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MuHkN2zE02",
      },
      {
        front: "partido",
        back: "match",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PbB7AaiJA8",
      },
      {
        front: "película",
        back: "film",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OAsbv41dKk",
      },
      {
        front: "qué",
        back: "than",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cAjQfbNfX2",
      },
      {
        front: "semana",
        back: "week",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ebx047rTCb",
      },
      {
        front: "sábado",
        back: "Saturday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8ByX6YzAVe",
      },
      {
        front: "tu",
        back: "your",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OHYHGQ4AIx",
      },
      {
        front: "viernes",
        back: "friday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qVozy0ZCIj",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "eM9BOfq16M",
    title: "Unit 11",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "beber",
        back: "to drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b56o2ZiIN5",
      },
      {
        front: "carne",
        back: "meat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SmSUDKHrwH",
      },
      {
        front: "casa",
        back: "House",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3cPb9OgtU9",
      },
      {
        front: "comer",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uLHzzWcLJY",
      },
      {
        front: "ensalada",
        back: "salad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6p10h1h8m7",
      },
      {
        front: "estudia",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ADiG5HxHed",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiar",
        back: "to study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XdAB4B5emc",
      },
      {
        front: "estudias",
        back: "do you study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I95fwJQOnk",
      },
      {
        front: "estudio",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bF9BL24BLi",
      },
      {
        front: "europa",
        back: "Europe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kFNDHUPjwt",
      },
      {
        front: "francia",
        back: "France",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vTh4JZKKar",
      },
      {
        front: "francés",
        back: "French",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "efcxFvwISa",
      },
      {
        front: "fábrica",
        back: "factory",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D26RsIG6IM",
      },
      {
        front: "habla",
        back: "speaks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rTCP9JAGCg",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar",
        back: "to talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YWUGwcfSt7",
      },
      {
        front: "inglaterra",
        back: "England",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LZLfcS1T7h",
      },
      {
        front: "jugo",
        back: "juice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PC8QKW9hUe",
      },
      {
        front: "oficina",
        back: "office",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E9qwGFmLFM",
      },
      {
        front: "quién",
        back: "who",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZLIEwdXuzl",
      },
      {
        front: "sándwich",
        back: "sandwich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4UBrgJsLCe",
      },
      {
        front: "trabaja",
        back: "works",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H2vy0PX2is",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajar",
        back: "to work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EjbmfwFO0N",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajas",
        back: "you work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bqgbWF8tyH",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajo",
        back: "worked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wt2M5KX7vc",
      },
      {
        front: "vino",
        back: "wine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HzzvbZBpNk",
      },
      {
        front: "vive",
        back: "it lives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fad05kthjO",
      },
      {
        front: "vives",
        back: "do you live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iuSdc3jy7a",
      },
      {
        front: "vivir",
        back: "to live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hbocKMneEZ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "sFOtockKS7",
    title: "Unit 11",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "amiga",
        back: "friend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OoByAdN8il",
      },
      {
        front: "amigo",
        back: "friend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CW8gLEYsmm",
      },
      {
        front: "camarera",
        back: "waitress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b0cJxtbG5s",
      },
      {
        front: "camarero",
        back: "waiter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sJ6DNWFO3s",
      },
      {
        front: "celular",
        back: "mobile",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hqwW8mWSnb",
      },
      {
        front: "ciudad",
        back: "city",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ca14MFXf1j",
      },
      {
        front: "con",
        back: "with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pKmLTf7hg2",
      },
      {
        front: "dirección",
        back: "direction",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UgPAAwHwBh",
      },
      {
        front: "escuela",
        back: "school",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3rlrTNTekk",
      },
      {
        front: "familia",
        back: "family",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MK5TIICOlO",
      },
      {
        front: "gato",
        back: "cat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aWcfWC5G1s",
      },
      {
        front: "grande",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eh5lwvqxfk",
      },
      {
        front: "hermana",
        back: "sister",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LBDEcfipVp",
      },
      {
        front: "hermano",
        back: "brother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0i4muxWkyl",
      },
      {
        front: "importante",
        back: "important",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtH8ziOU0i",
      },
      {
        front: "joven",
        back: "young",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cI5Sha4pA4",
      },
      {
        front: "maestra",
        back: "teacher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LIMlHmgWvy",
      },
      {
        front: "maestro",
        back: "teacher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JXbnyT7kSn",
      },
      {
        front: "médica",
        back: "medical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5Y9pVOHGfB",
      },
      {
        front: "médico",
        back: "medical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fp679CcLUi",
      },
      {
        front: "novia",
        back: "girlfriend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "51gI5vqffz",
      },
      {
        front: "novio",
        back: "boyfriend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2KT6M1c6Ov",
      },
      {
        front: "número",
        back: "number",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZOBTc5Fafh",
      },
      {
        front: "perro",
        back: "dog",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FDEV1KDNey",
      },
      {
        front: "portugués",
        back: "Portuguese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6Fe3CskY6p",
      },
      {
        front: "pueblo",
        back: "town",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Sa76CxgdxQ",
      },
      {
        front: "restaurante",
        back: "restaurant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "255FMP0aE8",
      },
      {
        front: "ser",
        back: "to be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9TX3350T5o",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "vBbLF0UYY9",
    title: "Unit 12",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "agreement1",
        back: "agreement1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "80JsBSndeC",
      },
      {
        front: "agreement2",
        back: "agreement2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jm3YLchtMd",
      },
      {
        front: "agreement3",
        back: "agreement3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a5ngAk2PFa",
      },
      {
        front: "agreement",
        back: "agreement",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7kqRCVucqp",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Oa820Tq0MO",
    title: "Unit 13",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aprende",
        back: "learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V7EFtOsT0l",
      },
      {
        front: "aprender",
        back: "learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yb7vFqC1kD",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendes",
        back: "you learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FrpJzQYAQ3",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendo",
        back: "I learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Roq73vwBIk",
      },
      {
        front: "biblioteca",
        back: "library",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fLA9ePgo7x",
      },
      {
        front: "bibliotecas",
        back: "libraries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5EAEfDOoch",
      },
      {
        front: "bolígrafos",
        back: "pens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bV1goCTSIZ",
      },
      {
        front: "cero",
        back: "zero",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g8mhKRPx3o",
      },
      {
        front: "cinco",
        back: "five",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZaYBgIO2lA",
      },
      {
        front: "clase",
        back: "class",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8BAK7n2XdB",
      },
      {
        front: "clases",
        back: "lessons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RB4qQopwc5",
      },
      {
        front: "comprar",
        back: "purchase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a2Lj3lyeeI",
      },
      {
        front: "computadoras",
        back: "computers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1QOTsoFLLX",
      },
      {
        front: "cuatro",
        back: "four",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UiQNnKR5On",
      },
      {
        front: "dos",
        back: "two",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p5ZqxbzfFV",
      },
      {
        front: "esta",
        back: "is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Erk0ybZhag",
      },
      {
        front: "este",
        back: "East",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtHp9PGk6P",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiantes",
        back: "students",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cZrp9aJf1p",
      },
      {
        front: "libro",
        back: "book",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YSI2hCZpfA",
      },
      {
        front: "libros",
        back: "books",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dEXu2Jcdoa",
      },
      {
        front: "ocho",
        back: "eight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fqs6vZO6WB",
      },
      {
        front: "pregunta",
        back: "Question",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dAY5kuYXqT",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntas",
        back: "questions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k3cYEjRjRt",
      },
      {
        front: "seis",
        back: "six",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7Aecznummy",
      },
      {
        front: "siete",
        back: "seven",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F43VKaROz9",
      },
      {
        front: "tres",
        back: "three",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WU1J0ZcvFY",
      },
      {
        front: "universidad",
        back: "college",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c6NJRdwh6k",
      },
      {
        front: "uno",
        back: "one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SfAHZDhvQd",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "umkL3r1HSY",
    title: "Unit 13",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abuela",
        back: "Grandma",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0YPi1M554a",
      },
      {
        front: "abuelo",
        back: "grandfather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I8wJHQng4g",
      },
      {
        front: "alta",
        back: "high",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VefOb1DzVG",
      },
      {
        front: "alto",
        back: "high or tall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q3tKFWhSuV",
      },
      {
        front: "año",
        back: "year",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mbdnIM6idh",
      },
      {
        front: "años",
        back: "years",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bt4YXVrS4D",
      },
      {
        front: "baja",
        back: "low",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t7FGpvOBp9",
      },
      {
        front: "bajo",
        back: "low",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LC9jmipUuY",
      },
      {
        front: "bonita",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CfG98j7yHr",
      },
      {
        front: "bonito",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kDacihS9Ri",
      },
      {
        front: "diez",
        back: "ten",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wC4sboFjpa",
      },
      {
        front: "española",
        back: "Spanish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7VaxEhNjr6",
      },
      {
        front: "esposa",
        back: "wife",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zyXEt6d35f",
      },
      {
        front: "esposas",
        back: "wives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sLMVbd3Wr8",
      },
      {
        front: "esposo",
        back: "husband",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GcFEn0HejH",
      },
      {
        front: "esposos",
        back: "husbands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "URq3rQ0buR",
      },
      {
        front: "hija",
        back: "daughter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ss4JMEF1Mt",
      },
      {
        front: "hijas",
        back: "daughters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WD0Pfovy8y",
      },
      {
        front: "hijo",
        back: "child",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "93HedxfaHC",
      },
      {
        front: "hijos",
        back: "sons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2kf9FVNFwi",
      },
      {
        front: "inglesa",
        back: "english",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y8FEDanqu8",
      },
      {
        front: "inteligente",
        back: "intelligent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VEAgArfIEK",
      },
      {
        front: "italiana",
        back: "Italian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "taS7tw0s57",
      },
      {
        front: "italiano",
        back: "Italian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9f1DJYeJ5a",
      },
      {
        front: "madre",
        back: "mother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gPfGqTM2Vv",
      },
      {
        front: "madres",
        back: "mothers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M8DCv32QET",
      },
      {
        front: "mascota",
        back: "mascot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qqtJJcCAU7",
      },
      {
        front: "mascotas",
        back: "pets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MbcUGz8qU5",
      },
      {
        front: "nueve",
        back: "nine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pF10bdNFmd",
      },
      {
        front: "padre",
        back: "dad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WvWYJosaGz",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeña",
        back: "small",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fQ6RPl3WO2",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeño",
        back: "short",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xSjwJVbCEG",
      },
      {
        front: "simpática",
        back: "nice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8dz4sD2YsQ",
      },
      {
        front: "simpático",
        back: "sympathetic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9WIAyBctwe",
      },
      {
        front: "su",
        back: "his",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UCYImGNEHi",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "q3cpbhk0pz",
    title: "Unit 14",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ahora",
        back: "now",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HJx9yoXVK6",
      },
      {
        front: "aquí",
        back: "here",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g6sOw579M0",
      },
      {
        front: "carta",
        back: "letter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FJtMlzpmR8",
      },
      {
        front: "cartas",
        back: "cards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vtppP89dhg",
      },
      {
        front: "correo electrónico",
        back: "email",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dpUqAhkmG2",
      },
      {
        front: "cuál",
        back: "which one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "azhPtCJnKQ",
      },
      {
        front: "escribe",
        back: "writes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XLmFSCN0Vm",
      },
      {
        front: "escribes",
        back: "you write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K8bUnhAi5j",
      },
      {
        front: "escribir",
        back: "to write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LQRM2YOXaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "escribo",
        back: "I write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HWFMRt0fXw",
      },
      {
        front: "escritorio",
        back: "desk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1LhwMYgYkw",
      },
      {
        front: "escritorios",
        back: "desks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ukHR6GMVYN",
      },
      {
        front: "jefa",
        back: "boss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X4uTckFoRB",
      },
      {
        front: "jefas",
        back: "bosses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VkwoxP6dOz",
      },
      {
        front: "jefe",
        back: "chief",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UuOEQKr5Al",
      },
      {
        front: "las",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oe0Dmi9OHH",
      },
      {
        front: "lee",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wS04CnTm2I",
      },
      {
        front: "leer",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y4mdiNJKxJ",
      },
      {
        front: "lees",
        back: "you read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yM4CkaoAk1",
      },
      {
        front: "leo",
        back: "I read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J4XvYY4GFo",
      },
      {
        front: "los",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6MicH1lZij",
      },
      {
        front: "mensaje",
        back: "message",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YsM76OcLOe",
      },
      {
        front: "mensajes",
        back: "posts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LaqBP6GuFo",
      },
      {
        front: "mucho",
        back: "a lot of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BXU8Hx5HWS",
      },
      {
        front: "negocio",
        back: "deal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iBnKeZFTlk",
      },
      {
        front: "negocios",
        back: "business",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CiM5UM23qm",
      },
      {
        front: "nueva",
        back: "new",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nDTUrDa4tk",
      },
      {
        front: "nuevo",
        back: "new",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bbpoLlnF3g",
      },
      {
        front: "para",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RLFzuia43I",
      },
      {
        front: "poco",
        back: "little bit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hYdSYeqvxB",
      },
      {
        front: "problema",
        back: "issue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "va88GQPhz8",
      },
      {
        front: "problemas",
        back: "problems",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cVgdwPecI5",
      },
      {
        front: "secretaria",
        back: "Secretary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oriyepDbOd",
      },
      {
        front: "secretarias",
        back: "secretaries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gzku4lRe2d",
      },
      {
        front: "secretario",
        back: "secretary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fjL7FHAAbC",
      },
      {
        front: "tener",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FksTrYxo9p",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajo",
        back: "worked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OEPwsy2zEc",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajos",
        back: "works",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "knX8C45RYP",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "rtIMyakK5O",
    title: "Unit 14",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a veces",
        back: "sometimes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "avARUEOPfW",
      },
      {
        front: "aburrido",
        back: "bored",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u8Mni9sAfn",
      },
      {
        front: "bebé",
        back: "baby",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4mOPyQ2EtF",
      },
      {
        front: "bebés",
        back: "you drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jwwdhSLbHf",
      },
      {
        front: "conmigo",
        back: "with me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7TvxD3ZrWc",
      },
      {
        front: "contenta",
        back: "happy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CRJIopHewU",
      },
      {
        front: "contigo",
        back: "with you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ITfrx99iAM",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutar",
        back: "to enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "26Tvf34T1Y",
      },
      {
        front: "dormir",
        back: "to sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "INhMKydf0c",
      },
      {
        front: "emocionada",
        back: "moved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dGW2cGIgoN",
      },
      {
        front: "emocionado",
        back: "excited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZtVu4hpxLs",
      },
      {
        front: "emocionar",
        back: "thrill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sT19FleFVZ",
      },
      {
        front: "enferma",
        back: "sick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cw2ngvf4Zq",
      },
      {
        front: "enfermo",
        back: "sick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AwxgWGoQ5R",
      },
      {
        front: "enojada",
        back: "annoyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DWfpqK1tJr",
      },
      {
        front: "enojado",
        back: "angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WXFFe4kpSQ",
      },
      {
        front: "mamá",
        back: "breast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gFhnHX2AOY",
      },
      {
        front: "mamás",
        back: "moms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U7z2V6bqzm",
      },
      {
        front: "mañana",
        back: "morning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ChhJzbL37i",
      },
      {
        front: "me siento",
        back: "I feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yuGCgKlLA3",
      },
      {
        front: "nunca",
        back: "never",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RMjQaGBJ7e",
      },
      {
        front: "o",
        back: "either",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oU5ZRRzzd1",
      },
      {
        front: "otra vez",
        back: "again",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mdjsez1Bst",
      },
      {
        front: "papá",
        back: "potato",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UqDVYCk188",
      },
      {
        front: "por qué",
        back: "why",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8gwGSJK17r",
      },
      {
        front: "preocupado",
        back: "worried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iHtZ1r39B4",
      },
      {
        front: "qué",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ItqAJg6FVd",
      },
      {
        front: "tal",
        back: "how's it going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NZDYvwKGuf",
      },
      {
        front: "se siente",
        back: "it feels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hn7By95kYj",
      },
      {
        front: "siempre",
        back: "forever",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mfOxyrrkGi",
      },
      {
        front: "también",
        back: "also",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AmsGqT8OsF",
      },
      {
        front: "te sientes",
        back: "you feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KCXfKrslg8",
      },
      {
        front: "triste",
        back: "sad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Eq9SX5u73y",
      },
      {
        front: "un poco",
        back: "a little",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gmfVgMHYIN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "HhLUIleNaS",
    title: "Unit 15",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "amigos",
        back: "friends",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HJPReNfOJQ",
      },
      {
        front: "ciudades",
        back: "cities",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1CIX9zCSwv",
      },
      {
        front: "cuántas",
        back: "how many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vATI1KOV4n",
      },
      {
        front: "cuánto",
        back: "how much",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c3qp6ssDk3",
      },
      {
        front: "cuántos",
        back: "how many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RnTOPOX2lQ",
      },
      {
        front: "ellas",
        back: "they",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FZtW86u8gx",
      },
      {
        front: "ellos",
        back: "them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T4urTrMt70",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiamos",
        back: "we study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hBYabAjUKQ",
      },
      {
        front: "estudian",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9c3qsGhQ0i",
      },
      {
        front: "fines de semana",
        back: "weekends",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eC5pmzmnMj",
      },
      {
        front: "hablamos",
        back: "We speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TZwldgKMj9",
      },
      {
        front: "hablan",
        back: "speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6u5UZX5eSw",
      },
      {
        front: "hombres",
        back: "mens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jX4PG9IkEK",
      },
      {
        front: "jugador",
        back: "player",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3ay90Vn5uh",
      },
      {
        front: "jugadora",
        back: "player",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wzy4dQ885f",
      },
      {
        front: "jugadoras",
        back: "female players",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VahQ8bKOVH",
      },
      {
        front: "jugadores",
        back: "players",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DZQm16Nsz5",
      },
      {
        front: "muchas",
        back: "many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3Dt4brxlIW",
      },
      {
        front: "muchos",
        back: "Many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wnRcpFQFRh",
      },
      {
        front: "mujeres",
        back: "women",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bgImC5J4nu",
      },
      {
        front: "nosotras",
        back: "we",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LExTkrgRo9",
      },
      {
        front: "nosotros",
        back: "us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mu2Ih0QM6l",
      },
      {
        front: "señoras",
        back: "ladies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p9P13z7z5L",
      },
      {
        front: "señores",
        back: "Sirs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L6X1VxjcNe",
      },
      {
        front: "somos",
        back: "we are",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cq3bncnDwI",
      },
      {
        front: "son",
        back: "are",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Srpse0LqMY",
      },
      {
        front: "unas",
        back: "nail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FXsPAlrBmc",
      },
      {
        front: "universidades",
        back: "universities",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8TW9kxTRM9",
      },
      {
        front: "unos",
        back: "some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lmcmhLrsTc",
      },
      {
        front: "ustedes",
        back: "you guys",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZG7DwT86PU",
      },
      {
        front: "vacaciones",
        back: "Vacations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SRnwxpzqMt",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "oaYH4SY9t7",
    title: "Unit 16",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bonitas",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jKPABiO41W",
      },
      {
        front: "bonitos",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c678utljmi",
      },
      {
        front: "camisa",
        back: "shirt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t3N157u8nG",
      },
      {
        front: "camisas",
        back: "shirts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zSvmYL99o5",
      },
      {
        front: "camiseta",
        back: "T shirt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YcgIRVL4rg",
      },
      {
        front: "camisetas",
        back: "Tshirts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V8d3d6pT3v",
      },
      {
        front: "carteras",
        back: "wallets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mzr26ooYS6",
      },
      {
        front: "estas",
        back: "are",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SKMHdy1CSj",
      },
      {
        front: "estos",
        back: "these",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g9OouRgGQa",
      },
      {
        front: "grandes",
        back: "large",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2I1iiTTDCz",
      },
      {
        front: "interesantes",
        back: "interesting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C3vrCHQIBs",
      },
      {
        front: "mis",
        back: "my",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8qQLBLqn7",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitamos",
        back: "we need",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8z7zJIoUu5",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitan",
        back: "need",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7pr5yIJCSD",
      },
      {
        front: "nuevas",
        back: "new",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8vAybG9Gy1",
      },
      {
        front: "nuevos",
        back: "new",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "34XaBheTuY",
      },
      {
        front: "pantalones",
        back: "pants",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O1uIKzSYaz",
      },
      {
        front: "pantalón",
        back: "trousers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fr5nBnVxtF",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeñas",
        back: "little",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9Bqo6ivDJ2",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeños",
        back: "little ones",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1SiXKHLJ5t",
      },
      {
        front: "roja",
        back: "red",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S5OErXHYKh",
      },
      {
        front: "rojas",
        back: "red",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5Aw2r2Nj1V",
      },
      {
        front: "rojo",
        back: "red",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MzBXhMSkH4",
      },
      {
        front: "rojos",
        back: "reds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iRB9fizlIa",
      },
      {
        front: "sus",
        back: "their",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KHEKCkkN79",
      },
      {
        front: "tus",
        back: "your",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Sij2JYdmY8",
      },
      {
        front: "usamos",
        back: "we use",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gB8UYSYWCX",
      },
      {
        front: "usan",
        back: "use",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0sXKUDzmUr",
      },
      {
        front: "verde",
        back: "green",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yma0Vc88K8",
      },
      {
        front: "verdes",
        back: "green",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rMyVW8izus",
      },
      {
        front: "vestido",
        back: "dress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BiPch60L9Q",
      },
      {
        front: "vestidos",
        back: "dresses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "urhnl6O7Oe",
      },
      {
        front: "zapato",
        back: "shoe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "grngvxl3Ep",
      },
      {
        front: "zapatos",
        back: "shoes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ciro7zUE7C",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "XM0BwOQYol",
    title: "Unit 16",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "prestense21",
        back: "borrow21",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RvYjT3hLAZ",
      },
      {
        front: "prestense22",
        back: "borrow22",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cpOmYZxnRC",
      },
      {
        front: "prestense23",
        back: "borrow23",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rwxEbe7VkF",
      },
      {
        front: "prestense",
        back: "lend yourself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dzKpbptMHA",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "4kyYe9RtLv",
    title: "Unit 17",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BNTJo5QLr1",
      },
      {
        front: "aeropuerto",
        back: "airport",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KWoLjFcBJa",
      },
      {
        front: "aeropuertos",
        back: "airports",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TSsrDvPL8A",
      },
      {
        front: "al",
        back: "to the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TdVKlHW9GH",
      },
      {
        front: "al lado",
        back: "beside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4oh3NagJhc",
      },
      {
        front: "autobuses",
        back: "buses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q0SYKgZjcS",
      },
      {
        front: "autobús",
        back: "bus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fn15SaQfdG",
      },
      {
        front: "banco",
        back: "bank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K1hppofUKz",
      },
      {
        front: "bancos",
        back: "banks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WP73VVK9ZF",
      },
      {
        front: "calle",
        back: "street",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZRD6cSVRto",
      },
      {
        front: "calles",
        back: "streets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tDsdSMbLkg",
      },
      {
        front: "cerca",
        back: "near",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oNYcBHGDq8",
      },
      {
        front: "cerca de",
        back: "nearly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "48f8JmacOm",
      },
      {
        front: "del",
        back: "of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AhDrIojWzU",
      },
      {
        front: "derecha",
        back: "right",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wvQHMwmlAu",
      },
      {
        front: "el café",
        back: "the coffee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kZ4NgAAj62",
      },
      {
        front: "estaciones",
        back: "seasons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fgb0GE4IO2",
      },
      {
        front: "estación",
        back: "station",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a7xr7SXwzs",
      },
      {
        front: "estamos",
        back: "we're",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kXsHF3JN8G",
      },
      {
        front: "están",
        back: "is it so",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d74Qc8vLEC",
      },
      {
        front: "hospital",
        back: "hospital",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qhOJobPQnH",
      },
      {
        front: "hospitales",
        back: "hospitals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2vJIDCwKSY",
      },
      {
        front: "hotel",
        back: "hotel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SL8OpkqYky",
      },
      {
        front: "hoteles",
        back: "Hotels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "96N4Augaxx",
      },
      {
        front: "ir",
        back: "to go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A6FNH32mvR",
      },
      {
        front: "izquierda",
        back: "left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fDlMobuYOI",
      },
      {
        front: "lejos",
        back: "far",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3mdJ6g8N1e",
      },
      {
        front: "metro",
        back: "meter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "armF3y3oXh",
      },
      {
        front: "metros",
        back: "meters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DCyEZiycE3",
      },
      {
        front: "parque",
        back: "park",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GuBW2lHbm6",
      },
      {
        front: "parques",
        back: "parks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iEvLYgF7bV",
      },
      {
        front: "puerta",
        back: "gate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FrbOZBm6Pv",
      },
      {
        front: "puertas",
        back: "doors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZOjMyv2Fnc",
      },
      {
        front: "supermercados",
        back: "supermarkets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MQmxSNTarX",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tGnJ461L1m",
      },
      {
        front: "tren",
        back: "train",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0awEgeJJda",
      },
      {
        front: "trenes",
        back: "trains",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g4RLL2TAHS",
      },
      {
        front: "viajar",
        back: "travel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kXYGxjRe3n",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "6AnemBBUsd",
    title: "Unit 18",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrir",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ofduuHjse7",
      },
      {
        front: "aburridas",
        back: "boring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HduqImzv2m",
      },
      {
        front: "aburridos",
        back: "bored",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vpjK0sYJgX",
      },
      {
        front: "arroz",
        back: "rice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rvpou7fKfD",
      },
      {
        front: "buena",
        back: "good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "taBWEcwlvb",
      },
      {
        front: "buenas",
        back: "good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4JV2GHeIWW",
      },
      {
        front: "bueno",
        back: "well",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qqqMJDR0BV",
      },
      {
        front: "buenos",
        back: "good ones",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EQHwzl62DD",
      },
      {
        front: "caminar",
        back: "walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2BtTlaFfJI",
      },
      {
        front: "casas",
        back: "houses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "si0K8dmNVH",
      },
      {
        front: "comemos",
        back: "we eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gWD8vMwChY",
      },
      {
        front: "comen",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vjzpg8Opn2",
      },
      {
        front: "comida",
        back: "meal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KxcNsjMu8y",
      },
      {
        front: "correos electrónicos",
        back: "emails",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0VJdmxzpSp",
      },
      {
        front: "divertidas",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dwIgo3JJ6Y",
      },
      {
        front: "divertidos",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I6r34jwZSN",
      },
      {
        front: "escriben",
        back: "they write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0tsYUpHFHW",
      },
      {
        front: "escribimos",
        back: "we wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eVPktnylfi",
      },
      {
        front: "juntos",
        back: "together",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Ko47z8jYz",
      },
      {
        front: "leemos",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jwYSz6uoCL",
      },
      {
        front: "leen",
        back: "they read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d2PEc8WX2e",
      },
      {
        front: "mucha",
        back: "a lot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kTpCaoKN9Q",
      },
      {
        front: "mucho",
        back: "a lot of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3jFWUmKz8H",
      },
      {
        front: "periódico",
        back: "Newspaper",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yhQOUgs1CL",
      },
      {
        front: "periódicos",
        back: "newspapers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cpbTpORBBv",
      },
      {
        front: "playa",
        back: "beach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kb2SjTW3Zy",
      },
      {
        front: "playas",
        back: "Beaches",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wJKia1yVTM",
      },
      {
        front: "pollo",
        back: "chicken",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hSOARhUwXB",
      },
      {
        front: "pollos",
        back: "chickens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kN2SMWlsCv",
      },
      {
        front: "queremos",
        back: "we want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K8qNyC4enZ",
      },
      {
        front: "quieren",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DnWJwKQnZ3",
      },
      {
        front: "restaurantes",
        back: "restaurants",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RB03g7jVps",
      },
      {
        front: "sándwiches",
        back: "sandwiches",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1p8NVxRTRQ",
      },
      {
        front: "tarde",
        back: "afternoon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MX8yZtFcb0",
      },
      {
        front: "tardes",
        back: "afternoon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MInnUkOKbQ",
      },
      {
        front: "verano",
        back: "summer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "INTaiGFGWo",
      },
      {
        front: "veranos",
        back: "summers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MuspgphL3g",
      },
      {
        front: "viven",
        back: "they live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mXwsLEdQA4",
      },
      {
        front: "vivimos",
        back: "we live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FLjbYZXUTj",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "a37mgXe7nZ",
    title: "Unit 18",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abren",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ugoGFY4HXz",
      },
      {
        front: "abrimos",
        back: "we open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hQF5X07J6Z",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendemos",
        back: "we learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IW744t8f7N",
      },
      {
        front: "aprenden",
        back: "they learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hLA4l3Bja0",
      },
      {
        front: "beben",
        back: "they drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zgBJm18y3r",
      },
      {
        front: "comer una",
        back: "eat one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4V8ttapMzE",
      },
      {
        front: "compramos",
        back: "we bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1MMkYKyC93",
      },
      {
        front: "compran",
        back: "they buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5ZpnAQjFML",
      },
      {
        front: "ella come",
        back: "she eats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RBAlid0Kwq",
      },
      {
        front: "ellas escriben",
        back: "They write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aBoiRD9J2L",
      },
      {
        front: "ellos hablan",
        back: "they speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "suysf1o86v",
      },
      {
        front: "ellos leen",
        back: "they read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tZlc8nNfZg",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar español",
        back: "speak Spanish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SJKgNfwEfj",
      },
      {
        front: "leer este",
        back: "read this",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "InRR79B3N3",
      },
      {
        front: "necesita escribir",
        back: "need to write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZCCEQ3kp32",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitamos abrir",
        back: "we need to open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ruVQZhUy4L",
      },
      {
        front: "necesito comprar",
        back: "I need to buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SrNjr9jFHR",
      },
      {
        front: "nosotras vivimos",
        back: "we live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xnmHJTYl5E",
      },
      {
        front: "nosotros comemos",
        back: "we eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SVZ5buN5pM",
      },
      {
        front: "nosotros leemos",
        back: "we read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OW3THQfLpR",
      },
      {
        front: "quiere aprender",
        back: "He wants to learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Re9zZ5EUHj",
      },
      {
        front: "quiero beber",
        back: "I want to drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yJ2kfM2CTZ",
      },
      {
        front: "salen",
        back: "come out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vY2b7ArGBm",
      },
      {
        front: "salimos",
        back: "we went out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9BUIoBAJQi",
      },
      {
        front: "salir",
        back: "go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xpmWll0WSt",
      },
      {
        front: "toma",
        back: "taking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "58JUmJDsS1",
      },
      {
        front: "tomamos",
        back: "we take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VTAp3w74TQ",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar el",
        back: "take the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aq3nE0mvZU",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajamos",
        back: "we work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kwWw3UpHrQ",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajan",
        back: "they work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9viMaHJFbJ",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajar en",
        back: "work in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3IZhNdsYq1",
      },
      {
        front: "tú bebes",
        back: "you drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NzTBttNPEo",
      },
      {
        front: "tú escribes",
        back: "you write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yPP05rzjn9",
      },
      {
        front: "tú hablas",
        back: "you speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3elU1mlwya",
      },
      {
        front: "usted vive",
        back: "you live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pprG580QQh",
      },
      {
        front: "vivir en",
        back: "live in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xbBreBpmFD",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "aakPNup1SD",
    title: "Unit 19",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "algo",
        back: "something",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GJfSJ2EGpF",
      },
      {
        front: "azúcar",
        back: "sugar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6zu8T563fX",
      },
      {
        front: "bicicleta",
        back: "bike",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rS4VPr72uo",
      },
      {
        front: "bicicletas",
        back: "bikes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "StqKDbSgRz",
      },
      {
        front: "chica",
        back: "girl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VenwKNVSQv",
      },
      {
        front: "chicas",
        back: "girls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZupwDCCK4z",
      },
      {
        front: "chico",
        back: "guy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JN67IqPmL0",
      },
      {
        front: "chicos",
        back: "Boys",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PgsBcYU8J2",
      },
      {
        front: "chocolate",
        back: "Chocolat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a1qF19yLeJ",
      },
      {
        front: "chocolates",
        back: "chocolates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zaqxssC2eH",
      },
      {
        front: "correr",
        back: "rush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ut8aZ37kOs",
      },
      {
        front: "creo que",
        back: "I think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F2KtZPpDiZ",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujar",
        back: "to draw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b6KDmOkKsw",
      },
      {
        front: "elegante",
        back: "Elegant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SzzqyuxLhB",
      },
      {
        front: "elegantes",
        back: "elegant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mfWlmNBcZY",
      },
      {
        front: "esa",
        back: "that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "poMLLUxYB7",
      },
      {
        front: "ese",
        back: "that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SZnru5VA0V",
      },
      {
        front: "falda",
        back: "skirt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wtL0rTerfU",
      },
      {
        front: "faldas",
        back: "skirts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lZooSDpFXf",
      },
      {
        front: "favorito",
        back: "favorite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oDtQWfsptw",
      },
      {
        front: "favoritos",
        back: "favorites",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mrrFGKnxU4",
      },
      {
        front: "jugar",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gjAaFqZiAm",
      },
      {
        front: "me encanta",
        back: "I'm lovin 'it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UtAPHJyiWk",
      },
      {
        front: "me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NIKgfumY64",
      },
      {
        front: "gusta",
        back: "I like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8qdqQbHj4d",
      },
      {
        front: "música",
        back: "music",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ToQrCCn0fx",
      },
      {
        front: "nadar",
        back: "to swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "scjrUMjz1c",
      },
      {
        front: "pastel",
        back: "pie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LVAbeoBLUo",
      },
      {
        front: "pero",
        back: "but",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P4v5TSdQsp",
      },
      {
        front: "perros",
        back: "dogs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kbY1RbcgGt",
      },
      {
        front: "piscina",
        back: "pool",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fmPtdGWtP6",
      },
      {
        front: "piscinas",
        back: "swimming pools",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xYVXQEGamb",
      },
      {
        front: "porque",
        back: "because",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nokqMFLdB8",
      },
      {
        front: "queso",
        back: "cheese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b3UfqxpB7V",
      },
      {
        front: "quesos",
        back: "cheeses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T63cia3YzD",
      },
      {
        front: "ropa",
        back: "clothes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oxWgpfORCQ",
      },
      {
        front: "sombrero",
        back: "hat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JiWIMuXfT9",
      },
      {
        front: "sombreros",
        back: "hats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0d2Ppjy5iK",
      },
      {
        front: "te encanta",
        back: "You love it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uHu7HRlaJR",
      },
      {
        front: "te gusta",
        back: "you like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MWICTsoqcQ",
      },
      {
        front: "vieja",
        back: "old woman",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PHXt0k1p5A",
      },
      {
        front: "viejas",
        back: "old",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xkiA0sEugJ",
      },
      {
        front: "viejo",
        back: "old",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A6EyGgKtsx",
      },
      {
        front: "viejos",
        back: "old",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PJtRDniEkE",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "pT2RvHorcY",
    title: "Unit 19",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a menudo",
        back: "often",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yLeVXMOmby",
      },
      {
        front: "a qué hora",
        back: "what time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YFxm3IQX3t",
      },
      {
        front: "cine",
        back: "movies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JlEj5JL1Ss",
      },
      {
        front: "doce",
        back: "twelve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UqEjJs8abn",
      },
      {
        front: "domingos",
        back: "Sundays",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iZGMtAipkl",
      },
      {
        front: "días",
        back: "days",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zqSWhrlnTK",
      },
      {
        front: "hora",
        back: "time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LrVl6HsaNO",
      },
      {
        front: "horas",
        back: "hours",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qUuc9naJn6",
      },
      {
        front: "me ducho",
        back: "I shower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WxciRtpL66",
      },
      {
        front: "me levanto",
        back: "I get up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qBfVkQuuTu",
      },
      {
        front: "media",
        back: "half",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OyHSTSw6Di",
      },
      {
        front: "mirar",
        back: "watch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q5t7pZnCBo",
      },
      {
        front: "noche",
        back: "evening",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "59mDKAoYvx",
      },
      {
        front: "noches",
        back: "nights",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ttS9bZmbPu",
      },
      {
        front: "once",
        back: "eleven",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TGZM7wkuFo",
      },
      {
        front: "se ducha",
        back: "showering",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bVCfNimkLb",
      },
      {
        front: "se levanta",
        back: "he wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9fSxoMfr7a",
      },
      {
        front: "sábados",
        back: "saturdays",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3itGvYuOzM",
      },
      {
        front: "te duchas",
        back: "You have a shower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BaZfm7q34E",
      },
      {
        front: "te levantas",
        back: "you wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NKKv6fpGfO",
      },
      {
        front: "televisión",
        back: "TV",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "39OOFriPx0",
      },
      {
        front: "tengo que",
        back: "I have to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q58ZmNVvJz",
      },
      {
        front: "tiene que",
        back: "have to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9fWRwTR47n",
      },
      {
        front: "tienes que",
        back: "you have to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ASXT3L1AEV",
      },
      {
        front: "todas",
        back: "all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GwGRr9d8bz",
      },
      {
        front: "todo",
        back: "all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "koMS7tGYth",
      },
      {
        front: "todos",
        back: "everyone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p5VZenU0rb",
      },
      {
        front: "va",
        back: "goes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XXnN1hKmrM",
      },
      {
        front: "vamos",
        back: "we go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dsQYY961cG",
      },
      {
        front: "van",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l92KDM3wMe",
      },
      {
        front: "vas",
        back: "you go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PtgUSOHRGr",
      },
      {
        front: "voy",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eOaNhDADXd",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "V59VXgo4oT",
    title: "Unit 20",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "azul",
        back: "blue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ifX4viwguC",
      },
      {
        front: "azules",
        back: "blue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mzLIOgaxHj",
      },
      {
        front: "baño",
        back: "bathroom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KnAA9B4cNx",
      },
      {
        front: "baños",
        back: "toilets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E9fkWsQcou",
      },
      {
        front: "cama",
        back: "bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L2N5NaHVjX",
      },
      {
        front: "camas",
        back: "Beds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M3zcTqpfiR",
      },
      {
        front: "celulares",
        back: "cell phones",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "okAZRDQp9q",
      },
      {
        front: "cocina",
        back: "kitchen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iyABmBEodx",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinas",
        back: "kitchens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FxqD6PURfu",
      },
      {
        front: "compra",
        back: "purchase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7sf40We09R",
      },
      {
        front: "compro",
        back: "bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j9y6CY83YI",
      },
      {
        front: "debajo",
        back: "below",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rao4PRI7RA",
      },
      {
        front: "dormitorio",
        back: "bedroom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hi3yFdNpAS",
      },
      {
        front: "dormitorios",
        back: "bedrooms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KATRhivgeN",
      },
      {
        front: "esas",
        back: "those",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "igQ6YIejsL",
      },
      {
        front: "esos",
        back: "those",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LMGK1SKhGG",
      },
      {
        front: "estantería",
        back: "shelving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qg03OUln1c",
      },
      {
        front: "estanterías",
        back: "shelves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jh7p7vKIim",
      },
      {
        front: "habitaciones",
        back: "bedrooms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GpilKoKnoR",
      },
      {
        front: "habitación",
        back: "room",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TeBvpwgJgB",
      },
      {
        front: "hay",
        back: "there are",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "insZB5iwRn",
      },
      {
        front: "jardines",
        back: "gardens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q2ZgyD5GJ4",
      },
      {
        front: "jardín",
        back: "yard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1IkQGAO90c",
      },
      {
        front: "limpia",
        back: "clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zEW4hf0iHp",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiamos",
        back: "we clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "833xaBEkC4",
      },
      {
        front: "limpian",
        back: "they clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HqojSRixqg",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiar",
        back: "clean up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N6XzTmTcH6",
      },
      {
        front: "limpias",
        back: "clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AT8wJwStoj",
      },
      {
        front: "limpio",
        back: "cleansed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cSYkUuWydS",
      },
      {
        front: "moderna",
        back: "modern",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t2BIGzVeOh",
      },
      {
        front: "modernas",
        back: "modern",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9a8JBp8IKu",
      },
      {
        front: "moderno",
        back: "modern",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "68J2jWUU8s",
      },
      {
        front: "modernos",
        back: "modern",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VTQyxJzlLt",
      },
      {
        front: "nevera",
        back: "fridge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VWZS1JWG3d",
      },
      {
        front: "neveras",
        back: "refrigerators",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xAiEahrt2U",
      },
      {
        front: "pintamos",
        back: "we paint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YJBZrXtZfw",
      },
      {
        front: "pintan",
        back: "they paint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LDgI3SVEwB",
      },
      {
        front: "pintar",
        back: "to paint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lvwB4ko4RW",
      },
      {
        front: "pintas",
        back: "pints",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6XHyY4qhlt",
      },
      {
        front: "pinto",
        back: "I paint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u7dPoeqZbx",
      },
      {
        front: "planta",
        back: "plant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FXFFVoiuiZ",
      },
      {
        front: "plantas",
        back: "plants",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7DPukZLxoJ",
      },
      {
        front: "reloj",
        back: "watch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fUUwUL891j",
      },
      {
        front: "relojes",
        back: "clocks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IUMT0Nu5Ez",
      },
      {
        front: "sala",
        back: "room",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YpfSbF031A",
      },
      {
        front: "salas",
        back: "rooms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fKOedNRLBC",
      },
      {
        front: "silla",
        back: "chair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FjKDH2WVaG",
      },
      {
        front: "sillas",
        back: "chairs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZhEqVubn1B",
      },
      {
        front: "sobre",
        back: "on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g4FIN8cnZY",
      },
      {
        front: "teléfonos",
        back: "phones",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pMzaSFCigZ",
      },
      {
        front: "tenemos",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3HnKmMHy2c",
      },
      {
        front: "tienen",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wY7T5u2wt4",
      },
      {
        front: "ventana",
        back: "window",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VwlmmjTGR5",
      },
      {
        front: "ventanas",
        back: "windows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zalsPEYTJY",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "BoU6Wi6B6m",
    title: "Unit 21",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "blanca",
        back: "white",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XyZZpE0fjs",
      },
      {
        front: "blancas",
        back: "white",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nKbGYpycYs",
      },
      {
        front: "blanco",
        back: "white",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pSBAXP9g2t",
      },
      {
        front: "blancos",
        back: "white",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O9tOz1fbJd",
      },
      {
        front: "botella",
        back: "bottle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IUUtr2O2RI",
      },
      {
        front: "botellas",
        back: "bottles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R1h7PvLF42",
      },
      {
        front: "camareras",
        back: "waitresses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oxgf6VR18I",
      },
      {
        front: "camarero",
        back: "waiter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MtbZRAuT40",
      },
      {
        front: "camareros",
        back: "Waiters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HmObiRsMDf",
      },
      {
        front: "cerveza",
        back: "beer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JfDY8d9wrE",
      },
      {
        front: "cervezas",
        back: "beers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XTCNWSSXn0",
      },
      {
        front: "cuchara",
        back: "spoon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lejTLV45JW",
      },
      {
        front: "cucharas",
        back: "spoons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PyjBalUqWn",
      },
      {
        front: "cuchillo",
        back: "knife",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hFANJgBr8p",
      },
      {
        front: "cuchillos",
        back: "knives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qzy6qhm34R",
      },
      {
        front: "cuenta",
        back: "bill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h4BBI0Pcte",
      },
      {
        front: "frijol",
        back: "beans",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cq5ufb8fcg",
      },
      {
        front: "frita",
        back: "fried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZlORg9ojHe",
      },
      {
        front: "menú",
        back: "menu",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9TW0UVe6UG",
      },
      {
        front: "menús",
        back: "menus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vg4FSPxTpf",
      },
      {
        front: "mesa",
        back: "desk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yEmXhFyznS",
      },
      {
        front: "mesas",
        back: "tables",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KFBwRvEUjY",
      },
      {
        front: "otra",
        back: "other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7HE6wXsdJd",
      },
      {
        front: "otro",
        back: "other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VPVxU8vA8o",
      },
      {
        front: "paga",
        back: "pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "InJdEjL4Hm",
      },
      {
        front: "pagan",
        back: "they pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tbQ3xlLr1j",
      },
      {
        front: "pagar",
        back: "to pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eZcHdp2otN",
      },
      {
        front: "pagas",
        back: "you pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5l8kdCYIXh",
      },
      {
        front: "pago",
        back: "I pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cuHG54cXTo",
      },
      {
        front: "pescado",
        back: "fish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PlFxpkVSI4",
      },
      {
        front: "pescados",
        back: "fish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "085cAsjNSH",
      },
      {
        front: "plato",
        back: "plate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "srTGV04CdP",
      },
      {
        front: "platos",
        back: "plates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jrUykKWe9w",
      },
      {
        front: "postre",
        back: "dessert",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F0TOrTGvzH",
      },
      {
        front: "postres",
        back: "desserts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wi4QvtE4hs",
      },
      {
        front: "puede traer",
        back: "you can bring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I1JwAtsQDP",
      },
      {
        front: "quisiera",
        back: "I'd like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GYvuiUmq64",
      },
      {
        front: "sal",
        back: "Salt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "smboZPjI5n",
      },
      {
        front: "sin",
        back: "without",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "16A5dcGmZW",
      },
      {
        front: "sopa",
        back: "Soup",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gt8gtrBFz7",
      },
      {
        front: "sopas",
        back: "soups",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KBRVVTtVU8",
      },
      {
        front: "un plato",
        back: "a dish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ue2iOA1ISS",
      },
      {
        front: "vaso",
        back: "glass",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwDca1yVjy",
      },
      {
        front: "vasos",
        back: "glasses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FH8ncnpxlJ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tL7bSi7k3J",
    title: "Unit 21",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abuelas",
        back: "grandmothers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PvctBXUati",
      },
      {
        front: "abuelo",
        back: "grandfather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BNqCZhhXos",
      },
      {
        front: "abuelos",
        back: "grandparents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xFomyUvMli",
      },
      {
        front: "americanas",
        back: "american",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aKNxBWmqRB",
      },
      {
        front: "americano",
        back: "American",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "81KRUw6YnX",
      },
      {
        front: "baloncesto",
        back: "basketball",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7k6F4Lpihb",
      },
      {
        front: "conciertos",
        back: "concerts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O7QXlbrla4",
      },
      {
        front: "deporte",
        back: "sport",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PKsQJykF6B",
      },
      {
        front: "deportes",
        back: "sports",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wMJkWreYh1",
      },
      {
        front: "escuchar",
        back: "to listen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H28RE2Fs5l",
      },
      {
        front: "familias",
        back: "families",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pS1JNdigyl",
      },
      {
        front: "hermanas",
        back: "sisters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WcPhYEDZ6c",
      },
      {
        front: "hermano",
        back: "brother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ocwaeOSzQR",
      },
      {
        front: "hermanos",
        back: "brothers and sisters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yp6iyc5gxP",
      },
      {
        front: "le encanta",
        back: "he loves it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RuJqK5CNFa",
      },
      {
        front: "le gusta",
        back: "likes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gmJwN45tit",
      },
      {
        front: "marido",
        back: "husband",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0vkbldd91i",
      },
      {
        front: "mayor",
        back: "higher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nyymsWHvnB",
      },
      {
        front: "mayores",
        back: "greater",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aPqHhx7V6v",
      },
      {
        front: "menor",
        back: "minor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ICfPJ9MVFl",
      },
      {
        front: "menores",
        back: "minors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "90fQ032U9Y",
      },
      {
        front: "nos encanta",
        back: "we love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gjNAtOeJUw",
      },
      {
        front: "nos gusta",
        back: "we like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lI5FMODewX",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestra",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yg00LcaTQ3",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestras",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MMlNHXq2T2",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestro",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QIM3ty3lpX",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestros",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cYbxtEf4A6",
      },
      {
        front: "padres",
        back: "fathers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WHiEYzeVE3",
      },
      {
        front: "películas",
        back: "films",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8O4Epry8j",
      },
      {
        front: "se llaman",
        back: "called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CHMlGkGKUA",
      },
      {
        front: "simpáticas",
        back: "nice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QZohBAacfW",
      },
      {
        front: "simpático",
        back: "sympathetic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YXQkliw1Bz",
      },
      {
        front: "simpáticos",
        back: "nice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YN2T84kYbK",
      },
      {
        front: "toca",
        back: "touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2eZ7hMsaZ4",
      },
      {
        front: "tocamos",
        back: "we touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cyd7mojbZl",
      },
      {
        front: "tocan",
        back: "touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L6qC8zFThu",
      },
      {
        front: "tocar",
        back: "touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3f2r3NtZit",
      },
      {
        front: "tocas",
        back: "you touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nI2e8oW8gI",
      },
      {
        front: "toco",
        back: "I play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J936oWD3gJ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "6eMvcR09pd",
    title: "Unit 22",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abre",
        back: "opens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I2YxUQ2zlr",
      },
      {
        front: "barata",
        back: "cheap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kAlzbOhxom",
      },
      {
        front: "baratas",
        back: "cheap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0N6aF93U5L",
      },
      {
        front: "barato",
        back: "cheap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NUcar06kCp",
      },
      {
        front: "baratos",
        back: "cheap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JiGVndYv8s",
      },
      {
        front: "busca",
        back: "search",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DD8YhXyNYS",
      },
      {
        front: "buscamos",
        back: "we seek",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TRh5biKEmF",
      },
      {
        front: "buscar",
        back: "seek",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u7qQSSNip8",
      },
      {
        front: "buscas",
        back: "you seek",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YVXv5SjCRp",
      },
      {
        front: "busco",
        back: "I search",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QIIYfzoBCz",
      },
      {
        front: "cara",
        back: "expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AzpvQAtPwq",
      },
      {
        front: "caras",
        back: "faces",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qImjYFtrxf",
      },
      {
        front: "caro",
        back: "expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t0k4le9Kvv",
      },
      {
        front: "caros",
        back: "expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tl3tzoA6mP",
      },
      {
        front: "catorce",
        back: "fourteen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yEvGjVgkSk",
      },
      {
        front: "cierra",
        back: "close",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OfYPTksdE6",
      },
      {
        front: "cuesta",
        back: "cost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eHuWUZEQ0B",
      },
      {
        front: "cuestan",
        back: "they cost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ktZvOr0ScL",
      },
      {
        front: "de compras",
        back: "Shopping",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f3q0LTyI5B",
      },
      {
        front: "diecinueve",
        back: "nighteen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3RMlmvxxSD",
      },
      {
        front: "dieciocho",
        back: "eighteen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "axJcyhFCRE",
      },
      {
        front: "diecisiete",
        back: "seventeen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jEQQo9M3ml",
      },
      {
        front: "dieciséis",
        back: "sixteen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f13jXjodsK",
      },
      {
        front: "dólar",
        back: "dollar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vfI2cbYD03",
      },
      {
        front: "dólares",
        back: "Dollars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uNdpL3Ielt",
      },
      {
        front: "en efectivo",
        back: "cash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "foomTR9U7z",
      },
      {
        front: "me puedo probar",
        back: "I can try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G4Hrjqoao1",
      },
      {
        front: "mí",
        back: "my",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ryS1Dc6neR",
      },
      {
        front: "pesos",
        back: "pesos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6pbiviS9IG",
      },
      {
        front: "precio",
        back: "price",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtactHKBt8",
      },
      {
        front: "precios",
        back: "prices",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hw33ZjNxdY",
      },
      {
        front: "probador",
        back: "fitting room",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SsAgsrIRDE",
      },
      {
        front: "probadores",
        back: "testers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1EgPpFYkMy",
      },
      {
        front: "quince",
        back: "fifteen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "58Ulnthn6C",
      },
      {
        front: "tallas",
        back: "sizes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rpo31RyUIY",
      },
      {
        front: "tarjeta de crédito",
        back: "credit card",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LIP27CqJWW",
      },
      {
        front: "ti",
        back: "you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E3FDZoSfZf",
      },
      {
        front: "tienda",
        back: "shop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q9x8RAkP3A",
      },
      {
        front: "tiendas",
        back: "stores",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sdRYeuv7Ei",
      },
      {
        front: "trece",
        back: "thirteen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yzNMqWFTsv",
      },
      {
        front: "veinte",
        back: "twenty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QJFpSEUOEm",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "pMgfVLPmO7",
    title: "Unit 23",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abierta",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EcvE3kaZYD",
      },
      {
        front: "abiertas",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LsTb3WCQTd",
      },
      {
        front: "abierto",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oua6kU2hM0",
      },
      {
        front: "abiertos",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cCukauRnic",
      },
      {
        front: "altas",
        back: "tall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aEugpGBW44",
      },
      {
        front: "altos",
        back: "tall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QpdqZxtBaG",
      },
      {
        front: "amarilla",
        back: "yellow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DwF9XPlxV2",
      },
      {
        front: "amarillas",
        back: "yellow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sU65R7Plev",
      },
      {
        front: "amarillo",
        back: "yellow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4CZpkYAJZH",
      },
      {
        front: "amarillos",
        back: "yellow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PNLO9cFes6",
      },
      {
        front: "cansadas",
        back: "tired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZNzDa1HO7w",
      },
      {
        front: "cansado",
        back: "tired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2hmTd0x9Iq",
      },
      {
        front: "cansados",
        back: "tired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QGyD61gpH0",
      },
      {
        front: "emocionadas",
        back: "excited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gIHiU1ZUYq",
      },
      {
        front: "emocionados",
        back: "excited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V54Htpbw8w",
      },
      {
        front: "enfermos",
        back: "sick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2nDcUq05i8",
      },
      {
        front: "enojado",
        back: "angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZX4BFFabgd",
      },
      {
        front: "enojados",
        back: "angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SUIQSGCPy3",
      },
      {
        front: "es divertido",
        back: "it's fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vrkogNAoj7",
      },
      {
        front: "es grande",
        back: "is big",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "601jaFPkw5",
      },
      {
        front: "es muy simpático",
        back: "Is very nice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YumF9mUonm",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiosa",
        back: "studious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VWQ84DJJzU",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiosas",
        back: "studious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t7D9SjS0HI",
      },
      {
        front: "estudioso",
        back: "studious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yx3LjtWZJC",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiosos",
        back: "scholars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "swFBvDNFMd",
      },
      {
        front: "felices",
        back: "happy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K9PBMMPqGz",
      },
      {
        front: "inteligentes",
        back: "smart",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gGXajwxcNr",
      },
      {
        front: "limpia",
        back: "clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aguOoWD8Mb",
      },
      {
        front: "limpias",
        back: "clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M5KeRkk4sY",
      },
      {
        front: "limpio",
        back: "cleansed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2EQaNs5xI9",
      },
      {
        front: "morenas",
        back: "brunettes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lGwzS2Tadf",
      },
      {
        front: "moreno",
        back: "Brown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZssR1X9chY",
      },
      {
        front: "morenos",
        back: "brown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G6ZKSs2DT1",
      },
      {
        front: "negra",
        back: "black",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qIgFyFvdlV",
      },
      {
        front: "negras",
        back: "black",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Pmd2w7fCvl",
      },
      {
        front: "negro",
        back: "black",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vDXMop0h0S",
      },
      {
        front: "negros",
        back: "black",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LkuQxH5t67",
      },
      {
        front: "nerviosa",
        back: "nervous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tKGXVkPOWF",
      },
      {
        front: "nerviosas",
        back: "nervous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "674pliYJVW",
      },
      {
        front: "nervioso",
        back: "nervous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xTVqqN6lSg",
      },
      {
        front: "nerviosos",
        back: "nervous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jOn2afCpMt",
      },
      {
        front: "ocupadas",
        back: "busy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4eT7l6Qqv2",
      },
      {
        front: "ocupado",
        back: "occupied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8R2vUUq8wy",
      },
      {
        front: "ocupados",
        back: "busy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6OiACPocp8",
      },
      {
        front: "perezosa",
        back: "lazy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0FZtZRDhMW",
      },
      {
        front: "perezosas",
        back: "lazy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dBvG0Bxx1n",
      },
      {
        front: "perezoso",
        back: "lazy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "740Oq6x2lq",
      },
      {
        front: "perezosos",
        back: "lazy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mclHHJlbak",
      },
      {
        front: "persona",
        back: "person",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I3Ieq5bn0C",
      },
      {
        front: "personas",
        back: "people",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pPmVQqIOiM",
      },
      {
        front: "preocupado",
        back: "worried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8DnzCy2vBc",
      },
      {
        front: "preocupados",
        back: "worried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZCHbRYg4rG",
      },
      {
        front: "responsable",
        back: "responsible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SedhfYwpFx",
      },
      {
        front: "responsables",
        back: "responsible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q7H7TabSs3",
      },
      {
        front: "rubias",
        back: "blondes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VLtSp5jAyx",
      },
      {
        front: "rubio",
        back: "blond",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UzwUrmgC1l",
      },
      {
        front: "rubios",
        back: "blondes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZX4HVgq84Z",
      },
      {
        front: "sorprendidas",
        back: "surprised",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oLhCuCPXBu",
      },
      {
        front: "sorprendido",
        back: "Surprised",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aFdUZfryGR",
      },
      {
        front: "sucia",
        back: "dirty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z9aS0SH6wV",
      },
      {
        front: "sucias",
        back: "dirty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wmOPcppOAH",
      },
      {
        front: "sucio",
        back: "dirty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SUrkCmzb7n",
      },
      {
        front: "sucios",
        back: "dirty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xZDoRKJRt4",
      },
      {
        front: "tristes",
        back: "sad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hSSHkbbN8Q",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jHbSzQ4GDz",
    title: "Unit 23",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "tobe1",
        back: "tobe1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jep99Z2EFQ",
      },
      {
        front: "tobe2",
        back: "tobe2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HVuWrkNoj8",
      },
      {
        front: "tobe3",
        back: "tobe3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zgctDPwGsI",
      },
      {
        front: "tobe",
        back: "tobe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5DRyaXQdI6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0PrmryTuaU",
    title: "Unit 24",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a mí",
        back: "to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dHuJvJy1aj",
      },
      {
        front: "a nosotros",
        back: "us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j4LxW49nnh",
      },
      {
        front: "a ti",
        back: "to you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NH2wUo0s1c",
      },
      {
        front: "a usted",
        back: "to you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cJARRdQXrl",
      },
      {
        front: "a ustedes",
        back: "to you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3X1KEhxrFX",
      },
      {
        front: "a él",
        back: "to the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OjhQNRTMm9",
      },
      {
        front: "aquel",
        back: "that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2VOukgIQej",
      },
      {
        front: "aquella",
        back: "that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nFiJjjGyR4",
      },
      {
        front: "aquellas",
        back: "those",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cfGDkc5a9b",
      },
      {
        front: "aquellos",
        back: "those",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SSv0Giqd88",
      },
      {
        front: "caballo",
        back: "horse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z8evNNduaO",
      },
      {
        front: "caballos",
        back: "horses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nCfgBtdKRW",
      },
      {
        front: "camina",
        back: "walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v5hXJ02TqA",
      },
      {
        front: "caminan",
        back: "they walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NFQcM7q0aV",
      },
      {
        front: "caminas",
        back: "you walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d8Jj4EweLX",
      },
      {
        front: "camino",
        back: "path",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qsjx3O9og7",
      },
      {
        front: "corre",
        back: "run",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jwmCQf5zK0",
      },
      {
        front: "corremos",
        back: "we run",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pD8LZjU5mO",
      },
      {
        front: "corren",
        back: "they run",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oMnKs6bU9T",
      },
      {
        front: "corres",
        back: "you run",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KjiFct7BaN",
      },
      {
        front: "corro",
        back: "I run",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QmTSutmPxU",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutan",
        back: "enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E6xiORxl5a",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutar",
        back: "to enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aLGXOuUdft",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutas",
        back: "you enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CZJWlagXKb",
      },
      {
        front: "disfruto",
        back: "I enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "loZ7xrdPV2",
      },
      {
        front: "les encanta",
        back: "they love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwus5OWHPI",
      },
      {
        front: "les gusta",
        back: "they like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hduErrammx",
      },
      {
        front: "montan",
        back: "they ride",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nb0CL0vc3N",
      },
      {
        front: "montar",
        back: "mount",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m16T5tnOWq",
      },
      {
        front: "montas",
        back: "you ride",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ckk8DvasUQ",
      },
      {
        front: "normalmente",
        back: "usually",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "39b6aWrl7m",
      },
      {
        front: "para ella",
        back: "for her",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PCm16muhSM",
      },
      {
        front: "para nosotros",
        back: "for us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5C75QTluQ9",
      },
      {
        front: "para",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HhhtiSECMx",
      },
      {
        front: "él",
        back: "for him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tC02JxBQfR",
      },
      {
        front: "pasa",
        back: "happens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LnsmXgikvJ",
      },
      {
        front: "pasan",
        back: "pass",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lLBfOfr9mn",
      },
      {
        front: "pasar",
        back: "happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fbX5vPEFeu",
      },
      {
        front: "pasas",
        back: "raisins",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aIJQtT3Gn3",
      },
      {
        front: "paso",
        back: "He passed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fz27nMRgKD",
      },
      {
        front: "regalo",
        back: "present",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8IpfQt3KOM",
      },
      {
        front: "río",
        back: "river",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "47huRAa8RQ",
      },
      {
        front: "ríos",
        back: "rivers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l7oeCmoEGL",
      },
      {
        front: "tenis",
        back: "tennis",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DszD0h7E6v",
      },
      {
        front: "tiempo",
        back: "weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bdCc65puoN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7ZALc6yINd",
    title: "Unit 25",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "Alemania",
        back: "Germany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qljzlqyZ27",
      },
      {
        front: "alemania",
        back: "Germany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zd0ZythaXi",
      },
      {
        front: "algunas",
        back: "some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dyf0ETAkT1",
      },
      {
        front: "algunos",
        back: "Some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t7QgKrvZ2s",
      },
      {
        front: "amar",
        back: "to love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B17bKArlXc",
      },
      {
        front: "ayuda",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GQQBztrAKp",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudamos",
        back: "we help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fqIrFK7Hjc",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudan",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fGSrE7bDYn",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudar",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ptw4heQNS0",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudas",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fo7rSHHZ59",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudo",
        back: "helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wuFkSqwB4N",
      },
      {
        front: "conoce",
        back: "known",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4CMv46FVYt",
      },
      {
        front: "conocemos",
        back: "we know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lnQumB3Ynq",
      },
      {
        front: "conocer",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sv45mAjyvr",
      },
      {
        front: "conoces",
        back: "you know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2gTq7p4Hcz",
      },
      {
        front: "conozco",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Du6lxgbqsn",
      },
      {
        front: "diferente",
        back: "different",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BGpvtDGku6",
      },
      {
        front: "diferentes",
        back: "different",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QHitqARw5w",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñar",
        back: "to teach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FYpZSZBpV8",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñas",
        back: "you teach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GBkRi4QNsS",
      },
      {
        front: "gente",
        back: "people",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ydNcIjkAYc",
      },
      {
        front: "llama",
        back: "call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gdhmYlKv2C",
      },
      {
        front: "llamamos",
        back: "we call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M8bJ9xzj21",
      },
      {
        front: "llaman",
        back: "call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UjD5B9yIPU",
      },
      {
        front: "llamar",
        back: "to call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L0NR5NpCpP",
      },
      {
        front: "llamas",
        back: "calls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zyZQCoqTAM",
      },
      {
        front: "llamo",
        back: "called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xUDUAvbyxs",
      },
      {
        front: "lugar",
        back: "place",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aCnLoM4yIs",
      },
      {
        front: "lugares",
        back: "places",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iEeaSTYLh7",
      },
      {
        front: "maestras",
        back: "teachers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cYfFT4hOSw",
      },
      {
        front: "maestro",
        back: "teacher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZhuuONCzZN",
      },
      {
        front: "maestros",
        back: "teachers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wfEqpK7860",
      },
      {
        front: "médicas",
        back: "medical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TPYgFFGacN",
      },
      {
        front: "médico",
        back: "medical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nuLWNMK0mk",
      },
      {
        front: "médicos",
        back: "doctors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h9U0NuVUUM",
      },
      {
        front: "niñas",
        back: "girls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bGU3nn7lxw",
      },
      {
        front: "niños",
        back: "kids",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZT6p9pxciW",
      },
      {
        front: "parte",
        back: "part",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ngbuAfbxJq",
      },
      {
        front: "partes",
        back: "parts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rj4BAYmOdw",
      },
      {
        front: "país",
        back: "country",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C0rjdUrwY7",
      },
      {
        front: "países",
        back: "countries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v3I9yoM9XQ",
      },
      {
        front: "pueblos",
        back: "towns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2l9VqzIBtI",
      },
      {
        front: "tele",
        back: "TV",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bGlGSaHK30",
      },
      {
        front: "usualmente",
        back: "usually",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VzaRdt37Bd",
      },
      {
        front: "ve",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jwDjrvlkGQ",
      },
      {
        front: "vemos",
        back: "we see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GNiPQHGMhT",
      },
      {
        front: "ven",
        back: "come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K8BsHbqRby",
      },
      {
        front: "veo",
        back: "I see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "91owKneO05",
      },
      {
        front: "ver",
        back: "see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oYAKToMHTl",
      },
      {
        front: "ves",
        back: "you see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "woLNcyHpl6",
      },
      {
        front: "visita",
        back: "visit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MG9mR7u80k",
      },
      {
        front: "visitamos",
        back: "we visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4bzxyWxXzE",
      },
      {
        front: "visitan",
        back: "they visit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q8et8434oO",
      },
      {
        front: "visitar",
        back: "to visit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NPOxu5GjeN",
      },
      {
        front: "visitas",
        back: "visits",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NRw1YfxQiG",
      },
      {
        front: "visito",
        back: "visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KjZQkK7oKQ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "cCyYBvYpzq",
    title: "Unit 25",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrigo",
        back: "coat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uPTcg9MyvR",
      },
      {
        front: "abrigos",
        back: "coats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RbaINtQHhD",
      },
      {
        front: "adulto",
        back: "adult",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DaExbkJ7jj",
      },
      {
        front: "adultos",
        back: "Adults",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1IO9PNyLTE",
      },
      {
        front: "animal",
        back: "animal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B8FOXcQqFg",
      },
      {
        front: "animales",
        back: "animals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fVbMnI2jSG",
      },
      {
        front: "bailan",
        back: "they dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lxyRu9Q0rL",
      },
      {
        front: "bailar",
        back: "to dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jk1SfXacBx",
      },
      {
        front: "bailas",
        back: "you dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PvFD9tlvdU",
      },
      {
        front: "bailo",
        back: "I danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q30WBvYDFd",
      },
      {
        front: "calor",
        back: "heat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "szuMslFjKN",
      },
      {
        front: "cuántos años",
        back: "how many years",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tq3ACtOlHf",
      },
      {
        front: "de verdad",
        back: "for real",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YYIrWV0x9n",
      },
      {
        front: "frío",
        back: "cold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ShVEFrohyr",
      },
      {
        front: "ganas",
        back: "desire",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zYQabaw3pg",
      },
      {
        front: "gris",
        back: "grey",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LO2m2PMhAw",
      },
      {
        front: "grises",
        back: "gray",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1cWIScB0tN",
      },
      {
        front: "hambre",
        back: "hungry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wj5W4phYzL",
      },
      {
        front: "jugos",
        back: "juices",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nyX2v9d7wj",
      },
      {
        front: "jóvenes",
        back: "youths",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "70w6kX1NmV",
      },
      {
        front: "larga",
        back: "long",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u12XkGhp8J",
      },
      {
        front: "largas",
        back: "long",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tUi5qepQi8",
      },
      {
        front: "largo",
        back: "long",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3ASz2x8o2F",
      },
      {
        front: "largos",
        back: "long",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9WlrSCSWhH",
      },
      {
        front: "marrones",
        back: "browns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FS0yyxKJeA",
      },
      {
        front: "marrón",
        back: "Brown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XiJBHjfQsi",
      },
      {
        front: "miedo",
        back: "fear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yZT53twsJT",
      },
      {
        front: "pizza",
        back: "Pizza",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dl653lNfhD",
      },
      {
        front: "pizzas",
        back: "pizza",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0JMOYGdsma",
      },
      {
        front: "puesto",
        back: "Market Stall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pqRJGyUrm4",
      },
      {
        front: "sed",
        back: "thirst",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nC2MEOnEJM",
      },
      {
        front: "señoritas",
        back: "ladies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Pkq6VosgtQ",
      },
      {
        front: "sueño",
        back: "sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EbcUtDlUvs",
      },
      {
        front: "veinticinco",
        back: "twenty-five",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ANpRtbqZ7i",
      },
      {
        front: "veinticuatro",
        back: "twenty four",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "185a16ikaF",
      },
      {
        front: "veintidós",
        back: "twenty two",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aBpBWa1Y9P",
      },
      {
        front: "veintitrés",
        back: "twenty three",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "njYvV7DF2L",
      },
      {
        front: "veintiuno",
        back: "twenty one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ic0FD2X2T8",
      },
      {
        front: "veintiún",
        back: "twenty one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hPcPoJWA8T",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ZESC1yaZAE",
    title: "Unit 26",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cursos",
        back: "courses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ccYb7WnPTk",
      },
      {
        front: "me",
        back: "I",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0I7NN0fwlO",
      },
      {
        front: "me ama",
        back: "Loves Me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "exVG1PZCkB",
      },
      {
        front: "me ayudas",
        back: "you help me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uUWg40JXrR",
      },
      {
        front: "me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PQARkGJlOm",
      },
      {
        front: "compra",
        back: "you buy me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8mBphwzgdd",
      },
      {
        front: "me conoce",
        back: "knows me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r9Z71LsdNF",
      },
      {
        front: "me enseña",
        back: "teaches me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wia3MQfdbl",
      },
      {
        front: "me escucha",
        back: "do you listen me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KmQ27m8kJS",
      },
      {
        front: "me llaman",
        back: "they call me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5fMNxu6A8o",
      },
      {
        front: "me necesita",
        back: "she needs me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o12fG6lW57",
      },
      {
        front: "muñeca",
        back: "wrist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d7wCWlrJtB",
      },
      {
        front: "muñecas",
        back: "dolls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EHq9lbyRlq",
      },
      {
        front: "nos",
        back: "us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ya9FxyLd8w",
      },
      {
        front: "nos ayudan",
        back: "they help us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xCkIuQTi42",
      },
      {
        front: "nos compra",
        back: "buy us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hY9E63Ppmx",
      },
      {
        front: "nos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x5mKCGrABp",
      },
      {
        front: "conocen",
        back: "they know us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DvOGMe36jY",
      },
      {
        front: "nos escuchan",
        back: "they listen to us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZAxIDJzF44",
      },
      {
        front: "nos llamas",
        back: "you call us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gZpG7OeliL",
      },
      {
        front: "nos visita",
        back: "visits us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GYnWCJryac",
      },
      {
        front: "te",
        back: "tea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YL6FcGjZbC",
      },
      {
        front: "te amo",
        back: "love you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5Wk73IF0Q6",
      },
      {
        front: "te ayudo",
        back: "do I help you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NOywLRRv4G",
      },
      {
        front: "te compra",
        back: "buys you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MIPnIPvS4b",
      },
      {
        front: "te conozco",
        back: "I know you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oNwUGcq2WV",
      },
      {
        front: "te llamamos",
        back: "we call you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9PK11Z4Y6D",
      },
      {
        front: "te necesito",
        back: "I need you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LFSUkxpUWt",
      },
      {
        front: "te visitan",
        back: "they visit you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TcRWvhcLbe",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "VJuGdJngwn",
    title: "Unit 27",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "almuerzo",
        back: "lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q6ASkoukUA",
      },
      {
        front: "antes",
        back: "before",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fooyuX4SKG",
      },
      {
        front: "cada",
        back: "each",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JFp4VCMWRC",
      },
      {
        front: "cena",
        back: "Dinner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xrP3Io2JWV",
      },
      {
        front: "cosa",
        back: "stuff",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YQmJw80fzj",
      },
      {
        front: "cosas",
        back: "things",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e42XFzyxmL",
      },
      {
        front: "demasiado",
        back: "too",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v4nZ2gLmNt",
      },
      {
        front: "desayuno",
        back: "breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QmQJwH1gX1",
      },
      {
        front: "después",
        back: "after",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w6nCxE7dtW",
      },
      {
        front: "diario",
        back: "diary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T7xDzkPSgd",
      },
      {
        front: "diarios",
        back: "diaries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iL8dwvVYaK",
      },
      {
        front: "difícil",
        back: "hard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MdTMpXKUCv",
      },
      {
        front: "difíciles",
        back: "difficult",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "15jUKAZtJQ",
      },
      {
        front: "fáciles",
        back: "easy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EvfwHSzXDY",
      },
      {
        front: "hace",
        back: "make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ymd8dRjK8Y",
      },
      {
        front: "hacemos",
        back: "we make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Prq1wSVDUj",
      },
      {
        front: "hacen",
        back: "make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YYRJ6B6tTh",
      },
      {
        front: "hacer",
        back: "to do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RXyxuvBI2N",
      },
      {
        front: "haces",
        back: "you do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "675aMc7u4P",
      },
      {
        front: "hago",
        back: "do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A1aCcbvYud",
      },
      {
        front: "levantarse",
        back: "get up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v0l0mVPQU1",
      },
      {
        front: "me pongo",
        back: "I wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZlJF5T9vFC",
      },
      {
        front: "ponerse",
        back: "to put on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wb8baTMC36",
      },
      {
        front: "sale",
        back: "comes out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MRaDbu7l7A",
      },
      {
        front: "sales",
        back: "you go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ETMNXO8p7F",
      },
      {
        front: "salgo",
        back: "I go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YNeYPmOKBR",
      },
      {
        front: "se pone",
        back: "it gets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IlzwDnfDw7",
      },
      {
        front: "semanas",
        back: "weeks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VEIwTqn6SM",
      },
      {
        front: "solo",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JJaJvkv3jF",
      },
      {
        front: "tarde",
        back: "afternoon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KMMt89fzRF",
      },
      {
        front: "tarea",
        back: "task",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bT8rzMkjjx",
      },
      {
        front: "tareas",
        back: "chores",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iHP0KRTlid",
      },
      {
        front: "te pones",
        back: "you put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h4FEB9yxsK",
      },
      {
        front: "temprano",
        back: "early",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vosyRebbFr",
      },
      {
        front: "toman",
        back: "they take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "weDNfOkf4S",
      },
      {
        front: "tomo",
        back: "I take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PkUxZXaUrG",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "U5fLeyu70u",
    title: "Unit 28",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "almorzamos",
        back: "we have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "45uYqycixK",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzar",
        back: "to have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "82axIfXiFb",
      },
      {
        front: "almuerzan",
        back: "they have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Eq7YFOr2MZ",
      },
      {
        front: "almuerzas",
        back: "you have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cDqSHgMWCm",
      },
      {
        front: "almuerza",
        back: "he/she/it has lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mZGojp5hjJ",
      },
      {
        front: "poder",
        back: "to be able",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BioeSVWvvZ",
      },
      {
        front: "podemos",
        back: "we can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eBs4U58cQs",
      },
      {
        front: "puedo",
        back: "I can (can I)",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MuE20Mn4k6",
      },
      {
        front: "puede",
        back: "he/she/it can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fc9Zkb091q",
      },
      {
        front: "pueden",
        back: "they can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MI3zKSgphM",
      },
      {
        front: "probamos",
        back: "we try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LvsvqvHBHI",
      },
      {
        front: "probar",
        back: "to try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AV5NSL21A0",
      },
      {
        front: "prueba",
        back: "he/she/it tries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XARlgND7C9",
      },
      {
        front: "prueban",
        back: "they try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K58Zc6UtF6",
      },
      {
        front: "pruebo",
        back: "I try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uLwbI1nqrn",
      },
      {
        front: "pierdo",
        back: "I lose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w84ch5n2Xm",
      },
      {
        front: "pierdes",
        back: "you lose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0nP3kAeThp",
      },
      {
        front: "pierde",
        back: "he/she/it loses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zaPQPcctni",
      },
      {
        front: "perdemos",
        back: "we lose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "utOzgmlTkQ",
      },
      {
        front: "pierden",
        back: "they lose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lon6kMnTWd",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "l1QDO2Ys0y",
    title: "Unit 29",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abril",
        back: "April",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1QfvWyXaWZ",
      },
      {
        front: "agosto",
        back: "August",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5FQjiIEwht",
      },
      {
        front: "buen tiempo",
        back: "good weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vmyfglgqyb",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo está el tiempo",
        back: "how's the weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q4lS6qxJ5r",
      },
      {
        front: "diciembre",
        back: "December",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sLTat0ySoN",
      },
      {
        front: "enero",
        back: "January",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9H2DlipbV9",
      },
      {
        front: "febrero",
        back: "february",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bafLTuTp20",
      },
      {
        front: "hace calor",
        back: "is hot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RVFDSGEhYJ",
      },
      {
        front: "hace frío",
        back: "it's cold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pOtbCUfV98",
      },
      {
        front: "invierno",
        back: "winter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UR9pmbSNz9",
      },
      {
        front: "inviernos",
        back: "winters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wf6QkSkAhS",
      },
      {
        front: "julio",
        back: "July",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IAeqCpkWRq",
      },
      {
        front: "junio",
        back: "june",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VoRrxxkumR",
      },
      {
        front: "llueve",
        back: "Rains",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Txt60UYmCl",
      },
      {
        front: "mal tiempo",
        back: "bad weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lCU2ANRdRj",
      },
      {
        front: "marzo",
        back: "march",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v1QWB4hVld",
      },
      {
        front: "mayo",
        back: "May",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zhTGQfrG5a",
      },
      {
        front: "mes",
        back: "month",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VpUuh5Jjgk",
      },
      {
        front: "meses",
        back: "months",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EfpwWjqfgQ",
      },
      {
        front: "nieva",
        back: "snows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WzvqAXThfG",
      },
      {
        front: "noviembre",
        back: "november",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c4SgLJbjVT",
      },
      {
        front: "nublado",
        back: "cloudy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LdIMEeMnsC",
      },
      {
        front: "octubre",
        back: "October",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TB5d2cokuf",
      },
      {
        front: "oscuro",
        back: "Dark",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0CJtJF8bzD",
      },
      {
        front: "oscuros",
        back: "dark",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H7T1mv52kL",
      },
      {
        front: "otoños",
        back: "autumns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5v4v3LZJZn",
      },
      {
        front: "primavera",
        back: "spring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S7KTnBYB8Z",
      },
      {
        front: "primaveras",
        back: "springs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pw3iK0NIG5",
      },
      {
        front: "qué tiempo hace",
        back: "How is the weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DTtIr9zWST",
      },
      {
        front: "septiembre",
        back: "september",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AQlRgjEpUh",
      },
      {
        front: "sol",
        back: "sun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwY8ABVqzS",
      },
      {
        front: "viento",
        back: "wind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eYb5k4mNrU",
      },
      {
        front: "vientos",
        back: "winds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yKyhsJ25xv",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "WwsMXFNqDh",
    title: "Unit 30",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "canciones",
        back: "songs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2xGTcG1AG3",
      },
      {
        front: "canción",
        back: "song",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N2NgyyNNVe",
      },
      {
        front: "canta",
        back: "sings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yWovI9EkBJ",
      },
      {
        front: "cantamos",
        back: "we sang",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l30m6wrn6Z",
      },
      {
        front: "cantan",
        back: "they sing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SWL7Fiic46",
      },
      {
        front: "cantar",
        back: "sing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QhisOmkNAG",
      },
      {
        front: "cantas",
        back: "do you sing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ToV3ER8PVM",
      },
      {
        front: "canto",
        back: "singing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t2rWTbCJWS",
      },
      {
        front: "carnes",
        back: "meats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eLGvk7YFlv",
      },
      {
        front: "china",
        back: "China",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cLdFGBdZHP",
      },
      {
        front: "chino",
        back: "Chinese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0SeWckH0BL",
      },
      {
        front: "cocina",
        back: "kitchen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NAz5yHydxr",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinamos",
        back: "we cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qubHudT3cH",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinan",
        back: "they cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QrAMK3YkzL",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinar",
        back: "cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lAkFldpxcL",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinas",
        back: "kitchens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A1G5K3e1SM",
      },
      {
        front: "cocino",
        back: "I cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cKrHMXcrJS",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo se dice",
        back: "How do you say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S4n8grYM80",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo se",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4PgsP58qGu",
      },
      {
        front: "escribe",
        back: "how is this written",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I5hlZqjcW9",
      },
      {
        front: "edad",
        back: "age",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nItTQ9lQfl",
      },
      {
        front: "lengua",
        back: "language",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ejZVulvPhh",
      },
      {
        front: "lenguas",
        back: "languages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SZ9Nou5i3x",
      },
      {
        front: "maneja",
        back: "drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dPLAyCGGSe",
      },
      {
        front: "manejamos",
        back: "we drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BPKZfLd2qJ",
      },
      {
        front: "manejan",
        back: "drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bWaSLt3eUO",
      },
      {
        front: "manejar",
        back: "handle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jGdaJdmw8D",
      },
      {
        front: "manejas",
        back: "do you drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FrmP9ntO90",
      },
      {
        front: "manejo",
        back: "driving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5x7FVM9xZW",
      },
      {
        front: "misma",
        back: "same",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UhIa4VOXyo",
      },
      {
        front: "mismas",
        back: "same",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DK48heub1B",
      },
      {
        front: "mismo",
        back: "same",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UswEDHUxJb",
      },
      {
        front: "mismos",
        back: "themselves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jXnN2nocge",
      },
      {
        front: "nada",
        back: "any",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fNX1xXgwEF",
      },
      {
        front: "nadan",
        back: "they swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BaxhNGiwLk",
      },
      {
        front: "nadas",
        back: "you swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lRprOGCnfd",
      },
      {
        front: "nado",
        back: "I swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p27iWQcBc0",
      },
      {
        front: "no lo sé",
        back: "I do not know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qwtkULSrfR",
      },
      {
        front: "palabra",
        back: "word",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "824GDoKmMy",
      },
      {
        front: "palabras",
        back: "words",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4RBbvDXE8A",
      },
      {
        front: "respuesta",
        back: "reply",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nd5NK2N4tu",
      },
      {
        front: "respuestas",
        back: "answers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BiDxk8zhM1",
      },
      {
        front: "sabe",
        back: "knows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PPATJzwnmL",
      },
      {
        front: "sabe usted",
        back: "do you know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J1LwXVaNSa",
      },
      {
        front: "sabemos",
        back: "we know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GwSOczTHk2",
      },
      {
        front: "sabemos dónde",
        back: "we know where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DJdEaiCMdX",
      },
      {
        front: "saben",
        back: "they know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EfoJngQUid",
      },
      {
        front: "saber",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jo8TpBl3N0",
      },
      {
        front: "sabes",
        back: "do you know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gipmOzMGD0",
      },
      {
        front: "sabes cuándo",
        back: "you know when",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tWEcuQognO",
      },
      {
        front: "sabes nadar",
        back: "you know how to swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R7YW7l2T4r",
      },
      {
        front: "sabes quién",
        back: "do you know who",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eGMJAY4le9",
      },
      {
        front: "sé",
        back: "HE",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WHB6qAngqE",
      },
      {
        front: "sé cuándo",
        back: "I know when",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2nHBOtHvyx",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "yyAdopbLsC",
    title: "Unit 30",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "arte",
        back: "art",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gVVWUdjzdc",
      },
      {
        front: "artes",
        back: "Arts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HT8Eikb0gf",
      },
      {
        front: "asignatura",
        back: "course",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GyGyDuvxGi",
      },
      {
        front: "asignaturas",
        back: "subjects",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HAuFOKHiuT",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaciones",
        back: "conversations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yhfd4ugWSV",
      },
      {
        front: "conversación",
        back: "conversation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j22FDWLP8z",
      },
      {
        front: "cuáles",
        back: "which",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xd0ZO6ijBb",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujamos",
        back: "we draw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ikjD4nwOiH",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujan",
        back: "they draw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xN6Zp8ctr7",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujas",
        back: "you draw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4AfHyyzKvY",
      },
      {
        front: "esto",
        back: "this",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rmYICZeO3N",
      },
      {
        front: "europea",
        back: "european",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9aOkCZM2z4",
      },
      {
        front: "europeas",
        back: "European",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zrJhTl5GMW",
      },
      {
        front: "europeo",
        back: "European",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NRwS50bl9e",
      },
      {
        front: "europeos",
        back: "europeans",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NwuZRTWfgc",
      },
      {
        front: "fiestas",
        back: "parties",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bnVPZWv2sg",
      },
      {
        front: "foto",
        back: "Photo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EWMts8YlBH",
      },
      {
        front: "fotos",
        back: "Photos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fiF2vqe5Xl",
      },
      {
        front: "grupo",
        back: "cluster",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uhAtgo6ic6",
      },
      {
        front: "importantes",
        back: "important",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qJ7ktXFNrz",
      },
      {
        front: "interesa jugar",
        back: "interested in playing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p4Guca5RBo",
      },
      {
        front: "juega",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YbEhOX6O2H",
      },
      {
        front: "juegan",
        back: "they play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qUUQ15fAjF",
      },
      {
        front: "juegas",
        back: "you play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AYRECu0WMd",
      },
      {
        front: "juego",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L60czDoQU6",
      },
      {
        front: "jugamos",
        back: "let's play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ET1CWSG1Wd",
      },
      {
        front: "le interesa",
        back: "you are interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8NmfBMhGYp",
      },
      {
        front: "les interesa",
        back: "they are interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e9q665dBUG",
      },
      {
        front: "me interesa",
        back: "I'm interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6irpNp81Xw",
      },
      {
        front: "museo",
        back: "museum",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KPViWPoOIH",
      },
      {
        front: "museos",
        back: "museums",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wVFEJZk10x",
      },
      {
        front: "nos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U0fDZWGY4Z",
      },
      {
        front: "interesa",
        back: "we are interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BfPpzAJPS5",
      },
      {
        front: "otras",
        back: "others",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ln40MDopsM",
      },
      {
        front: "otros",
        back: "others",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GwFTraydgW",
      },
      {
        front: "partidos",
        back: "matches",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mN6jykBRQT",
      },
      {
        front: "pintura",
        back: "paint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ycLhbL88Zi",
      },
      {
        front: "pinturas",
        back: "paintings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FXdxtGWvo5",
      },
      {
        front: "practicar",
        back: "to practice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eM9Szk2mXy",
      },
      {
        front: "preferida",
        back: "preferred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9pb4t57u9h",
      },
      {
        front: "preferido",
        back: "favorite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JrZDz3iVDX",
      },
      {
        front: "radio",
        back: "radio",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Ad8qZs23l",
      },
      {
        front: "te",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UZDWVoBOpV",
      },
      {
        front: "interesa",
        back: "are you interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f9LtTLbRHO",
      },
      {
        front: "viajas",
        back: "you travel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bixs6Zb8O4",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "bdTeh83yPQ",
    title: "Unit 31",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adónde",
        back: "where to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iSiPGglbsY",
      },
      {
        front: "aviones",
        back: "planes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9gvdnsqYaE",
      },
      {
        front: "avión",
        back: "plane",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k0doOOQD8k",
      },
      {
        front: "boletos",
        back: "tickets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PClGJiDAwM",
      },
      {
        front: "carros",
        back: "cars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NQqHdY81pa",
      },
      {
        front: "cuarto",
        back: "quarter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hyv1caBmVV",
      },
      {
        front: "cámara",
        back: "camera",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t7KCmXeuIv",
      },
      {
        front: "cámaras",
        back: "cameras",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NnNu2D96H3",
      },
      {
        front: "estar",
        back: "to be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JfB9CW4VqC",
      },
      {
        front: "llega",
        back: "arrives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vsj58JzQZB",
      },
      {
        front: "llegamos",
        back: "we arrived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s6MvjXa26a",
      },
      {
        front: "llegan",
        back: "arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TruZJSYoMq",
      },
      {
        front: "llegar",
        back: "arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JhuiyUWl4t",
      },
      {
        front: "llegas",
        back: "you arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jp96b8oUm2",
      },
      {
        front: "llego",
        back: "arrived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9ZN7Ko1Nhw",
      },
      {
        front: "maletas",
        back: "suitcases",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R1gwgArHac",
      },
      {
        front: "menos",
        back: "less",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nvNq6AcwtE",
      },
      {
        front: "minuto",
        back: "minute",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KA134Ag9wI",
      },
      {
        front: "minutos",
        back: "minutes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eIt3BTzdBj",
      },
      {
        front: "pasaportes",
        back: "passports",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z7lBPCyYQn",
      },
      {
        front: "por",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7Ahj0vXLN9",
      },
      {
        front: "pronto",
        back: "early",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pQBh8RO7Qr",
      },
      {
        front: "próxima",
        back: "next",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YqFD9xMa13",
      },
      {
        front: "próximas",
        back: "forthcoming",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fNmM7xWnk2",
      },
      {
        front: "próximo",
        back: "next",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5aO9X2jOq0",
      },
      {
        front: "taxis",
        back: "taxi",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FadX2W8Xr6",
      },
      {
        front: "treinta",
        back: "thirty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bzfMvKMKbb",
      },
      {
        front: "va a",
        back: "will",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aNbZbqaNCT",
      },
      {
        front: "vamos a",
        back: "we are going to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4TiPUrMY6W",
      },
      {
        front: "van a",
        back: "going to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S8EywpvXlg",
      },
      {
        front: "vas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "61RHqGeUZx",
      },
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "you'll",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "63WOCSSkrc",
      },
      {
        front: "veintinueve",
        back: "twenty nine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eRPEXhr4gI",
      },
      {
        front: "veintiocho",
        back: "twenty eight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WzzcmQPk64",
      },
      {
        front: "veintisiete",
        back: "twenty seven",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WxiQfvPw9Q",
      },
      {
        front: "veintiséis",
        back: "twenty six",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VAtJizl1X9",
      },
      {
        front: "voy a",
        back: "I will",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kdJ3ucfE5Z",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ejHtlxXhL1",
    title: "Unit 32",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ambas",
        back: "both",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K1WbEIiKP3",
      },
      {
        front: "ambos",
        back: "both of them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iIN4PBNinX",
      },
      {
        front: "bailes",
        back: "dances",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "paaNytLIjm",
      },
      {
        front: "bananas",
        back: "bananas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lxyXmRl600",
      },
      {
        front: "bota",
        back: "boot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6EqZvGv783",
      },
      {
        front: "botas",
        back: "boots",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "khtbnFiRb9",
      },
      {
        front: "calientes",
        back: "hot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z0MyS2I9Pb",
      },
      {
        front: "chilena",
        back: "Chilean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GuuHeUEY9q",
      },
      {
        front: "chileno",
        back: "Chilean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YIzG7aYpaN",
      },
      {
        front: "chilenos",
        back: "Chileans",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sqF9i391Di",
      },
      {
        front: "color",
        back: "color",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YDrFNEa8VW",
      },
      {
        front: "colores",
        back: "colors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CLXsQp26ED",
      },
      {
        front: "cubanas",
        back: "Cuban",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kM2GjTPNW5",
      },
      {
        front: "cubano",
        back: "Cuban",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iDIqpdk7vo",
      },
      {
        front: "cubanos",
        back: "cubans",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4uqAubS0tF",
      },
      {
        front: "dulce",
        back: "sweet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dBkOskrxVx",
      },
      {
        front: "dulces",
        back: "sweets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XrJDhXCn6n",
      },
      {
        front: "encantan",
        back: "they love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IQZbCcIBAo",
      },
      {
        front: "ensaladas",
        back: "salads",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gwuxb0tgqm",
      },
      {
        front: "flor",
        back: "flower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KJSbCx8a7a",
      },
      {
        front: "flores",
        back: "flowers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JabFp4YVC7",
      },
      {
        front: "francesa",
        back: "French",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BxewFUFv8H",
      },
      {
        front: "franceses",
        back: "French",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8yoywScMYK",
      },
      {
        front: "gustan",
        back: "like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7Scn8YQc3w",
      },
      {
        front: "interesan",
        back: "interest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nqxGjx75nh",
      },
      {
        front: "italianas",
        back: "Italian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jGwOfBx7Vc",
      },
      {
        front: "italiano",
        back: "Italian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SLIZ7NduzG",
      },
      {
        front: "juego",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QIz7CB0ra3",
      },
      {
        front: "juegos",
        back: "games",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ioVVl0MVlZ",
      },
      {
        front: "latina",
        back: "latin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "32leqpO5ZA",
      },
      {
        front: "latinas",
        back: "latinas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "69khXNE3Qy",
      },
      {
        front: "latinos",
        back: "latinos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "85VIeIsvnW",
      },
      {
        front: "lentes",
        back: "lenses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d3c6yTI9XB",
      },
      {
        front: "naranja",
        back: "orange",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hpW8lBo8aL",
      },
      {
        front: "naranjas",
        back: "oranges",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "btQrlPjVhE",
      },
      {
        front: "ojo",
        back: "eye",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JZQ4oDq35s",
      },
      {
        front: "ojos",
        back: "eyes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tH4MzgPxKF",
      },
      {
        front: "par",
        back: "pair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8bPg7azuga",
      },
      {
        front: "pares",
        back: "peers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fIuhzvBfYC",
      },
      {
        front: "pájaro",
        back: "bird",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mYnCdWdvEb",
      },
      {
        front: "pájaros",
        back: "birds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x9lcimP5YM",
      },
      {
        front: "rápida",
        back: "quick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bDps1pa9IF",
      },
      {
        front: "rápidas",
        back: "fast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f03jIeDS76",
      },
      {
        front: "rápido",
        back: "Quick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NnwDHH9GjP",
      },
      {
        front: "rápidos",
        back: "rapid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fMtV487QSK",
      },
      {
        front: "sitio",
        back: "place",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "djJLTiJ2WL",
      },
      {
        front: "sitios",
        back: "sites",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PAZuonxZBi",
      },
      {
        front: "vaqueros",
        back: "Cowboys",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lMDKlBncNJ",
      },
      {
        front: "vinos",
        back: "wines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qGGVO7jGMG",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "misnFKvnmZ",
    title: "Unit 32",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bajas",
        back: "low",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IvUVfog6wf",
      },
      {
        front: "bajos",
        back: "low",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B1AtmDDX3z",
      },
      {
        front: "bello",
        back: "beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jds3nFmzxK",
      },
      {
        front: "blusa",
        back: "blouse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VX1qkEoFRa",
      },
      {
        front: "chaqueta",
        back: "jacket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hFxYNyivdr",
      },
      {
        front: "chaquetas",
        back: "jackets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wlUZjT8jg8",
      },
      {
        front: "como",
        back: "What",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VacUYGSEaS",
      },
      {
        front: "cómodas",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x9dEkU6P5g",
      },
      {
        front: "cómodo",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rWfPFWNAoQ",
      },
      {
        front: "delgada",
        back: "thin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IouDSekkmP",
      },
      {
        front: "delgados",
        back: "thin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jY8965Jltx",
      },
      {
        front: "el mejor",
        back: "the best",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2JpIrqkezI",
      },
      {
        front: "el más",
        back: "the more",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mev7othgnK",
      },
      {
        front: "el peor",
        back: "worst",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sDh1OH6gmW",
      },
      {
        front: "es tan",
        back: "are",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4DcOIDAYco",
      },
      {
        front: "famosa",
        back: "famous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3m7rkF3NoL",
      },
      {
        front: "famosas",
        back: "famous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "alC02kNJmz",
      },
      {
        front: "famoso",
        back: "famous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yMn2SNGKPx",
      },
      {
        front: "gorra",
        back: "Cap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w0oxYfrH8A",
      },
      {
        front: "la más",
        back: "the most",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XoCPdCgA4i",
      },
      {
        front: "mejores",
        back: "top",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Almfq4XeTP",
      },
      {
        front: "menos",
        back: "less",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TqQAIcikB9",
      },
      {
        front: "mundo",
        back: "world",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wFSGfNrgdP",
      },
      {
        front: "mundos",
        back: "worlds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rjQ0vyqNJG",
      },
      {
        front: "más",
        back: "plus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "biEtzAlbgI",
      },
      {
        front: "peores",
        back: "worse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UFYwzEyOZY",
      },
      {
        front: "popular",
        back: "popular",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iVEGSUPE4r",
      },
      {
        front: "populares",
        back: "popular",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VJye51op5f",
      },
      {
        front: "que",
        back: "what",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nkHNUlblu9",
      },
      {
        front: "qué divertido",
        back: "What fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oGXyx7pYM6",
      },
      {
        front: "qué elegante",
        back: "how elegant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4ojOISlOzk",
      },
      {
        front: "qué interesante",
        back: "interesting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zoIX0HxQuR",
      },
      {
        front: "tan",
        back: "so",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VmMtL1HpKx",
      },
      {
        front: "tan bonita",
        back: "so pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3eQNhnLQ8r",
      },
      {
        front: "tan bonito",
        back: "so pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4NWEz970Dw",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "a0ydMdtO9O",
    title: "Unit 33",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abre",
        back: "opens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yXrvechNWG",
      },
      {
        front: "abres",
        back: "you open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "naHgPZuDEx",
      },
      {
        front: "alto",
        back: "high or tall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rzi3uMuyiq",
      },
      {
        front: "beba",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YKtoB58VLe",
      },
      {
        front: "cierra",
        back: "close",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DpVvQqLwQv",
      },
      {
        front: "cierras la",
        back: "you close the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uK70jFa6tW",
      },
      {
        front: "despacio",
        back: "slowly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4BgafLXCml",
      },
      {
        front: "escriba",
        back: "scribe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gThqALkA08",
      },
      {
        front: "estudia",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DOFNujV6ko",
      },
      {
        front: "estudias en",
        back: "you study in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bvZZNkZvFp",
      },
      {
        front: "habla",
        back: "speaks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hWRsh2kdYO",
      },
      {
        front: "hablas con",
        back: "you speak with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pSpPbjBF0r",
      },
      {
        front: "hable",
        back: "I talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ROkJunlaWu",
      },
      {
        front: "lee",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "say1V34PQW",
      },
      {
        front: "pruebe",
        back: "try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qEa71sFxX2",
      },
      {
        front: "página",
        back: "page",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "adx41uNYVq",
      },
      {
        front: "páginas",
        back: "pages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FjzMuZkZ2e",
      },
      {
        front: "trabaje",
        back: "work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AIqYHn6yh4",
      },
      {
        front: "tú lees",
        back: "you read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XDsgOpTDec",
      },
      {
        front: "tú vuelves",
        back: "you return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zjUsSlEfMz",
      },
      {
        front: "usted bebe",
        back: "you drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uMLyDya7h4",
      },
      {
        front: "usted escribe",
        back: "you write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BfwkpnmDFJ",
      },
      {
        front: "usted habla",
        back: "you speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xBKVJwGLwy",
      },
      {
        front: "usted prueba",
        back: "you test",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Abhn3do8o",
      },
      {
        front: "usted trabaja",
        back: "you work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yqEOqlsmVq",
      },
      {
        front: "usted vuelve",
        back: "you come back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yFuxHYQhXy",
      },
      {
        front: "vuelva",
        back: "come back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GmhkLWrxb5",
      },
      {
        front: "vuelve",
        back: "returns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SPjdoG9V5N",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ZalEdcZBkG",
    title: "Unit 34",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "tolike1",
        back: "tolike1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZQB05I8be6",
      },
      {
        front: "tolike2",
        back: "tolike2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wc7RaoNHhP",
      },
      {
        front: "tolike3",
        back: "tolike3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XhD11e7lmq",
      },
      {
        front: "tolike",
        back: "tolike",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W7xbNY2jxu",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "b3uvyr1Nyp",
    title: "Unit 34",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bolsa",
        back: "bag",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bGpChjN4BD",
      },
      {
        front: "bolsas",
        back: "bags",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lJadIfd205",
      },
      {
        front: "centavos",
        back: "cents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iFsJxq5dyy",
      },
      {
        front: "chorizo",
        back: "chorizo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tkBklsNmdv",
      },
      {
        front: "chorizos",
        back: "sausages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BSA4JYCl9Q",
      },
      {
        front: "cincuenta",
        back: "fifty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qNuuIdIUnY",
      },
      {
        front: "compra",
        back: "purchase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xaFVaBXDT0",
      },
      {
        front: "cuarenta",
        back: "Fourty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OEGeUfffTA",
      },
      {
        front: "cuánta",
        back: "how much",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RvAP8eWDs2",
      },
      {
        front: "fruta",
        back: "fruit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fYtP8105dv",
      },
      {
        front: "frutas",
        back: "fruit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "febnEnDtxv",
      },
      {
        front: "huevo",
        back: "egg",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tYZyWGlh0Q",
      },
      {
        front: "kilo",
        back: "kilo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C9eBhbIDYQ",
      },
      {
        front: "lavamos",
        back: "we wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yjBClQvzZ5",
      },
      {
        front: "lavan",
        back: "wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GCQ869gSQK",
      },
      {
        front: "lavar",
        back: "wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VMfqvdxEUK",
      },
      {
        front: "lavas",
        back: "you wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x5JVbgPAGz",
      },
      {
        front: "lleva",
        back: "carries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yobgB7y3tz",
      },
      {
        front: "llevamos",
        back: "we carry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P40eHCOhgd",
      },
      {
        front: "llevan",
        back: "They carry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZWwRuTMlhS",
      },
      {
        front: "llevar",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iIrSoziXMX",
      },
      {
        front: "llevas",
        back: "you carry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8p4z4zHGp",
      },
      {
        front: "llevo",
        back: "he took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8wqvSAGVsJ",
      },
      {
        front: "mantequilla",
        back: "Butter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Rs97mxBAZ",
      },
      {
        front: "naranja",
        back: "orange",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "prCtC5pcS1",
      },
      {
        front: "papa",
        back: "dad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OoJN7L1d9E",
      },
      {
        front: "picante",
        back: "spicy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WgI42AkHOr",
      },
      {
        front: "picantes",
        back: "spicy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7WjuX98DPI",
      },
      {
        front: "plátano",
        back: "banana",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "STIZSWZPue",
      },
      {
        front: "plátanos",
        back: "bananas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zEX6kEmXF1",
      },
      {
        front: "pone",
        back: "places",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jLZbYpMtKB",
      },
      {
        front: "ponemos",
        back: "we put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7RZzQnV7if",
      },
      {
        front: "ponen",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pB0dQO5YxZ",
      },
      {
        front: "poner",
        back: "place",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o3ymMrvOIL",
      },
      {
        front: "pones",
        back: "you put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j55CrFch82",
      },
      {
        front: "pongo",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1QiEukoxdp",
      },
      {
        front: "refrigerador",
        back: "refrigerator",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nu5Qb6C5uc",
      },
      {
        front: "refrigeradores",
        back: "refrigerators",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TwbXjWIU6M",
      },
      {
        front: "sesenta",
        back: "sixty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mUcj5ZRb7P",
      },
      {
        front: "tenemos que",
        back: "we have to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HdyYbI2uB0",
      },
      {
        front: "tienen que",
        back: "they have to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J84WTeppq6",
      },
      {
        front: "tomate",
        back: "tomatoes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TBQwlbZ8ZU",
      },
      {
        front: "vegetal",
        back: "vegetable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AKXqaiEGhG",
      },
      {
        front: "vegetales",
        back: "vegetables",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LvpPw9uN0r",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "4IPtqiTvsE",
    title: "Unit 35",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abriendo",
        back: "opening",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tGf5UdQqcB",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendiendo",
        back: "learning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7jf2ZlZ8uO",
      },
      {
        front: "aula",
        back: "classroom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KaXY6H6UC5",
      },
      {
        front: "bebiendo",
        back: "drinking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WSSoEsiX2o",
      },
      {
        front: "comiendo",
        back: "eating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eDLYxIoUx5",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujando",
        back: "drawing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mhUJ6fEnhN",
      },
      {
        front: "escribiendo",
        back: "writing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kzycXfptvI",
      },
      {
        front: "escuchando",
        back: "listening",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oHjWPNrLpt",
      },
      {
        front: "escuelas",
        back: "schools",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pWdDpzZftN",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiando",
        back: "studying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rvOJzm5mRp",
      },
      {
        front: "hablando",
        back: "speaking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "35J7AXpjQk",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar con",
        back: "talk to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PbHLhY4YGV",
      },
      {
        front: "haciendo",
        back: "making",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6rT7I8hVia",
      },
      {
        front: "lección",
        back: "lesson",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jEqKQm00ns",
      },
      {
        front: "leyendo",
        back: "reading",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZuhjH8zfUw",
      },
      {
        front: "nota",
        back: "note",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LWZosdfLCJ",
      },
      {
        front: "notas",
        back: "notes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YDvz93cnf8",
      },
      {
        front: "pizarra",
        back: "board",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6rdTIvJpGP",
      },
      {
        front: "pizarras",
        back: "blackboards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VybzsRRM6s",
      },
      {
        front: "que escribir",
        back: "what to write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2swSgaKgfh",
      },
      {
        front: "que estudiar",
        back: "what to study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ayF8BxAjbI",
      },
      {
        front: "que hacer",
        back: "to do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tiPke8TeaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "que leer",
        back: "what to read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FojQWqbYFO",
      },
      {
        front: "queremos abrir",
        back: "we want to open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ZYnXWXN29",
      },
      {
        front: "quiere dibujar",
        back: "wants to draw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iLmYjuurLI",
      },
      {
        front: "quieren beber",
        back: "they want to drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sPDtN6PHGH",
      },
      {
        front: "quiero",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M3xIh6XZd2",
      },
      {
        front: "aprender",
        back: "I want to learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "muVV59p12j",
      },
      {
        front: "saliendo",
        back: "coming out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "py9cDMF17w",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "rZMzQ4rDxp",
    title: "Unit 36",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abro",
        back: "I open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9HXGrkhJmp",
      },
      {
        front: "bebemos",
        back: "we drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L5pVdOUeTa",
      },
      {
        front: "bici",
        back: "bike",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VRayyBNuuW",
      },
      {
        front: "cafés",
        back: "cafes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a2E3laMmpF",
      },
      {
        front: "cierro",
        back: "I close",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i3AQiwmkjP",
      },
      {
        front: "gatos",
        back: "cats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PySszTRXoz",
      },
      {
        front: "imagen",
        back: "picture",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uhkCTt6XH6",
      },
      {
        front: "imágenes",
        back: "images",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "myE273iTRP",
      },
      {
        front: "la",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mwKsRoCVWh",
      },
      {
        front: "la quiero",
        back: "I love her",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f4o0JXV400",
      },
      {
        front: "las",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6Ry9k39E3O",
      },
      {
        front: "las comen",
        back: "eat them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D3Gv3Bvz9f",
      },
      {
        front: "las necesita",
        back: "need them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1iVqgtss4B",
      },
      {
        front: "ligeras",
        back: "light",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iyhfPrwUSK",
      },
      {
        front: "lo",
        back: "it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nMF1F69iMM",
      },
      {
        front: "lo compro",
        back: "I buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yVi04fBO5u",
      },
      {
        front: "lo quiero",
        back: "I love you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MbX5t8fUV4",
      },
      {
        front: "los",
        back: "the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fPu1QV4ekz",
      },
      {
        front: "los comen",
        back: "eat them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b38gIlRBJ0",
      },
      {
        front: "los necesita",
        back: "need them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QKB9pCReOG",
      },
      {
        front: "mala",
        back: "bad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LRLzWU4tIk",
      },
      {
        front: "malo",
        back: "evil",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PkW04VkCMX",
      },
      {
        front: "malos",
        back: "bad",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bj2BtnNMJP",
      },
      {
        front: "paquete",
        back: "package",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bSsY5wofOA",
      },
      {
        front: "paquetes",
        back: "packages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UTNhOOFPAq",
      },
      {
        front: "pruebas",
        back: "tests",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H8zt4tg49g",
      },
      {
        front: "salsa",
        back: "sauce",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kGexe8u8W4",
      },
      {
        front: "todas",
        back: "all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hsCMDgq9JO",
      },
      {
        front: "todo el tiempo",
        back: "all the time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b6QjkSAn9E",
      },
      {
        front: "todos",
        back: "everyone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YntRgT7y3g",
      },
      {
        front: "tés",
        back: "teas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hDtisXGepm",
      },
      {
        front: "ya",
        back: "Already",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2eOGaHoYLz",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "qLmDRhsAFP",
    title: "Unit 36",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cara",
        back: "expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y1XIEV1kv4",
      },
      {
        front: "caras",
        back: "faces",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CydeSeLHT3",
      },
      {
        front: "cepillarse",
        back: "brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fejHTiK3uO",
      },
      {
        front: "cepillo",
        back: "brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cO4QKUPhap",
      },
      {
        front: "cepillo de dientes",
        back: "toothbrush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c9fWIdVWzV",
      },
      {
        front: "cepillos",
        back: "brushes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P24JDPfVgg",
      },
      {
        front: "diente",
        back: "tooth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kyIOGvLX2N",
      },
      {
        front: "dientes",
        back: "teeth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wGIKftpy8z",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarse",
        back: "wash up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2siuzskuJA",
      },
      {
        front: "llave",
        back: "key",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pnIWa48FLV",
      },
      {
        front: "llaves",
        back: "keys",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NMv2Cu6lo6",
      },
      {
        front: "mano",
        back: "hand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4qWjUJ7CxK",
      },
      {
        front: "manos",
        back: "hands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sub7PYvf1h",
      },
      {
        front: "me cepillo",
        back: "I brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0NYFx1j9Xk",
      },
      {
        front: "me lavo",
        back: "I wash myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P42XnPSl2U",
      },
      {
        front: "mía",
        back: "mine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7AjNtEbGup",
      },
      {
        front: "mío",
        back: "Own",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yk9xLh2CEG",
      },
      {
        front: "nos cepillamos",
        back: "we brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oc9cUlbes5",
      },
      {
        front: "nos duchamos",
        back: "we showered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OL4CW73Zyq",
      },
      {
        front: "nos lavamos",
        back: "we wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DEXUdC4keI",
      },
      {
        front: "nos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cSeMSuUhSq",
      },
      {
        front: "levantamos",
        back: "we got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BY3dULLc2D",
      },
      {
        front: "nos llamamos",
        back: "We call each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3pcfR3LTkk",
      },
      {
        front: "nos ponemos",
        back: "we get",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XGAuigtjUr",
      },
      {
        front: "nos sentimos",
        back: "we feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "THnQFkmOHT",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestra",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1uoA1Z91nC",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestras",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7yknUvxqs9",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestro",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NiwtpYvsN1",
      },
      {
        front: "nuestros",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K5BeHYqafs",
      },
      {
        front: "se cepilla",
        back: "he brushes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4oAD97qQKV",
      },
      {
        front: "se cepillan",
        back: "they brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mGzGXcnmqb",
      },
      {
        front: "se duchan",
        back: "they take a shower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NcEVU5xvCT",
      },
      {
        front: "se lava",
        back: "Wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ftnnQBPT6h",
      },
      {
        front: "se lavan",
        back: "Washing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cj6kALQw5c",
      },
      {
        front: "se levantan",
        back: "they get up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RLottZSj4c",
      },
      {
        front: "se ponen",
        back: "are placed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L9RsYqnIw2",
      },
      {
        front: "se sienten",
        back: "they feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sAxraS9gPb",
      },
      {
        front: "suyas",
        back: "his",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cXAHayV29V",
      },
      {
        front: "suyo",
        back: "yours",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IlOgqq8sZx",
      },
      {
        front: "te cepillas",
        back: "you brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2fLHrMAKF6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "eNkIRvtAif",
    title: "Unit 36",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cambiamos",
        back: "we changed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8ot22SWY3x",
      },
      {
        front: "cambiando",
        back: "Changing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "581eQ1RMsq",
      },
      {
        front: "cambiar",
        back: "change",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NjUy5pfGiz",
      },
      {
        front: "decir",
        back: "say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vdrLvqIV0P",
      },
      {
        front: "empiezas",
        back: "you start",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YpQhrN1DPK",
      },
      {
        front: "fecha",
        back: "date",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7SvWsptE7A",
      },
      {
        front: "fechas",
        back: "dates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7P78q1bpiX",
      },
      {
        front: "gustar",
        back: "like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q0M2m5WAyr",
      },
      {
        front: "gustaría",
        back: "would like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SMGdh1su0g",
      },
      {
        front: "invitan",
        back: "invite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l3e8Ydx29I",
      },
      {
        front: "invitar",
        back: "invite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nHb7uXp4ML",
      },
      {
        front: "invitas",
        back: "you invite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0ho63vqZqz",
      },
      {
        front: "invito",
        back: "invite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4UOlLxx0vR",
      },
      {
        front: "luego",
        back: "later",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "prWWsbuyUa",
      },
      {
        front: "me quedo",
        back: "I stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7tyTM9t8uW",
      },
      {
        front: "nos quedamos",
        back: "we stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UKInWAaugD",
      },
      {
        front: "pensamos",
        back: "we think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XJPJ10p7dR",
      },
      {
        front: "pensando",
        back: "thinking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sDSc3RKH5x",
      },
      {
        front: "pensar",
        back: "to think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZgwmyDuZzt",
      },
      {
        front: "piensa",
        back: "think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7KNx1TdEpR",
      },
      {
        front: "pienso",
        back: "I think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0UIGSTVLuN",
      },
      {
        front: "plan",
        back: "plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kuEsycQrNI",
      },
      {
        front: "planes",
        back: "plans",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J2qsvpDj53",
      },
      {
        front: "por supuesto",
        back: "of course",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8eQNrzz6kR",
      },
      {
        front: "primero",
        back: "First",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T56omCf2S9",
      },
      {
        front: "puedes",
        back: "you may",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DykovkzoRx",
      },
      {
        front: "que viene",
        back: "coming",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XFQdpnAPvS",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarse",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xStotCCZxD",
      },
      {
        front: "se queda",
        back: "stays",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d3kr678LGf",
      },
      {
        front: "se quedan",
        back: "they stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0DnNO01R43",
      },
      {
        front: "sobre",
        back: "on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LjrXoohzyX",
      },
      {
        front: "te quedas",
        back: "you stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XYdwc6aBG2",
      },
      {
        front: "todo el mundo",
        back: "all the world",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T9hlyYZ4Pb",
      },
      {
        front: "vengo",
        back: "I come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j2IVdsX9QJ",
      },
      {
        front: "venimos",
        back: "we come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pdKIchjt3J",
      },
      {
        front: "venir",
        back: "to come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LuWoB6yWEj",
      },
      {
        front: "viene",
        back: "comes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uWuZWF0EIA",
      },
      {
        front: "vienen",
        back: "they come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jRXhDhhE9X",
      },
      {
        front: "vienes",
        back: "you come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "071UlGokOH",
      },
      {
        front: "vuelvo",
        back: "I come back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G4TIAupqoc",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "HyrjZYt2S3",
    title: "Unit 37",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aprendiendo a",
        back: "learning to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sCmUYYlKKI",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudo a",
        back: "helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z6ZTl5kcCy",
      },
      {
        front: "cenar",
        back: "have dinner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "83VpYcSNh5",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunar",
        back: "eat breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9ZcXA63xKe",
      },
      {
        front: "empezamos a",
        back: "we started to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "APlzYAVXNp",
      },
      {
        front: "encontrar",
        back: "to find",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MvTKJx1tMw",
      },
      {
        front: "enseña a",
        back: "teach to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oReYXiBiAL",
      },
      {
        front: "entrada",
        back: "entrance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XaRV02Sp3N",
      },
      {
        front: "entradas",
        back: "tickets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S30DUSibFZ",
      },
      {
        front: "esperar",
        back: "expect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jOfZ31PdYC",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarnos",
        back: "wash ourselves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0ubBuCYjLe",
      },
      {
        front: "levantarme",
        back: "get up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vp8SZquLZa",
      },
      {
        front: "levantarte",
        back: "get up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sa1B2r3Hdi",
      },
      {
        front: "papel",
        back: "paper",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v5eeHo0Oyn",
      },
      {
        front: "papeles",
        back: "papers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9awwx8RTBC",
      },
      {
        front: "pie",
        back: "foot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "erXfqxLhpK",
      },
      {
        front: "pies",
        back: "feet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mIoFpHrn2B",
      },
      {
        front: "ponerme",
        back: "put myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K20rF66lrA",
      },
      {
        front: "ponerte",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yLEvMSDMYv",
      },
      {
        front: "probarse",
        back: "to try on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yt4GTWgvGe",
      },
      {
        front: "probarte",
        back: "taste you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S3AgGchv2c",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarme",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hjorGRsbpB",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarnos",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qzq34V6Mda",
      },
      {
        front: "recordar",
        back: "remind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ClzXuYphhU",
      },
      {
        front: "salir a",
        back: "go to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3dOimYzHZJ",
      },
      {
        front: "taza",
        back: "Bowl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E69dRBes4B",
      },
      {
        front: "tazas",
        back: "cups",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7rkXM3cnIR",
      },
      {
        front: "volar",
        back: "to fly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gneeHyQ7KU",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ok11RSBK0o",
    title: "Unit 38",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abres la",
        back: "you open the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q6bxvpqJmB",
      },
      {
        front: "acá",
        back: "here",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nb6Ouog1za",
      },
      {
        front: "allá",
        back: "there",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yxUyo3nxL6",
      },
      {
        front: "caja",
        back: "box",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E9b5kkhjwx",
      },
      {
        front: "cajas",
        back: "boxes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jPeKnPN95I",
      },
      {
        front: "cierro la",
        back: "I close the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nOhIWtimTO",
      },
      {
        front: "coges",
        back: "you take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rleFuxT04a",
      },
      {
        front: "cuartos",
        back: "rooms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "esmgpbGa1Q",
      },
      {
        front: "césped",
        back: "grass",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "88OXta9YKt",
      },
      {
        front: "demasiada",
        back: "too much",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fNA1tlHQyp",
      },
      {
        front: "demasiadas",
        back: "too many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FNu4AbHgoX",
      },
      {
        front: "demasiado",
        back: "too",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yFVpkCbkUQ",
      },
      {
        front: "demasiados",
        back: "too many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l2gqUXsnoi",
      },
      {
        front: "eso",
        back: "that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IcafvpwbF4",
      },
      {
        front: "granja",
        back: "farm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qSo98G2RVS",
      },
      {
        front: "levántate",
        back: "Get up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1gLeK7vIwD",
      },
      {
        front: "levántese",
        back: "stand up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7y0TH03F6T",
      },
      {
        front: "lávate",
        back: "wash yourself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DevzONxqQU",
      },
      {
        front: "lávese",
        back: "wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NiMLdZaX62",
      },
      {
        front: "mirando",
        back: "looking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0oY4cJ02t1",
      },
      {
        front: "miro",
        back: "I look",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JQMKASZLrD",
      },
      {
        front: "nos ayudas",
        back: "you help us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GYHY4CMZVi",
      },
      {
        front: "pared",
        back: "wall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4eAtCLzjwe",
      },
      {
        front: "paredes",
        back: "walls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NK1uxJ2bkZ",
      },
      {
        front: "piso",
        back: "floor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FtB60cgclC",
      },
      {
        front: "pisos",
        back: "floors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7UGb3F8hl3",
      },
      {
        front: "poca",
        back: "little",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1oSMi0Sahg",
      },
      {
        front: "pocas",
        back: "few",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aTB7BMCge6",
      },
      {
        front: "poco",
        back: "little bit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "em6dqqicH3",
      },
      {
        front: "pocos",
        back: "few",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xNvcTCJJZ3",
      },
      {
        front: "seguras",
        back: "safe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Def9fzGijt",
      },
      {
        front: "seguro",
        back: "sure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H7rF4hdZEG",
      },
      {
        front: "seguros",
        back: "insurance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t3QIaXcTqk",
      },
      {
        front: "sentarse",
        back: "feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gOj4eOf7sE",
      },
      {
        front: "siéntate",
        back: "Sit down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EkWw5H0FP2",
      },
      {
        front: "siéntese",
        back: "sit down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4DDd4NxVb1",
      },
      {
        front: "toda",
        back: "all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HskVvnIXXC",
      },
      {
        front: "todo",
        back: "all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OrJhD58rOK",
      },
      {
        front: "traes",
        back: "you bring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "26e2PK3ea0",
      },
      {
        front: "traigo",
        back: "I bring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HoPv155TIs",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "33vk3umlhr",
    title: "Unit 38",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "almuerza",
        back: "lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xk1Qj4PHnU",
      },
      {
        front: "almuerzo",
        back: "lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4X2OzP5dgk",
      },
      {
        front: "cien",
        back: "hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kka2rCUHBc",
      },
      {
        front: "dan",
        back: "give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oqfQtXzGZT",
      },
      {
        front: "dar",
        back: "give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rZ75HC4Hhf",
      },
      {
        front: "decimos",
        back: "we say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RQxu7n99Rt",
      },
      {
        front: "dice",
        back: "He says",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ysKfVFRa6O",
      },
      {
        front: "dicen",
        back: "they say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eLnNKZIxgP",
      },
      {
        front: "dices",
        back: "you say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BbGDItmcNl",
      },
      {
        front: "digo",
        back: "say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mb16PTkoa9",
      },
      {
        front: "doy",
        back: "I give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ueQg4jqVxc",
      },
      {
        front: "hermoso",
        back: "handsome",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OCMyPPgVw5",
      },
      {
        front: "inglesas",
        back: "English",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qERfkqqqu7",
      },
      {
        front: "ingleses",
        back: "English",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vz5q6o9aJG",
      },
      {
        front: "le",
        back: "you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7iy3fulJBm",
      },
      {
        front: "le hago",
        back: "I do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OUQCgtr5gz",
      },
      {
        front: "les",
        back: "them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s6g4DyDgJD",
      },
      {
        front: "mandamos",
        back: "we sent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Or00vii2d4",
      },
      {
        front: "mandar",
        back: "send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zbSXzyZMS0",
      },
      {
        front: "mandas",
        back: "you send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CtC7FIbadh",
      },
      {
        front: "mesera",
        back: "waitress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZFTlP0aTa2",
      },
      {
        front: "mesero",
        back: "waiter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oX3DNq8XZd",
      },
      {
        front: "mil",
        back: "one thousand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wvDvOTHSjr",
      },
      {
        front: "millones",
        back: "millions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SnNoz8hpk7",
      },
      {
        front: "millón",
        back: "million",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5zIt5S3SHL",
      },
      {
        front: "nada",
        back: "any",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xOSq6wW1Qu",
      },
      {
        front: "nada es",
        back: "nothing is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D7liSTUYdz",
      },
      {
        front: "noventa",
        back: "ninety",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lt0TGho1pg",
      },
      {
        front: "ochenta",
        back: "eighty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V0ZeRmTfEi",
      },
      {
        front: "oficinas",
        back: "Offices",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u0x4MplQN4",
      },
      {
        front: "portuguesa",
        back: "portuguese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lyL2pZrLW5",
      },
      {
        front: "portuguesas",
        back: "portuguese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ijpHMsbeT",
      },
      {
        front: "portugueses",
        back: "portuguese",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MzDYd1PZFV",
      },
      {
        front: "pregunta",
        back: "Question",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wPWRQcjBuy",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntamos",
        back: "we asked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "936KjhhmCP",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntan",
        back: "they ask",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RoJrjrcQlV",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntar",
        back: "to ask",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P3XKyoMLSP",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntas",
        back: "questions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zy4Qw8Dsta",
      },
      {
        front: "pregunto",
        back: "I ask",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AQhjXkFs4e",
      },
      {
        front: "setenta",
        back: "seventy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2khOY6vAfg",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "kwQ4VY69De",
    title: "Unit 39",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "objects1",
        back: "objects1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YWPn5ICIQP",
      },
      {
        front: "objects2",
        back: "objects2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1BtcllL4Bz",
      },
      {
        front: "objects3",
        back: "objects3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F1KwsMfw4r",
      },
      {
        front: "objects",
        back: "objects",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MY2BzRHOSz",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "zkBdcncCZF",
    title: "Unit 40",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abajo",
        back: "below",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yPyt6OIRff",
      },
      {
        front: "arriba",
        back: "up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6F0f3VCRuJ",
      },
      {
        front: "atrás",
        back: "behind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JhHV0czO0u",
      },
      {
        front: "buscando",
        back: "searching",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dy3FUCIsUr",
      },
      {
        front: "carretera",
        back: "road",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RDvN8QgNgH",
      },
      {
        front: "cercana",
        back: "close",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cR1UBhIkZY",
      },
      {
        front: "cercano",
        back: "near",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LZXBur0CIi",
      },
      {
        front: "dentro",
        back: "inside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LcjfgK08h0",
      },
      {
        front: "derecho",
        back: "right",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RRZZOwfVdW",
      },
      {
        front: "detrás",
        back: "behind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WCsxrRSxUy",
      },
      {
        front: "direcciones",
        back: "addresses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtcxoV2EtP",
      },
      {
        front: "disculpa",
        back: "sorry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vp3R47UHgb",
      },
      {
        front: "disculpe",
        back: "señor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jdV8ExY1U6",
      },
      {
        front: "enfrente",
        back: "in front",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QvRT27jxF3",
      },
      {
        front: "entre",
        back: "Come in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wf738h7DWu",
      },
      {
        front: "espera",
        back: "wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oyIqxKoDx1",
      },
      {
        front: "esperando",
        back: "expecting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0WyKZpRrZ5",
      },
      {
        front: "espero",
        back: "wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P1tc3ce3Gy",
      },
      {
        front: "final",
        back: "final",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S4xqu6isSf",
      },
      {
        front: "fuera",
        back: "outside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BsuM6p24Dt",
      },
      {
        front: "gira",
        back: "tour",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V1D4J1XVhd",
      },
      {
        front: "giramos",
        back: "we turn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iZ94j4Zpun",
      },
      {
        front: "girar",
        back: "spin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nTQe7mOkEG",
      },
      {
        front: "giras",
        back: "tours",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WqkfdDKwTX",
      },
      {
        front: "gire",
        back: "turn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gDDI0od2vA",
      },
      {
        front: "giro",
        back: "turn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SDzzZg7ii2",
      },
      {
        front: "perdona",
        back: "forgives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fo9rfEJ1ev",
      },
      {
        front: "perdone",
        back: "excuse me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rPMeQi7DlQ",
      },
      {
        front: "seguir",
        back: "continue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yAgDn4hjmV",
      },
      {
        front: "siga",
        back: "follow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ny5eJ22Frr",
      },
      {
        front: "sigue",
        back: "follow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "51mBvliuRk",
      },
      {
        front: "tome",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GlWFUpg29Z",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "b0zAdgcAcF",
    title: "Unit 40",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aprendiste",
        back: "you learned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SRE5f3iOzB",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendí",
        back: "I learned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ex8CHbEjq1",
      },
      {
        front: "ayer",
        back: "Yesterday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IlHPKEqYg1",
      },
      {
        front: "bebiste",
        back: "you drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7odl2YFUxD",
      },
      {
        front: "bebí",
        back: "drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oE5JFEuzh5",
      },
      {
        front: "comiste",
        back: "You ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DLVmgHDv1O",
      },
      {
        front: "comí",
        back: "I ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5oOn574jAd",
      },
      {
        front: "conociste",
        back: "you met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YJIGk2p1CL",
      },
      {
        front: "conocí",
        back: "I met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CNJyyGrpgU",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiaste",
        back: "have you studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JxP4LxEh07",
      },
      {
        front: "estudié",
        back: "studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bLrVD920os",
      },
      {
        front: "estuve",
        back: "I was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GTTQpaoauS",
      },
      {
        front: "estuviste",
        back: "you were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "liqGvh19Sn",
      },
      {
        front: "fui",
        back: "I was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G3vZccqeb5",
      },
      {
        front: "fuiste",
        back: "you were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zMsYflUWad",
      },
      {
        front: "hablaste",
        back: "you spoke",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "auZTLqBssS",
      },
      {
        front: "hablé",
        back: "I talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8uBlO6E4oq",
      },
      {
        front: "hace mucho tiempo",
        back: "long ago",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0qCdOZBDtl",
      },
      {
        front: "pasada",
        back: "pass",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pv8bExe6SN",
      },
      {
        front: "pasadas",
        back: "past",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5xHSz5ptnT",
      },
      {
        front: "pasado",
        back: "last",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ocJdkPzjuU",
      },
      {
        front: "pasados",
        back: "past",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4rUqDHag3O",
      },
      {
        front: "probaste",
        back: "did you try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G0cmZrotaf",
      },
      {
        front: "probé",
        back: "i tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U9rOvFJWgT",
      },
      {
        front: "viajaste",
        back: "you traveled",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VGXoB9De4l",
      },
      {
        front: "viaje",
        back: "travel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZIPXjju27l",
      },
      {
        front: "viajes",
        back: "travels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l60fTzgArW",
      },
      {
        front: "viajé",
        back: "travel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Zba4NhCij",
      },
      {
        front: "visitaste",
        back: "did you visit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q86ZLs1BG4",
      },
      {
        front: "visité",
        back: "Visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KkCjCIFCAJ",
      },
      {
        front: "viviste",
        back: "you lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l4SXnLahGq",
      },
      {
        front: "viví",
        back: "i lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0NR32YjogS",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "9GxwDRWBWv",
    title: "Unit 41",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrieron",
        back: "they opened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ceOYPDP2G2",
      },
      {
        front: "abrió",
        back: "Opened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Obk8U4SJlD",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendieron",
        back: "they learned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uxBBSY2hM0",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendió",
        back: "learned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ClAxgjyiYl",
      },
      {
        front: "búhos",
        back: "owls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VqQu3XXQnR",
      },
      {
        front: "cerdo",
        back: "pig",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1r7GkPQhlr",
      },
      {
        front: "cerdos",
        back: "pigs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UqpnUE5Zl9",
      },
      {
        front: "cerraron",
        back: "closed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "paXtlAF6aH",
      },
      {
        front: "cerró",
        back: "hill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u0NTxRS2y6",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinaron",
        back: "they cooked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S2X9XKEugB",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinó",
        back: "cooked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ika06Gd4kl",
      },
      {
        front: "comieron",
        back: "they ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4A4JiAmdJd",
      },
      {
        front: "comió",
        back: "ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ynD1aDDdu6",
      },
      {
        front: "escribieron",
        back: "they wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YGP13sNJwu",
      },
      {
        front: "escribió",
        back: "wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wDI8FXnYGt",
      },
      {
        front: "estuvieron",
        back: "they were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IeCA5ll90T",
      },
      {
        front: "estuvo",
        back: "he was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YL4N7HquSB",
      },
      {
        front: "fue",
        back: "was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mz3ZpvUnIY",
      },
      {
        front: "fueron",
        back: "They were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xS9ownCXDB",
      },
      {
        front: "lavaron",
        back: "they washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i6oPxByjgh",
      },
      {
        front: "lavó",
        back: "Washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TMO9APyhsj",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiaron",
        back: "they cleaned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hSIjofwQQx",
      },
      {
        front: "limpió",
        back: "clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AaN6TueSkr",
      },
      {
        front: "miraron",
        back: "they looked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sFoNCRpLJ8",
      },
      {
        front: "miró",
        back: "I look",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5FczcL53f3",
      },
      {
        front: "salieron",
        back: "They left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tEp60dinFi",
      },
      {
        front: "salió",
        back: "he left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "olTueAoWeV",
      },
      {
        front: "vaca",
        back: "cow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qhHKMCn7Ju",
      },
      {
        front: "vacas",
        back: "cows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6eBmd0ScIA",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "YNcd0Rkdxz",
    title: "Unit 42",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abriste",
        back: "you opened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4wk1w344Zc",
      },
      {
        front: "abrí",
        back: "I opened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T7wc0nJeYs",
      },
      {
        front: "bebieron",
        back: "drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UyW6aBzel8",
      },
      {
        front: "bebió",
        back: "drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3Eyw03LVSw",
      },
      {
        front: "caminaste",
        back: "you walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wmO82fuouu",
      },
      {
        front: "caminé",
        back: "i walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YKtOGQim6d",
      },
      {
        front: "cogimos",
        back: "we caught",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W2spUJTNmn",
      },
      {
        front: "conocieron",
        back: "they met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1Qd8v6Tpwj",
      },
      {
        front: "conoció",
        back: "He met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hAwOxoLD9i",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutaron",
        back: "they enjoyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GIvPt2ztF9",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutaste",
        back: "you enjoyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MairQsShGz",
      },
      {
        front: "disfruté",
        back: "enjoyment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SjoTyzMqDk",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutó",
        back: "enjoyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p2g44lPa3b",
      },
      {
        front: "escribiste",
        back: "you wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gy4wVdT1aq",
      },
      {
        front: "escribí",
        back: "i wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hVBEmkaLyB",
      },
      {
        front: "hice",
        back: "I did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uMa9A82KKK",
      },
      {
        front: "hicieron",
        back: "they made",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sQMKvkcXzU",
      },
      {
        front: "hicimos",
        back: "we did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h781mPOpvE",
      },
      {
        front: "hiciste",
        back: "did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Aqbwh8qqPh",
      },
      {
        front: "hizo",
        back: "did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a2G4bvyV1O",
      },
      {
        front: "miramos",
        back: "we look",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S9bfubRTFp",
      },
      {
        front: "saliste",
        back: "did you go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d5glKVoJK4",
      },
      {
        front: "salí",
        back: "I left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z0ykKPcvH4",
      },
      {
        front: "viajaron",
        back: "traveled",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fBaHna8Ncq",
      },
      {
        front: "viajó",
        back: "traveled",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G5YCor1yqB",
      },
      {
        front: "visitaron",
        back: "they visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L3rp4jtNSP",
      },
      {
        front: "visitó",
        back: "visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FZQxu0Rx7z",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "YcRmrESNuR",
    title: "Unit 42",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "anoche",
        back: "last night",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3jayG5wnIp",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendimos",
        back: "we learned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zu3lsWAiYU",
      },
      {
        front: "bailamos",
        back: "we Dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bWaYJCAHZh",
      },
      {
        front: "barco",
        back: "boat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fq7C7QLjC8",
      },
      {
        front: "barcos",
        back: "boats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jZg8RHytwD",
      },
      {
        front: "bebimos",
        back: "we drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "94brdhgMGM",
      },
      {
        front: "caminamos",
        back: "We walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KS2vH4ZfN9",
      },
      {
        front: "cenamos",
        back: "we had dinner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hfwIJK7WZv",
      },
      {
        front: "comimos",
        back: "we ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kFA5jzuInR",
      },
      {
        front: "conocimos",
        back: "we met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ty6lSlQQsR",
      },
      {
        front: "corrimos",
        back: "we ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8p8Wi95Byj",
      },
      {
        front: "después",
        back: "after",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aPtq80xoIj",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutamos",
        back: "We enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ev1dNyFwYF",
      },
      {
        front: "dormimos",
        back: "we slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MvgRnnLkjr",
      },
      {
        front: "escuchamos",
        back: "we hear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vr6iOK9CA4",
      },
      {
        front: "estuvimos",
        back: "we were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qDNyymlcCL",
      },
      {
        front: "fuimos",
        back: "went",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ipmGtJolN2",
      },
      {
        front: "montamos",
        back: "we ride",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3R8z3nya28",
      },
      {
        front: "nadamos",
        back: "we swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QGv8kWP9l1",
      },
      {
        front: "nieve",
        back: "snow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XFZhzAbDsw",
      },
      {
        front: "pasamos",
        back: "we passed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8dJSBqsEsa",
      },
      {
        front: "practicamos",
        back: "we practice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "acDPToLO21",
      },
      {
        front: "queridos",
        back: "dear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1q95FEDvBI",
      },
      {
        front: "salimos",
        back: "we went out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jDvBCkXfMs",
      },
      {
        front: "viajamos",
        back: "We travel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IOFti0jW0e",
      },
      {
        front: "vimos",
        back: "we saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YBPg5Cfer8",
      },
      {
        front: "visitamos",
        back: "we visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y0GTp1cqLP",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "AFMtYO1DmX",
    title: "Unit 43",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "alguno",
        back: "some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TnG63XABfs",
      },
      {
        front: "algún",
        back: "some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Sg4uXmTE0W",
      },
      {
        front: "ay",
        back: "Oh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IbDRBJPJEQ",
      },
      {
        front: "buen",
        back: "good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZF25DzLSYe",
      },
      {
        front: "ciento",
        back: "hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pYFfoEunJr",
      },
      {
        front: "completamente",
        back: "completely",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IBTqrxvdk5",
      },
      {
        front: "compré",
        back: "I bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qOmWrj6KXh",
      },
      {
        front: "compró",
        back: "I buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q67O2gHYTb",
      },
      {
        front: "con nadie",
        back: "with nobody",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3JQNwX2RUL",
      },
      {
        front: "doscientos",
        back: "Two Hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JMZmlefPya",
      },
      {
        front: "elegir",
        back: "choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ubFzywPy3b",
      },
      {
        front: "gran",
        back: "big",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iLVJU41776",
      },
      {
        front: "mal",
        back: "wrong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qJ5vf6X14G",
      },
      {
        front: "mi",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3QWModMpiJ",
      },
      {
        front: "nuevo",
        back: "my new",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e5oMnY6Hvr",
      },
      {
        front: "nadie",
        back: "no one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i07xR7sdPL",
      },
      {
        front: "ninguna",
        back: "none",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fn6Ge8hjK6",
      },
      {
        front: "ninguno",
        back: "none",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FGb9I2gMQw",
      },
      {
        front: "ninguno de",
        back: "none",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wA0mHoExGV",
      },
      {
        front: "ningunos",
        back: "none",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AU513Ro8vE",
      },
      {
        front: "ningún",
        back: "no",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XbMJ81I7kS",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidar",
        back: "forget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "20SK9wyHvL",
      },
      {
        front: "olvido",
        back: "forgot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CFEcUAJdhb",
      },
      {
        front: "pagamos",
        back: "we pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zp6fRQwqp4",
      },
      {
        front: "pagó",
        back: "I pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uKP1810iZM",
      },
      {
        front: "pobre",
        back: "poor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HaNuda5THA",
      },
      {
        front: "pobres",
        back: "poor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oRZb5FApy0",
      },
      {
        front: "primer",
        back: "first",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NYzadfsRb5",
      },
      {
        front: "segundo",
        back: "second",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qQWtFKfdlh",
      },
      {
        front: "tercer",
        back: "third",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aWScnffzed",
      },
      {
        front: "última",
        back: "last",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2AngsnBzIg",
      },
      {
        front: "últimas",
        back: "latest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dLM5N1up9h",
      },
      {
        front: "último",
        back: "latest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YpgPzF4Azl",
      },
      {
        front: "últimos",
        back: "last",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bgawx1dbPS",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "C2cE7CfVZ9",
    title: "Unit 44",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ahí",
        back: "there",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i717t5UIYV",
      },
      {
        front: "anuncios",
        back: "advertisements",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MXoLc16xeP",
      },
      {
        front: "coge",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mLPP6jbuDd",
      },
      {
        front: "cogemos",
        back: "we take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AhRD3JG8yy",
      },
      {
        front: "cogen",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GgIrBIGMoX",
      },
      {
        front: "coger",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VaV1O3LAFv",
      },
      {
        front: "cojo",
        back: "lame",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q20ENgXkaL",
      },
      {
        front: "dura",
        back: "hard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WVRfl6gjYB",
      },
      {
        front: "duro",
        back: "Lasted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "33MtQ3rH3e",
      },
      {
        front: "el azul",
        back: "the blue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hBhltWsE0H",
      },
      {
        front: "el mío",
        back: "mine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fcONB7OxP9",
      },
      {
        front: "el rojo",
        back: "the Red",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jLozmptfJd",
      },
      {
        front: "elegimos",
        back: "we choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mAHSTMaEfb",
      },
      {
        front: "elige",
        back: "choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AKOglvBy3i",
      },
      {
        front: "eligen",
        back: "choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OhiYDlUZgq",
      },
      {
        front: "eliges",
        back: "you choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NqZswkP93H",
      },
      {
        front: "elijo",
        back: "I choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mP0vxqhktB",
      },
      {
        front: "emocionante",
        back: "exciting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I2x9YDH9il",
      },
      {
        front: "encontraste",
        back: "by contrast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QFoHXS5Jdc",
      },
      {
        front: "encontré",
        back: "I found",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ggkj9ILNC",
      },
      {
        front: "encontró",
        back: "found",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aqGVsywAsd",
      },
      {
        front: "graciosa",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sX6XQtGutF",
      },
      {
        front: "graciosas",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YwMD38cFcH",
      },
      {
        front: "gracioso",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QbyCG7I3Xy",
      },
      {
        front: "la amarilla",
        back: "the yellow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qpv94ZWXau",
      },
      {
        front: "la tuya",
        back: "yours",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JEvh22qjBM",
      },
      {
        front: "las nuestras",
        back: "our",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dEnAVxrenB",
      },
      {
        front: "no",
        back: "not",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6F1YPfjaj5",
      },
      {
        front: "oraciones",
        back: "prayers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "btRBW6StLP",
      },
      {
        front: "pagaste",
        back: "you paid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S149Ml5i2v",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P0C8VeH6fg",
      },
      {
        front: "sí",
        back: "Yeah",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VgiohhFcbR",
      },
      {
        front: "usando",
        back: "wearing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fRM39yltWV",
      },
      {
        front: "vida",
        back: "lifetime",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "njYnwBI7FT",
      },
      {
        front: "vidas",
        back: "lives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G3sC2wAUzp",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7D5O2x3uyI",
    title: "Unit 44",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pasttense11",
        back: "pasttense11",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8bwwH05pwm",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense12",
        back: "pasttense12",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KYRe5PXFfy",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense13",
        back: "pasttense13",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Atz7AwHOKN",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense",
        back: "pasttense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tO66kNG2eo",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0YBGxPFsgr",
    title: "Unit 45",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "calurosa",
        back: "hot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HoZoTYJSLT",
      },
      {
        front: "caluroso",
        back: "warm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N6eYLoWpmt",
      },
      {
        front: "calurosos",
        back: "hot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GD9w3ssnyN",
      },
      {
        front: "caminó",
        back: "path",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C0IMHcmDSZ",
      },
      {
        front: "clima",
        back: "weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s4b0SmzK32",
      },
      {
        front: "comenzamos",
        back: "we started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pYj7RosItb",
      },
      {
        front: "comenzar",
        back: "begin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LZbSZrFEHD",
      },
      {
        front: "comienza",
        back: "begins",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w39V2NmSHC",
      },
      {
        front: "comienzas",
        back: "you start",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2nw7y1MbRU",
      },
      {
        front: "corrió",
        back: "ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7rHTitexns",
      },
      {
        front: "dormimos",
        back: "we slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "alSmYz14Pq",
      },
      {
        front: "duermen",
        back: "sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TyGM1ssoV8",
      },
      {
        front: "duermes",
        back: "Do you sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2HWpxCM4vX",
      },
      {
        front: "duermo",
        back: "I sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rI1B1L5xYb",
      },
      {
        front: "encantar",
        back: "love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "377QrlcXMm",
      },
      {
        front: "encontrarnos",
        back: "meet us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WDObAAVXAw",
      },
      {
        front: "encontrarse",
        back: "meet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NYYD7H4zN6",
      },
      {
        front: "frío",
        back: "cold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cJcSMFMLaV",
      },
      {
        front: "fue un",
        back: "was a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jioPLdW1nV",
      },
      {
        front: "fueron unos",
        back: "they were some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eGQJNJ5RKX",
      },
      {
        front: "haber",
        back: "to have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "luKbPHD7RM",
      },
      {
        front: "llover",
        back: "rain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7pQ9nHYSXf",
      },
      {
        front: "lloviendo",
        back: "raining",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R2lCDZQaNQ",
      },
      {
        front: "llovió",
        back: "it rained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OXOfEEcCoC",
      },
      {
        front: "lluvia",
        back: "rain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b39M9Eow1O",
      },
      {
        front: "me encuentro",
        back: "I meet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zFi7kUAcvw",
      },
      {
        front: "montaste",
        back: "you rode",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HLxMF4WcBO",
      },
      {
        front: "nevando",
        back: "snowing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XKcKT546Ge",
      },
      {
        front: "nevar",
        back: "to snow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "26LHaCjINZ",
      },
      {
        front: "nevó",
        back: "nevus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qkzsDu8G5Q",
      },
      {
        front: "nos encontramos",
        back: "we meet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "33k0dfHWaP",
      },
      {
        front: "primera",
        back: "first",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oqbIhJHhMh",
      },
      {
        front: "primeras",
        back: "first",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dRgprPv8Zm",
      },
      {
        front: "primero",
        back: "First",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WKduXtMgC4",
      },
      {
        front: "primeros",
        back: "first",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kgtiMkIclk",
      },
      {
        front: "se encuentra",
        back: "it's found",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SwIXqwk7Ui",
      },
      {
        front: "se encuentran",
        back: "they find each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x7sqbxTSte",
      },
      {
        front: "te encuentras",
        back: "you meet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Br02sBi4nK",
      },
      {
        front: "todo",
        back: "all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OVh41QRpZt",
      },
      {
        front: "árbol",
        back: "tree",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cjDdKddiW2",
      },
      {
        front: "árboles",
        back: "trees",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l7UH7XboNg",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jWQkJraTOW",
    title: "Unit 45",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "algo de",
        back: "some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hESSt23No9",
      },
      {
        front: "alguien",
        back: "someone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4xW4R27eQU",
      },
      {
        front: "caminaron",
        back: "they walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c9DKOLDr2C",
      },
      {
        front: "compraron",
        back: "bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pvpWdQQ0LL",
      },
      {
        front: "compraste",
        back: "you bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iXHElcZCGQ",
      },
      {
        front: "cuatrocientos",
        back: "four hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pxlD6Fvffz",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutando",
        back: "enjoying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GcumtZpzaw",
      },
      {
        front: "encontramos",
        back: "we find",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "94dIitcYfo",
      },
      {
        front: "encontraron",
        back: "They found",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u1t7ehww1A",
      },
      {
        front: "entonces",
        back: "then",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qf7Jl9xx67",
      },
      {
        front: "espere",
        back: "Wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VULOeaK2WG",
      },
      {
        front: "fumar",
        back: "to smoke",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c9EuEddV91",
      },
      {
        front: "hay alguna",
        back: "There are some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ssAtN0WDJ5",
      },
      {
        front: "hay algún",
        back: "is there any",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qP7kUygIs2",
      },
      {
        front: "nacionalidad",
        back: "nationality",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7KZ4CjHZxF",
      },
      {
        front: "nos vemos",
        back: "See ya",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OgfnaOQbXU",
      },
      {
        front: "posible",
        back: "possible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1wjCDk7fT8",
      },
      {
        front: "querría",
        back: "I would want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JKhii6k3uZ",
      },
      {
        front: "quinientos",
        back: "five hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xjHjTp0J36",
      },
      {
        front: "ruido",
        back: "noise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ht0AP0oWhR",
      },
      {
        front: "seiscientos",
        back: "six hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZmXgnjUXCn",
      },
      {
        front: "siguiente",
        back: "Next",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZSwAHpnfEi",
      },
      {
        front: "siguientes",
        back: "following",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YKRYBRoDsw",
      },
      {
        front: "trescientos",
        back: "three hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4LJT1Ua2uQ",
      },
      {
        front: "vine",
        back: "came",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DZHi3suxN4",
      },
      {
        front: "vinieron",
        back: "they came",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xshzRmTZsA",
      },
      {
        front: "vinimos",
        back: "we came",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hi1dbetTct",
      },
      {
        front: "viniste",
        back: "did you come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "extFjORJiz",
      },
      {
        front: "vino",
        back: "wine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wW10cKe0SK",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tHIeT6YgYn",
    title: "Unit 46",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "canté",
        back: "sing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ke3aOIHBsC",
      },
      {
        front: "cantó",
        back: "singing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qYLjLbLKQJ",
      },
      {
        front: "cogieron",
        back: "They took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tVV8zLt06D",
      },
      {
        front: "cogiste",
        back: "you took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LarswN8uos",
      },
      {
        front: "cogió",
        back: "caught",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P8jBnEN0tZ",
      },
      {
        front: "cogí",
        back: "I took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Feqgd0UMCA",
      },
      {
        front: "comprende",
        back: "understands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VGt2wUNlD7",
      },
      {
        front: "comprenden",
        back: "understand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "co1JKxIQbl",
      },
      {
        front: "comprender",
        back: "grasp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7uNUZ7pINA",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendes",
        back: "do you understand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9CEPzgTN4I",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendo",
        back: "understand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8DZh8BzdQt",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujamos",
        back: "we draw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nUSNJXOWCW",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujaron",
        back: "they drew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CyB9WiyPzL",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujé",
        back: "I drew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QlgeBZWIWV",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujó",
        back: "He drew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MDuxvagkJd",
      },
      {
        front: "ejemplo",
        back: "example",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3pUzyErco1",
      },
      {
        front: "ejemplos",
        back: "examples",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m8gJOgJNN5",
      },
      {
        front: "empecé",
        back: "I started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AxmxzTB13O",
      },
      {
        front: "empezaron",
        back: "they started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mQknbFXsoB",
      },
      {
        front: "empezaste",
        back: "you started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uPumg6c7xQ",
      },
      {
        front: "empezó",
        back: "it started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jgVKECIZNs",
      },
      {
        front: "encuentran",
        back: "find",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4r6TsCys75",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñamos",
        back: "we teach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UBRtpo8SPv",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñando",
        back: "teaching",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nQVTPpr8Qm",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñar",
        back: "to teach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IgyVR4HgCZ",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñaron",
        back: "they taught",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BZfGlqDJDR",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñaste",
        back: "you taught",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rBzCeYeDXQ",
      },
      {
        front: "enseñé",
        back: "I taught",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qeuXUbktte",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiaron",
        back: "they studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CtywW6prMe",
      },
      {
        front: "estudió",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JFoCTw0cJx",
      },
      {
        front: "habló",
        back: "I speak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SyIDJE4quM",
      },
      {
        front: "me preocupo",
        back: "I am worried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yevI0QvNwx",
      },
      {
        front: "me siento",
        back: "I feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YOkE2dmR1g",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitar",
        back: "need",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fJ6v58Vyz2",
      },
      {
        front: "nos sentamos",
        back: "we sit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gtLua1LUhT",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidamos",
        back: "we forgot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UNEXTljrWf",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidaron",
        back: "they forgot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FtIrS3iTSu",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidaste",
        back: "you forgot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BCEa82Iagc",
      },
      {
        front: "parar",
        back: "stall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0Of7YPa2Jd",
      },
      {
        front: "preocupar+prpers",
        back: "worry+prospers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3EH7sSwSXT",
      },
      {
        front: "preocuparme",
        back: "worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ewxZiyb9hN",
      },
      {
        front: "preocuparnos",
        back: "worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtsUF164qq",
      },
      {
        front: "preocuparse",
        back: "to worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SHNtG5Otmo",
      },
      {
        front: "preocuparte",
        back: "worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HypDWCW2rn",
      },
      {
        front: "responde",
        back: "answer back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SI4zMrZcXF",
      },
      {
        front: "respondemos",
        back: "we answer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qotxt0XJ3V",
      },
      {
        front: "responden",
        back: "they answer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DdSuVOUvxo",
      },
      {
        front: "responder",
        back: "reply",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y9bjkqRtE7",
      },
      {
        front: "respondes",
        back: "you answer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K8WI9E1o7J",
      },
      {
        front: "respondieron",
        back: "they responded",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ghcAJvCKm6",
      },
      {
        front: "respondimos",
        back: "we responded",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GaPBK76wEE",
      },
      {
        front: "respondiste",
        back: "you answered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d6iYTRMGPu",
      },
      {
        front: "respondió",
        back: "answered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rzTz57QUMd",
      },
      {
        front: "respondo",
        back: "I answer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8idhifMzFn",
      },
      {
        front: "se preocupan",
        back: "they worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c16FRrbQx2",
      },
      {
        front: "se sientan",
        back: "they sit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eeRtA5pk5j",
      },
      {
        front: "sentarnos",
        back: "sit down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KD5FXNk5yc",
      },
      {
        front: "te preocupas",
        back: "you worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F8uKRdn6cd",
      },
      {
        front: "te sientas",
        back: "you sit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DVmhCckViE",
      },
      {
        front: "tomaron",
        back: "they took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WjQ4ZhB6Jm",
      },
      {
        front: "tomaste",
        back: "do you drink tea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GLq598Ri32",
      },
      {
        front: "tomé",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k08PLbUEXn",
      },
      {
        front: "tomó",
        back: "I take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jQGNQjD6i8",
      },
      {
        front: "vi",
        back: "saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zrHNXsNwc9",
      },
      {
        front: "vieron",
        back: "saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GR4EuvG9wk",
      },
      {
        front: "vio",
        back: "he saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RCLrWgkH2s",
      },
      {
        front: "viste",
        back: "dresses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yl3ioirTX3",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0fGRPdLqZa",
    title: "Unit 47",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acabar",
        back: "finish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GOV977AxfG",
      },
      {
        front: "acordarme",
        back: "remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fyBxBoCiMR",
      },
      {
        front: "acordarnos",
        back: "remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gQivm3Y6h4",
      },
      {
        front: "acordarte",
        back: "remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MypWP87XsN",
      },
      {
        front: "ah",
        back: "oh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CMwiZnkmKP",
      },
      {
        front: "barba",
        back: "beard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vAXqpX6dSS",
      },
      {
        front: "boca",
        back: "mouth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "33ROeKMvOw",
      },
      {
        front: "brazo",
        back: "arm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jOwsHvA9AB",
      },
      {
        front: "brazos",
        back: "arms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "32V85hNwUi",
      },
      {
        front: "cabeza",
        back: "head",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o0ZuKqcBS4",
      },
      {
        front: "cabezas",
        back: "heads",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jtL15BZpME",
      },
      {
        front: "cerré",
        back: "I closed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e1LqW927Dq",
      },
      {
        front: "cuerpo",
        back: "body",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zOjEKETJiO",
      },
      {
        front: "cuerpos",
        back: "bodies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oNLhfOKXXv",
      },
      {
        front: "despertarme",
        back: "wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LG5FfeRqch",
      },
      {
        front: "despertarnos",
        back: "wake us up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SwVdGNIofA",
      },
      {
        front: "despertarse",
        back: "wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dF2QDg7mlh",
      },
      {
        front: "despertarte",
        back: "wake you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nP53Qq67OA",
      },
      {
        front: "despiertas",
        back: "wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TGwmGZJWzi",
      },
      {
        front: "encima",
        back: "above",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mM8DN1EgnU",
      },
      {
        front: "gustó",
        back: "taste",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZmRQyLswgG",
      },
      {
        front: "lleva puesto",
        back: "wearing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3nEGOAR2Db",
      },
      {
        front: "me acuerdo",
        back: "I remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NhImc1Asd1",
      },
      {
        front: "me despierto",
        back: "I wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uRZSHKKc7L",
      },
      {
        front: "me levanté",
        back: "I got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Km8k93HjJG",
      },
      {
        front: "narices",
        back: "nose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hd5EXeu8z1",
      },
      {
        front: "nariz",
        back: "nose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NU3g7CYQzu",
      },
      {
        front: "nos acordamos",
        back: "we remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JpLvuoBR2L",
      },
      {
        front: "nos despertamos",
        back: "we wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZlY0yzRp4b",
      },
      {
        front: "nos levantamos",
        back: "we got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WgT02mwE8J",
      },
      {
        front: "oigo",
        back: "i hear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RoM9yCVWuV",
      },
      {
        front: "oye",
        back: "hears",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7tFovFnebN",
      },
      {
        front: "oyen",
        back: "hear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VjF64OFT8x",
      },
      {
        front: "oyes",
        back: "you hear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOdh4eY0JS",
      },
      {
        front: "oímos",
        back: "we heard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GeRaGx3eeZ",
      },
      {
        front: "oír",
        back: "hear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rhl4g6YyEU",
      },
      {
        front: "pierna",
        back: "leg",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yUP2oC5UBj",
      },
      {
        front: "piernas",
        back: "legs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xdoAEikDV7",
      },
      {
        front: "queda",
        back: "is left over",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sjJtjzkie7",
      },
      {
        front: "quedamos",
        back: "we stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hIvU2j3XGF",
      },
      {
        front: "quedan",
        back: "remain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6I4HSwlqRK",
      },
      {
        front: "quedar",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IThkfgo9C9",
      },
      {
        front: "quedas",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DoJOPkbgaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "quedo",
        back: "I stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1cPL5Ix1FF",
      },
      {
        front: "se acuerda",
        back: "he remembers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BdD5oYSJVI",
      },
      {
        front: "se acuerdan",
        back: "remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JpPZVmalQ8",
      },
      {
        front: "se despierta",
        back: "wakes up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kalhxWPEVk",
      },
      {
        front: "se despiertan",
        back: "they wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YZRzzwbmKj",
      },
      {
        front: "se levantaron",
        back: "they rose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qLVRv7BS6Z",
      },
      {
        front: "se levantó",
        back: "got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KVS4YTDcKk",
      },
      {
        front: "sentirnos",
        back: "feel us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yNFchhA2eo",
      },
      {
        front: "sentirse",
        back: "feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GeaixyLCIV",
      },
      {
        front: "sentirte",
        back: "feel you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T12OKYw4RR",
      },
      {
        front: "soñar",
        back: "Sound",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g2S6HhXx7w",
      },
      {
        front: "te acuerdas",
        back: "do you remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rAwLuqTMBt",
      },
      {
        front: "te despiertas",
        back: "you wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v83XOSH6kV",
      },
      {
        front: "te levantaste",
        back: "you got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5HgfMq7Ses",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "EFxq7G7Fth",
    title: "Unit 48",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acostar+prpers",
        back: "lay down+prpers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tA0UhBatuP",
      },
      {
        front: "acostarme",
        back: "lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jQFSWuXnPi",
      },
      {
        front: "acostarse",
        back: "lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e9wTtokwcw",
      },
      {
        front: "acostarte",
        back: "lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q1IxVKM9sZ",
      },
      {
        front: "ajedrez",
        back: "Chess",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xQPBBxlaPK",
      },
      {
        front: "allí",
        back: "over there",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MypSTw1tWj",
      },
      {
        front: "cansadísimo",
        back: "very tired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "spneoD01wb",
      },
      {
        front: "cuando",
        back: "when",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DygAyCGQ29",
      },
      {
        front: "de vez en cuando",
        back: "once in a while",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J032YSYpTW",
      },
      {
        front: "dificilísimo",
        back: "very difficult",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TTc7DObIWN",
      },
      {
        front: "encantaron",
        back: "they loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TFlngGfrLS",
      },
      {
        front: "encantó",
        back: "charm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RU5DqmLscY",
      },
      {
        front: "fantástica",
        back: "fantastic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QhOWm2YpUQ",
      },
      {
        front: "fantásticas",
        back: "fantastic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PXDPyfiSXq",
      },
      {
        front: "fantástico",
        back: "fantastic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bi1rfoncbf",
      },
      {
        front: "fantásticos",
        back: "fantastic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xttBbxF0Mc",
      },
      {
        front: "frecuentemente",
        back: "frequently",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vFp5tZY1OU",
      },
      {
        front: "generalmente",
        back: "usually",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2vz3hpcjES",
      },
      {
        front: "gimnasios",
        back: "gyms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h7cIN8mKle",
      },
      {
        front: "golf",
        back: "Golf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YsTKcVW3jR",
      },
      {
        front: "grandísimo",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwaS3LiL7z",
      },
      {
        front: "gustaron",
        back: "they liked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c9JgxNH7Vv",
      },
      {
        front: "me acuesto",
        back: "I lay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5BAzodqoKZ",
      },
      {
        front: "morada",
        back: "dwelling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m0sPGjMqhc",
      },
      {
        front: "morado",
        back: "purple",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xZCS7kgK5E",
      },
      {
        front: "nos acostamos",
        back: "we go to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rkd9XWRsHQ",
      },
      {
        front: "odia",
        back: "hates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QCpNmEzVQq",
      },
      {
        front: "odiar",
        back: "hate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H1bHH5MOx8",
      },
      {
        front: "odiaron",
        back: "they hated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XhXmPdC9ta",
      },
      {
        front: "odiaste",
        back: "you hated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k3ZnqTae6S",
      },
      {
        front: "odio",
        back: "hatred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QWlU3Wng2n",
      },
      {
        front: "preferimos",
        back: "we prefer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NepkM2WHli",
      },
      {
        front: "preferir",
        back: "to prefer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Pe4Qfh4xkv",
      },
      {
        front: "prefieren",
        back: "prefer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vKSYSLHy7t",
      },
      {
        front: "se acuesta",
        back: "lies down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DbCF6GHdd4",
      },
      {
        front: "se acuestan",
        back: "they lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RcjMWZgJ84",
      },
      {
        front: "te acuestas",
        back: "you lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5NobyeOZ5x",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XEAsYBK0sG",
      },
      {
        front: "un poco",
        back: "a little",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zjnTDquf2e",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "bNR7BaGoqx",
    title: "Unit 48",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ayudamos",
        back: "we help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SPqjIVrFGg",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudaste",
        back: "you helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TCAOI9nQPm",
      },
      {
        front: "bailaron",
        back: "they danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nnxFhScTkl",
      },
      {
        front: "bailaste",
        back: "you danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RfqxkYyQzf",
      },
      {
        front: "bailé",
        back: "dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QqmLl9CTSV",
      },
      {
        front: "bailó",
        back: "I danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QMWHwp2Frw",
      },
      {
        front: "cambiaron",
        back: "they changed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qBQFOoAjKy",
      },
      {
        front: "comencé",
        back: "I started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GZFbTBIGZI",
      },
      {
        front: "comenzaron",
        back: "started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z2EGxzzhTP",
      },
      {
        front: "comenzó",
        back: "started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fRPGgliJlo",
      },
      {
        front: "comprender",
        back: "grasp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "osvq4twoh4",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendieron",
        back: "they understood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cyJEeCIjtE",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendimos",
        back: "we understood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jCFp4NJK5y",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendiste",
        back: "did you understand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A1UgE0716y",
      },
      {
        front: "comprendió",
        back: "understood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d4YKoaAyB2",
      },
      {
        front: "esperamos",
        back: "we wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wLcXoxzZ4N",
      },
      {
        front: "esperaste",
        back: "did you wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CCmx4C6ynQ",
      },
      {
        front: "invitó",
        back: "invited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4Q6n0FmVEq",
      },
      {
        front: "llegaron",
        back: "they arrived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b4TC8G1Hyi",
      },
      {
        front: "llegué",
        back: "I arrived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uwEKnwEiUa",
      },
      {
        front: "llegó",
        back: "I arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FRAK0MqIwW",
      },
      {
        front: "mandamos",
        back: "we sent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QYCGMP9UsH",
      },
      {
        front: "mandaste",
        back: "did you send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zqEcC594te",
      },
      {
        front: "mandé",
        back: "What",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XjEe5xq1fj",
      },
      {
        front: "mandó",
        back: "command",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K5lnPmw20h",
      },
      {
        front: "miraste",
        back: "you looked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KveqjvrHPC",
      },
      {
        front: "morir",
        back: "To die",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HWIuxLVdDq",
      },
      {
        front: "nosotros fuimos",
        back: "we went",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RephJCbyHc",
      },
      {
        front: "novecientos",
        back: "nine hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vpa2nPLqf6",
      },
      {
        front: "ochocientos",
        back: "eight hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bVkrKI8GyR",
      },
      {
        front: "pensaron",
        back: "they thought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GCSVYR3sLN",
      },
      {
        front: "pensaste",
        back: "Thought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ndcm7N7V6C",
      },
      {
        front: "pensé",
        back: "I thought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QkoJVM86qu",
      },
      {
        front: "pensó",
        back: "thought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f0KhhbVVQ6",
      },
      {
        front: "pintaron",
        back: "they painted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jDEzbQJK3a",
      },
      {
        front: "pintaste",
        back: "you painted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XwfUSs3kwX",
      },
      {
        front: "pinté",
        back: "I painted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rg6oACzZCm",
      },
      {
        front: "practicaron",
        back: "they practiced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "frqg1jCSWh",
      },
      {
        front: "practicaste",
        back: "you practiced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hjsSIbCPAi",
      },
      {
        front: "practicó",
        back: "practical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gs2SFEDpGS",
      },
      {
        front: "practiqué",
        back: "I practiced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iMqUMbmHM7",
      },
      {
        front: "recordamos",
        back: "we remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1TlKsy2wY4",
      },
      {
        front: "recuerda",
        back: "remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I3PI0gz73z",
      },
      {
        front: "recuerdo",
        back: "memory",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iryQDsLWCI",
      },
      {
        front: "setecientos",
        back: "seven hundred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p0j9LfTqu7",
      },
      {
        front: "tú fuiste",
        back: "you went",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ygetF3Y9tz",
      },
      {
        front: "usaron",
        back: "they used",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rdTn36G2H8",
      },
      {
        front: "usaste",
        back: "you used",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PplJgxxHaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "usé",
        back: "i used",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iws1yuohLH",
      },
      {
        front: "vivieron",
        back: "they lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Sqiyt0bWrt",
      },
      {
        front: "vivió",
        back: "lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qb5FqQa1sO",
      },
      {
        front: "yo fui",
        back: "I went",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZWakyibzcV",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "6EfF0TCv7U",
    title: "Unit 49",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "alumnos",
        back: "students",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VZiJM4k862",
      },
      {
        front: "amables",
        back: "kind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9yiutiAxW6",
      },
      {
        front: "bosque",
        back: "forest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8ntwAbz2bd",
      },
      {
        front: "cereal",
        back: "cereal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BC48AGvmL6",
      },
      {
        front: "cereales",
        back: "cereals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bN1uPuNwv1",
      },
      {
        front: "comía",
        back: "I used to eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XxEBZMsMNv",
      },
      {
        front: "comías",
        back: "you ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "njoivZbDhY",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZGQleugHPr",
      },
      {
        front: "niña",
        back: "of girl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QKysIEK7Jp",
      },
      {
        front: "de niño",
        back: "as a child",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fw0x70DBp1",
      },
      {
        front: "era",
        back: "it was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kU5BY0Ft6b",
      },
      {
        front: "eras",
        back: "ages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kTreXVykxQ",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiaba",
        back: "studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aX5u1ihYwm",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiabas",
        back: "you studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3wYBsXexhx",
      },
      {
        front: "jugaba",
        back: "played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YhGAfgZTN0",
      },
      {
        front: "jugabas",
        back: "you played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "67tHSnRAPQ",
      },
      {
        front: "leía",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PKsFQwhHSq",
      },
      {
        front: "leías",
        back: "you read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BSHMbhhgSb",
      },
      {
        front: "montaba",
        back: "rode",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LSS3uZIoSX",
      },
      {
        front: "montabas",
        back: "you rode",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HD8ewV5U0X",
      },
      {
        front: "nadaba",
        back: "swam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BdanozKw84",
      },
      {
        front: "nadabas",
        back: "you swam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yicj344KEF",
      },
      {
        front: "tenías",
        back: "you had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FvSgCgQByf",
      },
      {
        front: "tranquila",
        back: "peaceful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QoM9uEg5gl",
      },
      {
        front: "tranquilas",
        back: "calm down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D9H8rIz2di",
      },
      {
        front: "tranquilo",
        back: "calm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z31KM2J1MK",
      },
      {
        front: "tranquilos",
        back: "quiet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qx6J7ngIS5",
      },
      {
        front: "vivía",
        back: "she lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N8p6O1RQeE",
      },
      {
        front: "vivías",
        back: "you lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sWVQAcGJz8",
      },
      {
        front: "vóleibol",
        back: "volleyball",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l1vk7lYb0j",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "N08DFFkwBv",
    title: "Unit 50",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pasttense21",
        back: "pasttense21",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YyXVSoBBlL",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense22",
        back: "pasttense22",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IAS60b39o3",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense23",
        back: "pasttense23",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "af9fsewDLd",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense",
        back: "pasttense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kpRr9FHT23",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ndrqsfKXyz",
    title: "Unit 50",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ayuda",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XvtVoi4py3",
      },
      {
        front: "ayude",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qb99h4dT5d",
      },
      {
        front: "disponible",
        back: "available",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AdVlQZaZ4g",
      },
      {
        front: "disponibles",
        back: "available",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EgrvYMW6PL",
      },
      {
        front: "empresa",
        back: "business",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sEtC2H9YpH",
      },
      {
        front: "escuche",
        back: "I listened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PuGlZ7jo3l",
      },
      {
        front: "espera",
        back: "wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DWVhEBu21i",
      },
      {
        front: "haga",
        back: "make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cm4I8iKVsg",
      },
      {
        front: "haz",
        back: "make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RctcGfkI6P",
      },
      {
        front: "jamás",
        back: "Never",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HkwXAsTMe3",
      },
      {
        front: "pon",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RAQBdoN9G4",
      },
      {
        front: "ponga",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8yo9BDPIte",
      },
      {
        front: "proyecto",
        back: "Project",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TZHxg5mpLA",
      },
      {
        front: "reuniones",
        back: "meetings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2tLLW7esrF",
      },
      {
        front: "reunión",
        back: "meeting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YhEnwc1gfI",
      },
      {
        front: "tampoco",
        back: "neither",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YPN8ySvvN7",
      },
      {
        front: "trabaja",
        back: "works",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aYkK4AK6A0",
      },
      {
        front: "tú haces",
        back: "you do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bFpPG0xLow",
      },
      {
        front: "tú pones",
        back: "you put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xf4WH13ws6",
      },
      {
        front: "tú vas",
        back: "you go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BJfgX43VMG",
      },
      {
        front: "usa",
        back: "uses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JYGPP8jlqT",
      },
      {
        front: "use",
        back: "use",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TL5NRhE51V",
      },
      {
        front: "usted hace",
        back: "you do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y4SqSkQ0DY",
      },
      {
        front: "usted pone",
        back: "you put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "buNHKpUsVr",
      },
      {
        front: "usted va",
        back: "you go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vE83WDS0rn",
      },
      {
        front: "vaya",
        back: "wow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6dV8zjrDrv",
      },
      {
        front: "ve",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dgSNd68are",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7fez6Hs1B1",
    title: "Unit 51",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a lo mejor",
        back: "maybe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Lpay9XTrcR",
      },
      {
        front: "aburrido",
        back: "bored",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y85F6QR07J",
      },
      {
        front: "aburridísima",
        back: "boring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ysqI432L6R",
      },
      {
        front: "aburridísimas",
        back: "very boring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bi2PPzRgKy",
      },
      {
        front: "aburridísimo",
        back: "boring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VKINLNFwvS",
      },
      {
        front: "aburridísimos",
        back: "very boring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hrl13hMzaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "bellísima",
        back: "Beautifull",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "579MMgBee6",
      },
      {
        front: "bellísimas",
        back: "beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ttqeEHfZDZ",
      },
      {
        front: "bellísimo",
        back: "beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KrCTebk4sr",
      },
      {
        front: "bellísimos",
        back: "beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yvos4T8vBs",
      },
      {
        front: "bueno",
        back: "well",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QD6hdVQHuk",
      },
      {
        front: "buenísimas",
        back: "very good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oljPsHqCBX",
      },
      {
        front: "buenísimos",
        back: "very good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qtfyH8cRL3",
      },
      {
        front: "carísima",
        back: "very expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gprsZbazs2",
      },
      {
        front: "carísimas",
        back: "very expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lgzenjL5TX",
      },
      {
        front: "carísimo",
        back: "very expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "imirwv7Hux",
      },
      {
        front: "carísimos",
        back: "very expensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gBXFYetvUA",
      },
      {
        front: "ciclismo",
        back: "cycling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rgh5BRrfqf",
      },
      {
        front: "correr",
        back: "rush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N7g7cL2dIa",
      },
      {
        front: "corrieron",
        back: "they ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M1xCB9xjTk",
      },
      {
        front: "corriste",
        back: "you ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FxQuVDebXg",
      },
      {
        front: "corrí",
        back: "i ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8U4JOchyd6",
      },
      {
        front: "cómics",
        back: "comics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l8S4VsecKU",
      },
      {
        front: "desafortunadamente",
        back: "unfortunately",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9x7YejiZvl",
      },
      {
        front: "descansos",
        back: "breaks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZwjLugnGyx",
      },
      {
        front: "divertido",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wjx7WPndFE",
      },
      {
        front: "divertidísima",
        back: "hilarious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Wh8Q3ur98",
      },
      {
        front: "divertidísimas",
        back: "hilarious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "10rSv7j8m0",
      },
      {
        front: "divertidísimo",
        back: "hilarious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NJ1OsWtQH2",
      },
      {
        front: "divertidísimos",
        back: "hilarious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4BhPpICf35",
      },
      {
        front: "espectáculo",
        back: "show",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B9GgopcZMW",
      },
      {
        front: "espectáculos",
        back: "shows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w2cR7Z5Je3",
      },
      {
        front: "excursiones",
        back: "excursions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vBkGel1aam",
      },
      {
        front: "excursión",
        back: "excursion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hZsDIynOoH",
      },
      {
        front: "grande",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JMDInXp5VZ",
      },
      {
        front: "grandísima",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MCq5lt1DwO",
      },
      {
        front: "grandísimas",
        back: "very big",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KIz4YpNAbD",
      },
      {
        front: "grandísimos",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PNLFGztvl3",
      },
      {
        front: "hermosísima",
        back: "most beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qJbmtPDApa",
      },
      {
        front: "hermosísimas",
        back: "very beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RqZE4wsQGs",
      },
      {
        front: "hermosísimo",
        back: "very beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CVXqReqKNn",
      },
      {
        front: "hermosísimos",
        back: "very beautiful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vBGtU1qdWK",
      },
      {
        front: "hip-hop",
        back: "hip hop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ynBduUaif7",
      },
      {
        front: "hobbies",
        back: "hobbies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dsnSez9jy0",
      },
      {
        front: "hobby",
        back: "hobby",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "slfOCOVwDr",
      },
      {
        front: "invita",
        back: "invites",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WwKkoEzxFs",
      },
      {
        front: "invite",
        back: "invite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mFJoPSUb68",
      },
      {
        front: "jazz",
        back: "jazz",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YRKaKupHb6",
      },
      {
        front: "lagos",
        back: "lakes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v3vPpnXL02",
      },
      {
        front: "malo",
        back: "evil",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tKy6kMzDST",
      },
      {
        front: "malísima",
        back: "lousy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n9qAigJLQk",
      },
      {
        front: "malísimo",
        back: "lousy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9jRRpYKQds",
      },
      {
        front: "malísimos",
        back: "lousy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W8y6HM68M9",
      },
      {
        front: "montar",
        back: "mount",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yeRpiZlknF",
      },
      {
        front: "montaron",
        back: "they rode",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6L4YHj6OJf",
      },
      {
        front: "monté",
        back: "mountain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o1jVLk0wmY",
      },
      {
        front: "montó",
        back: "amount",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lCyPTisffZ",
      },
      {
        front: "motocicletas",
        back: "motorcycles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7OyLKuZ8Da",
      },
      {
        front: "nadaron",
        back: "they swam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lKTC4wcnLx",
      },
      {
        front: "nadaste",
        back: "you swam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6cSaTvF4P2",
      },
      {
        front: "nadé",
        back: "swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iiWxODkxzn",
      },
      {
        front: "nadó",
        back: "I swim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "chwH4NlL9n",
      },
      {
        front: "obra de teatro",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SrsaLpjyN2",
      },
      {
        front: "qué hacemos",
        back: "what do we do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cuZlSKcfmV",
      },
      {
        front: "qué tal si",
        back: "what if",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PhnhdX7pan",
      },
      {
        front: "teatro",
        back: "theater",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xi506icXJP",
      },
      {
        front: "teatros",
        back: "theaters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rDrsla6UgK",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "aHdNYgdFJN",
    title: "Unit 52",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "año nuevo",
        back: "new Year",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lhKwQxuzNR",
      },
      {
        front: "comía",
        back: "I used to eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UBL4lenroR",
      },
      {
        front: "comíamos",
        back: "we ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "miB7eCaroS",
      },
      {
        front: "comían",
        back: "they ate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bWDgfurRb6",
      },
      {
        front: "durante",
        back: "during",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HpX6SDPiA2",
      },
      {
        front: "día de acción de gracias",
        back: "Thanksgiving Day",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j47YIlYEMq",
      },
      {
        front: "era",
        back: "it was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T1OmZ4k0hO",
      },
      {
        front: "eran",
        back: "they were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CwKhAZ4GJ5",
      },
      {
        front: "especial",
        back: "special",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GjhsYYNMJ6",
      },
      {
        front: "especiales",
        back: "specials",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lEd5SKJ1LV",
      },
      {
        front: "iglesia",
        back: "church",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VNS6vVMlmN",
      },
      {
        front: "iglesias",
        back: "churches",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A0UAM7r6Dj",
      },
      {
        front: "jugaba",
        back: "played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hr66rM5lkj",
      },
      {
        front: "jugaban",
        back: "they played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fEj4Y8cZIv",
      },
      {
        front: "jugábamos",
        back: "we played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cdpiY6diqW",
      },
      {
        front: "navidad",
        back: "Christmas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jieHElXmmw",
      },
      {
        front: "nochebuena",
        back: "good night",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O6KkiKU2Hm",
      },
      {
        front: "nochevieja",
        back: "New Years Eve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fRQmgUFYyr",
      },
      {
        front: "tarjeta",
        back: "card",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NO0Nfw3G8s",
      },
      {
        front: "tenía",
        back: "I had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cem82kHsUB",
      },
      {
        front: "teníamos",
        back: "we had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1YPKb2EgYZ",
      },
      {
        front: "tenían",
        back: "They had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mNQJklCHLa",
      },
      {
        front: "tradiciones",
        back: "traditions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "crEWDL23Z0",
      },
      {
        front: "tradición",
        back: "tradition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dtJLXefEfK",
      },
      {
        front: "visitaba",
        back: "visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MAif5aDFDK",
      },
      {
        front: "visitaban",
        back: "they visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "azqJnCBHXg",
      },
      {
        front: "vivía",
        back: "she lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rmDVqo3z1r",
      },
      {
        front: "vivíamos",
        back: "we lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OjB20wkiY7",
      },
      {
        front: "vivían",
        back: "they lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7f7mnImmcz",
      },
      {
        front: "éramos",
        back: "we were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uY9v3qHSDO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "5AAysqVwLH",
    title: "Unit 52",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aceite",
        back: "oil",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6OghKAfKPq",
      },
      {
        front: "aceites",
        back: "oils",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MEVfHmxZIX",
      },
      {
        front: "alcohol",
        back: "alcohol",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s79bKxf3WO",
      },
      {
        front: "algo más",
        back: "anything else",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rKgfPzrLtA",
      },
      {
        front: "asada",
        back: "roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "At6kxTrfW4",
      },
      {
        front: "asado",
        back: "roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Io1sqfRmd3",
      },
      {
        front: "buen provecho",
        back: "Bon Appetite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bqGl3I6gkx",
      },
      {
        front: "cenan",
        back: "have dinner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DdHD50R2d5",
      },
      {
        front: "cenaron",
        back: "they dined",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QMKFk7kLxO",
      },
      {
        front: "cenas",
        back: "dinners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qsMESVqTxk",
      },
      {
        front: "cenó",
        back: "frown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "59oK0q9Zql",
      },
      {
        front: "champanes",
        back: "champagnes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZgigUvUkqx",
      },
      {
        front: "champán",
        back: "champagne",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y1yAeb0u23",
      },
      {
        front: "chef",
        back: "Chef",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "km2Lefapm8",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinar",
        back: "cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S4RAEvkFFM",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinaste",
        back: "you cooked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ofIDNBagbL",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunamos",
        back: "we had breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L61U3MM8gC",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunan",
        back: "have breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kzCNY5qpL2",
      },
      {
        front: "desayuno",
        back: "breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4y88jlAvNm",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunó",
        back: "breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vaC1PLKYKT",
      },
      {
        front: "especial del día",
        back: "day's special",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vVThn8oJYz",
      },
      {
        front: "estupenda",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GdfG0E6wmH",
      },
      {
        front: "estupendas",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9JPoOUHpQY",
      },
      {
        front: "estupendo",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qlzwjMw4zT",
      },
      {
        front: "estupendos",
        back: "great",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wsr3XAzKZH",
      },
      {
        front: "excelente",
        back: "Excellent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NJSWs4GIPw",
      },
      {
        front: "excelentes",
        back: "excellent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4IEAqCAvBX",
      },
      {
        front: "extra",
        back: "extra",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p6s3M3RcV0",
      },
      {
        front: "extras",
        back: "Additional features",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Dq6Ftn9LGO",
      },
      {
        front: "hielo",
        back: "ice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cPSO4H7873",
      },
      {
        front: "llenas",
        back: "full",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wE835Y8qvA",
      },
      {
        front: "me puede traer",
        back: "Can you bring me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gA9c8FzTjQ",
      },
      {
        front: "panes",
        back: "breads",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AAhsTValxt",
      },
      {
        front: "pedimos",
        back: "we ask",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m3ej1tn5tZ",
      },
      {
        front: "pedir",
        back: "ask for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1q7w2jH5Pq",
      },
      {
        front: "pide",
        back: "requests",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b8Tq8vaSTM",
      },
      {
        front: "piden",
        back: "they ask",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "quRz2q4Z0Y",
      },
      {
        front: "probaron",
        back: "they tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mn9oUyIaPo",
      },
      {
        front: "saludable",
        back: "healthy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RKmT0UBL7B",
      },
      {
        front: "saludables",
        back: "healthy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mh3PLinSSO",
      },
      {
        front: "servimos",
        back: "we serve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P97Es34hVU",
      },
      {
        front: "servir",
        back: "to serve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XJIzDy5ZcU",
      },
      {
        front: "sirve",
        back: "it serves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OdvmOg9TEo",
      },
      {
        front: "sirves",
        back: "you serve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qjHhbxL67X",
      },
      {
        front: "sirvo",
        back: "I serve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hmQSHA5s0b",
      },
      {
        front: "traemos",
        back: "we bring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ysfFZVYdMh",
      },
      {
        front: "vegetariana",
        back: "vegetarian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "viqiGjFGlj",
      },
      {
        front: "vegetariano",
        back: "vegetarian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f7uJhWbElj",
      },
      {
        front: "vegetarianos",
        back: "vegetarians",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nlZ1ZLXGp2",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "5VylbE9sDS",
    title: "Unit 52",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acompañar",
        back: "accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lfmWbzVBez",
      },
      {
        front: "acompañas",
        back: "you accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3Q4WE11zmt",
      },
      {
        front: "acompaño",
        back: "accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X2Nd5mjE0t",
      },
      {
        front: "acompañó",
        back: "accompanied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qsi6rusAHG",
      },
      {
        front: "baila",
        back: "dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5dq5ZCeHZH",
      },
      {
        front: "bar",
        back: "Pub",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9LAZevEsSw",
      },
      {
        front: "bares",
        back: "pubs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZAXHRuUhXt",
      },
      {
        front: "centro",
        back: "center",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CfPpnI39qV",
      },
      {
        front: "centros",
        back: "centers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LNvRG9SSOj",
      },
      {
        front: "conversamos",
        back: "we talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qwAgePPebA",
      },
      {
        front: "conversar",
        back: "discuss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TDzKrkXSfj",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaron",
        back: "they talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r7ZPotnH5v",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaste",
        back: "you talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u3sUx8zeKh",
      },
      {
        front: "converso",
        back: "convert",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bZi9EgIESI",
      },
      {
        front: "conversé",
        back: "I talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rB3pfG0pO9",
      },
      {
        front: "conversó",
        back: "convert",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FgnMJeIZJv",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s2MSByWqNS",
      },
      {
        front: "le va",
        back: "how are you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "muc9lPT712",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo te va",
        back: "how's it going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ypD2WtYEqC",
      },
      {
        front: "donde",
        back: "where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OpyGp3jS76",
      },
      {
        front: "invitaciones",
        back: "invitations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7Q6SDSla05",
      },
      {
        front: "invitación",
        back: "invitation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KjTCODD59W",
      },
      {
        front: "llamamos",
        back: "we call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z3nwIXZHmv",
      },
      {
        front: "llamar",
        back: "to call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QIG149EcSm",
      },
      {
        front: "llamaron",
        back: "they called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "13sERwcEmb",
      },
      {
        front: "llamaste",
        back: "called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AWSoNdoHkk",
      },
      {
        front: "llamé",
        back: "I called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1kM3ZqRA8S",
      },
      {
        front: "llamó",
        back: "I call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FPsTNsfiYf",
      },
      {
        front: "llega",
        back: "arrives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0QOixR9mew",
      },
      {
        front: "llegue",
        back: "I arrived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "phBRWL1k9Z",
      },
      {
        front: "medianoche",
        back: "midnight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ahQ6Qp91sq",
      },
      {
        front: "mediodía",
        back: "midday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vDCV44ngQ3",
      },
      {
        front: "mira",
        back: "sight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hz67YsDQms",
      },
      {
        front: "oye",
        back: "hears",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pAFX59E5F7",
      },
      {
        front: "parece",
        back: "It seems",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5BhveGIhp2",
      },
      {
        front: "parrilla",
        back: "grill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tYftgVZMLR",
      },
      {
        front: "patio",
        back: "courtyard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PNgVtJQUfw",
      },
      {
        front: "patios",
        back: "patios",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aJuHZUoEQF",
      },
      {
        front: "pena",
        back: "pain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NAXqI3SYVa",
      },
      {
        front: "quiénes",
        back: "Who is it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "miCM5ZBimG",
      },
      {
        front: "qué le parece",
        back: "what do you think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dWtuzPCebO",
      },
      {
        front: "qué te parece",
        back: "how about",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fPuc7kH9Wl",
      },
      {
        front: "sorpresa",
        back: "surprise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8cAZiZhMnR",
      },
      {
        front: "ven",
        back: "come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YlVQDnxmbX",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "QJWHj3Xho6",
    title: "Unit 53",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abuelito",
        back: "Grandpa",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TMF7TaDnC3",
      },
      {
        front: "aventura",
        back: "adventure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dXqqebt3em",
      },
      {
        front: "aventuras",
        back: "adventure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tAwPeFAwb3",
      },
      {
        front: "campamento",
        back: "camp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zGZHuukc6I",
      },
      {
        front: "campamentos",
        back: "camps",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TDb79UXdUr",
      },
      {
        front: "compañera de cuarto",
        back: "roommate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bxDBAehfDW",
      },
      {
        front: "compañeras de clase",
        back: "classmates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LxS3ambyb8",
      },
      {
        front: "compañeras de cuarto",
        back: "Roommates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EWuEbHpE4w",
      },
      {
        front: "compañero de clase",
        back: "classmate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fPmRjRP9MO",
      },
      {
        front: "compañero de cuarto",
        back: "Roommate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xuDJY58tP3",
      },
      {
        front: "compañeros de clase",
        back: "classmates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lqkzWnrDWi",
      },
      {
        front: "compañeros de cuarto",
        back: "roommates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sXvaL1QlMQ",
      },
      {
        front: "cuentos",
        back: "stories",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xdneZpxOpW",
      },
      {
        front: "dije",
        back: "I said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vMclrAHycl",
      },
      {
        front: "dijiste",
        back: "said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NYAQZ2x2aM",
      },
      {
        front: "dijo",
        back: "said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wnTBUkf33z",
      },
      {
        front: "hace",
        back: "make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1HqdRDhIJK",
      },
      {
        front: "juego de mesa",
        back: "board game",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GuT5mC5IsX",
      },
      {
        front: "juegos de mesa",
        back: "table games",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "95HfvO4avn",
      },
      {
        front: "llevamos",
        back: "we carry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q95zEgkgJ9",
      },
      {
        front: "llevó",
        back: "I have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Kg0WgMmE0",
      },
      {
        front: "me acordé",
        back: "I remembered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T2Fi8XNHzm",
      },
      {
        front: "momento",
        back: "moment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1OGKfoGoev",
      },
      {
        front: "momentos",
        back: "moments",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H1cnaA9Yny",
      },
      {
        front: "nos acordamos",
        back: "we remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1C7DMsrUK0",
      },
      {
        front: "nota",
        back: "note",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CcuzQPEFZE",
      },
      {
        front: "notas",
        back: "notes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9UINCuromi",
      },
      {
        front: "premio",
        back: "prize",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E6JnHDt3bT",
      },
      {
        front: "premios",
        back: "awards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q95pWYEwlD",
      },
      {
        front: "prima",
        back: "cousin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kAK7CACpQr",
      },
      {
        front: "primas",
        back: "cousins",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wpczYHVzT0",
      },
      {
        front: "primo",
        back: "cousin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wuWqvxQvW9",
      },
      {
        front: "primos",
        back: "cousins",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I9BYNHRS2p",
      },
      {
        front: "recibe",
        back: "receives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZRQuewyQCm",
      },
      {
        front: "recibimos",
        back: "We received",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5BY0Cpxghy",
      },
      {
        front: "recibir",
        back: "to receive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FHtAz70vSr",
      },
      {
        front: "recibió",
        back: "He received",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ooLBEKgqHF",
      },
      {
        front: "recuerdo",
        back: "memory",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fIR9qffILo",
      },
      {
        front: "se acordaron",
        back: "they agreed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "epLJNHpusD",
      },
      {
        front: "se acordó",
        back: "he remembered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Sp3CcUkiFC",
      },
      {
        front: "te acordaste",
        back: "did you remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2jiQlgr0Vm",
      },
      {
        front: "traje",
        back: "costume",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T1TTtoCvcU",
      },
      {
        front: "trajiste",
        back: "you brought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jspWyIuEXh",
      },
      {
        front: "trajo",
        back: "He brought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9QaEvPUmZs",
      },
      {
        front: "tuve",
        back: "I had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zr4cfm8yZJ",
      },
      {
        front: "tuviste",
        back: "You saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FJohTDiQ6P",
      },
      {
        front: "tuvo",
        back: "had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mhXATcGpO6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "K8iA1whrFr",
    title: "Unit 54",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "alfombras",
        back: "carpets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DdlrUpuecN",
      },
      {
        front: "apaga",
        back: "turns off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ofBlCZBqCo",
      },
      {
        front: "apagada",
        back: "off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6bQQhjPOHA",
      },
      {
        front: "apagadas",
        back: "turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OJtnRZV0ZV",
      },
      {
        front: "apagado",
        back: "switched off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b27XIrRftg",
      },
      {
        front: "apagados",
        back: "turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tyFr0P5oyz",
      },
      {
        front: "apagar",
        back: "to turn off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TjradLybf3",
      },
      {
        front: "apagas",
        back: "you turn off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dtMSpaGP47",
      },
      {
        front: "apagaste",
        back: "you turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A9BJABVK2c",
      },
      {
        front: "apagó",
        back: "turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OVc5Ji0Ybq",
      },
      {
        front: "cafetera",
        back: "coffee maker",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KPsY7HGDpI",
      },
      {
        front: "creo que debería",
        back: "I think I should",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WGwHbnnQUm",
      },
      {
        front: "creo que deberías",
        back: "I think you should",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NO64rerWjy",
      },
      {
        front: "cómoda",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4m6NOC95ck",
      },
      {
        front: "cómodas",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EfeR4Ju3V0",
      },
      {
        front: "dormida",
        back: "asleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZOUtQcukXp",
      },
      {
        front: "dormidas",
        back: "asleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "90uM1l6WRg",
      },
      {
        front: "dormido",
        back: "asleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sdZ6fhVu5q",
      },
      {
        front: "dormidos",
        back: "asleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iu1aD2Swou",
      },
      {
        front: "dormir",
        back: "to sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C0qW21JIXf",
      },
      {
        front: "encendemos",
        back: "we turn on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G54GziVIzS",
      },
      {
        front: "encender",
        back: "light",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W446kzL4fU",
      },
      {
        front: "encendida",
        back: "turned on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QjAUASyFV1",
      },
      {
        front: "encendidas",
        back: "lit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "crU0F44V69",
      },
      {
        front: "encendido",
        back: "switched on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OM28TaTdNq",
      },
      {
        front: "encendidos",
        back: "turned on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xYa0ehl37j",
      },
      {
        front: "encendieron",
        back: "they turned on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOx3pkTdVm",
      },
      {
        front: "encendí",
        back: "I turned on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AkW5M0W5sr",
      },
      {
        front: "espejo",
        back: "mirror",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wkI9Tbwn3m",
      },
      {
        front: "espejos",
        back: "Mirrors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rgsDqW1xa6",
      },
      {
        front: "estufas",
        back: "stoves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O8oRVOKgPa",
      },
      {
        front: "lavadora",
        back: "washer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ooGlXuAUcw",
      },
      {
        front: "lavadoras",
        back: "washing machines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6omZaIe1NM",
      },
      {
        front: "luces",
        back: "lights",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PRyQvwleNG",
      },
      {
        front: "luz",
        back: "light",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K2wrwdtNQg",
      },
      {
        front: "lámpara",
        back: "lamp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q5to4ODh2p",
      },
      {
        front: "lámparas",
        back: "lamps",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V3fk4mgoMQ",
      },
      {
        front: "muebles",
        back: "furniture",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CZ8wG7xQ4x",
      },
      {
        front: "perder",
        back: "to lose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VjXkWLPmYf",
      },
      {
        front: "perdida",
        back: "loss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mt2Y6RNwoo",
      },
      {
        front: "perdidas",
        back: "losses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ONvLXvmZon",
      },
      {
        front: "perdido",
        back: "lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QIYjJUblfr",
      },
      {
        front: "pintada",
        back: "graffiti",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5AVE2A2iru",
      },
      {
        front: "pintadas",
        back: "painted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TSLvBwvO6h",
      },
      {
        front: "pintado",
        back: "painted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LXYRcX7BCq",
      },
      {
        front: "pintados",
        back: "painted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0Skrbw5YEL",
      },
      {
        front: "pintar",
        back: "to paint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "osF8TSTPX2",
      },
      {
        front: "portátil",
        back: "portable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C5tWNjgtg9",
      },
      {
        front: "portátiles",
        back: "laptops",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "98nFGcSNu9",
      },
      {
        front: "sillones",
        back: "armchairs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hyzezoMtBR",
      },
      {
        front: "sillón",
        back: "armchair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xdnCQOaD2V",
      },
      {
        front: "sofá",
        back: "sofa",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1DyhzdS07K",
      },
      {
        front: "televisor",
        back: "television",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9QSYit3KUx",
      },
      {
        front: "televisores",
        back: "televisions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sJ1NebGQ6F",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "hSqDWRtNWB",
    title: "Unit 54",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "actividad",
        back: "exercise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cimANhBkAg",
      },
      {
        front: "actividades",
        back: "activities",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FMOkEh7O8e",
      },
      {
        front: "cigarrillos",
        back: "cigarettes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7HjTcWk4BM",
      },
      {
        front: "cita",
        back: "appointment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k26AvHTmaR",
      },
      {
        front: "cuello",
        back: "neck",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EBkExr0aGx",
      },
      {
        front: "cuellos",
        back: "necks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rpF5g1Mdzk",
      },
      {
        front: "cuida",
        back: "takes care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CbdTp4yS0q",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidan",
        back: "take care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "282KuN63bC",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidar",
        back: "look after",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b4zxscRX61",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidas",
        back: "take care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wb661jRSIm",
      },
      {
        front: "debería",
        back: "ought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zlbpd0tQ5Z",
      },
      {
        front: "deberías",
        back: "you should",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gTiJbs81v9",
      },
      {
        front: "dedo",
        back: "finger",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "66XjRsDRSi",
      },
      {
        front: "dedos",
        back: "fingers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I6q3etI6Yd",
      },
      {
        front: "descansar",
        back: "to rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MIsJZ7QXio",
      },
      {
        front: "descansaron",
        back: "rested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "35J15hR5BC",
      },
      {
        front: "descansas",
        back: "you rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ik2g5R8pVC",
      },
      {
        front: "descansaste",
        back: "you rested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hg0orKKiNo",
      },
      {
        front: "descanso",
        back: "break",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c4D3BgfVpB",
      },
      {
        front: "descansó",
        back: "break",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NfoCQ4nAjV",
      },
      {
        front: "doler",
        back: "to hurt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Xs1azRAkX",
      },
      {
        front: "dolor",
        back: "pain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B4Gk2AYiL6",
      },
      {
        front: "dr.",
        back: "dr.",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wi7hE0D0Cb",
      },
      {
        front: "dra.",
        back: "dr.",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YbDvj2ERdW",
      },
      {
        front: "duele",
        back: "hurts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LakWcbB7bV",
      },
      {
        front: "duelen",
        back: "they hurt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wXuF8CdIWQ",
      },
      {
        front: "ejercicio",
        back: "exercise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jaiM1nOLqG",
      },
      {
        front: "enfermeras",
        back: "nurses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xZq5uWBfQO",
      },
      {
        front: "enfermeros",
        back: "nurses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B9HpdYPBhG",
      },
      {
        front: "espalda",
        back: "back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9g8eA5NOLK",
      },
      {
        front: "espaldas",
        back: "backs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jRjfvocuqK",
      },
      {
        front: "estómago",
        back: "stomach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xk4Gg8fwDk",
      },
      {
        front: "estómagos",
        back: "stomachs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "twQUOhf2Yd",
      },
      {
        front: "hay que",
        back: "must",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CPoWeCPFfw",
      },
      {
        front: "jabones",
        back: "soaps",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "quXbySwE7T",
      },
      {
        front: "jabón",
        back: "soap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bejWWTIMry",
      },
      {
        front: "me cepillé",
        back: "I brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2rfJfU9ups",
      },
      {
        front: "mover",
        back: "move",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Sa8w9oVmP",
      },
      {
        front: "nos cepillamos",
        back: "we brush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yo09tLBxPv",
      },
      {
        front: "pálida",
        back: "pale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tN8YMIK7yQ",
      },
      {
        front: "pálido",
        back: "Pale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3nACDhHHOr",
      },
      {
        front: "salud",
        back: "Health",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9Zp6jBeEW9",
      },
      {
        front: "se cepillaron",
        back: "they brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MC9IJgBfX0",
      },
      {
        front: "se cepilló",
        back: "brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PYkjor1OFb",
      },
      {
        front: "te cepillaste",
        back: "you brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w5C7lYzsD9",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "3F1SB6AK5U",
    title: "Unit 55",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "anuncio",
        back: "advertisement",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hnlxDx7rKa",
      },
      {
        front: "archivo",
        back: "File",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xrs2bIegyn",
      },
      {
        front: "canal",
        back: "channel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NFHnND7mEO",
      },
      {
        front: "canales",
        back: "channels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JGZhf8g7cV",
      },
      {
        front: "dijeron",
        back: "they said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ABXIffN5TP",
      },
      {
        front: "dijimos",
        back: "we said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "beq8AO6yUX",
      },
      {
        front: "documento",
        back: "document",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S7cQmQXPoP",
      },
      {
        front: "documentos",
        back: "documents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xENC5ZClMH",
      },
      {
        front: "entiendes",
        back: "you understand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4XOgzMITpl",
      },
      {
        front: "enviar",
        back: "send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hh1zBburxc",
      },
      {
        front: "fábricas",
        back: "factories",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CiPiQDxxXh",
      },
      {
        front: "información",
        back: "information",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UmURA2Vt8D",
      },
      {
        front: "ingeniera",
        back: "engineer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yl8oIlN2Cf",
      },
      {
        front: "ingenieras",
        back: "engineers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lj0MeuABQX",
      },
      {
        front: "ingeniero",
        back: "engineer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ME8zyICXbe",
      },
      {
        front: "ingenieros",
        back: "engineers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ez7oAXuVGW",
      },
      {
        front: "internet",
        back: "Internet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zKWbRYO4n3",
      },
      {
        front: "leí",
        back: "I read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HnJ2ncpotR",
      },
      {
        front: "mensajes",
        back: "posts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LBEyqbFBjs",
      },
      {
        front: "máquina",
        back: "machine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sxpKj93wV6",
      },
      {
        front: "máquinas",
        back: "machines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VcSeQmiZlS",
      },
      {
        front: "noticia",
        back: "News",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PyQ0ceNMT7",
      },
      {
        front: "noticias",
        back: "news",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cv4dA9R7sL",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntaron",
        back: "they asked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wDlHEt2ibv",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntaste",
        back: "Asked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4inpkVHq8N",
      },
      {
        front: "pregunté",
        back: "I asked for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5sX2RMJrwQ",
      },
      {
        front: "preguntó",
        back: "I ask",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M8iR0H3Ek8",
      },
      {
        front: "que",
        back: "what",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cI2WAt0tgC",
      },
      {
        front: "revista",
        back: "magazine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MKYLfQPROw",
      },
      {
        front: "revistas",
        back: "journals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GnxJ1tdi2h",
      },
      {
        front: "semanal",
        back: "weekly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lHRU1cX3E3",
      },
      {
        front: "sitios",
        back: "sites",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QUEoB8jZdP",
      },
      {
        front: "trajeron",
        back: "they brought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I1t5zo9qot",
      },
      {
        front: "trajimos",
        back: "we brought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fuilJeWdim",
      },
      {
        front: "tuvieron",
        back: "they had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vebEGtKRsL",
      },
      {
        front: "tuvimos",
        back: "we had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WzpGtxnZyQ",
      },
      {
        front: "verdad",
        back: "TRUE",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s8d7SOR5zD",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jiyvaJvZu5",
    title: "Unit 56",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pasttense31",
        back: "pasttense31",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tE5wEUIoQ3",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense32",
        back: "pasttense32",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hqs8nAOtwb",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense33",
        back: "pasttense33",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NGsGhrIJkk",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense",
        back: "pasttense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ht9juPvimX",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "KAdECrDIAH",
    title: "Unit 56",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "agricultor",
        back: "farmer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "75xHVz0Iqk",
      },
      {
        front: "agricultores",
        back: "farmers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UA8jNU70gb",
      },
      {
        front: "conejo",
        back: "rabbit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "erwnKDfnAD",
      },
      {
        front: "conejos",
        back: "rabbits",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X0DHML4ErZ",
      },
      {
        front: "dinosaurio",
        back: "dinosaur",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eN4nLOGpQE",
      },
      {
        front: "dinosaurios",
        back: "dinosaurs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oQY8LQU4cS",
      },
      {
        front: "el ajedrez",
        back: "the chess",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7LbTDh5yzt",
      },
      {
        front: "el baloncesto",
        back: "basketball",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a3RhdwBJdl",
      },
      {
        front: "el ciclismo",
        back: "cycling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C6m7QW4iRJ",
      },
      {
        front: "el español",
        back: "the Spanish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J0eDxe0gh0",
      },
      {
        front: "el fútbol",
        back: "football",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g0r7TYnQqa",
      },
      {
        front: "el inglés",
        back: "English",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3FVi0YJ2Zw",
      },
      {
        front: "elefante",
        back: "elephant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NIoqgND12a",
      },
      {
        front: "elefantes",
        back: "elephants",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mnacd8i3jU",
      },
      {
        front: "fuerte",
        back: "strong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c40Wv0I9Ia",
      },
      {
        front: "fuertes",
        back: "powerful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f32MU44pCO",
      },
      {
        front: "gramática",
        back: "grammar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6sLpFmWOo0",
      },
      {
        front: "las frutas",
        back: "the fruits",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "anBKo0EoM4",
      },
      {
        front: "los deportes",
        back: "sports",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zamq7CCDjb",
      },
      {
        front: "los gatos",
        back: "the cats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fWD7SVBXtB",
      },
      {
        front: "los lunes",
        back: "on Monday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2BK79N4S0C",
      },
      {
        front: "los maestros",
        back: "teachers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nJbeRz7L9W",
      },
      {
        front: "los médicos",
        back: "the doctors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "10BigZF2pb",
      },
      {
        front: "los padres",
        back: "parents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9MsXzKH0uI",
      },
      {
        front: "los",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v8GLLndQV0",
      },
      {
        front: "perros",
        back: "dogs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vWVXv9pTGE",
      },
      {
        front: "oso",
        back: "bear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qssEVNC5UF",
      },
      {
        front: "peligroso",
        back: "dangerous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uupL7Zr5cO",
      },
      {
        front: "pesadas",
        back: "heavy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WcpZ08Le8u",
      },
      {
        front: "pesados",
        back: "heavy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kUOZbztHrZ",
      },
      {
        front: "rápido",
        back: "Quick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Ov9EzM8uH",
      },
      {
        front: "útil",
        back: "Useful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0VzQIU0JXW",
      },
      {
        front: "útiles",
        back: "tools",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2BC5dvz4Cb",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "LbdYR0eQ82",
    title: "Unit 57",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "almorzar",
        back: "to have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vyWyQQHNjv",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzaron",
        back: "they had lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yS579sXpVN",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzaste",
        back: "did you have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DNnaQhnp4Z",
      },
      {
        front: "aprobamos",
        back: "we approve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "20Hk0nIDeE",
      },
      {
        front: "aprobar",
        back: "Approve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PVgPkFpdcr",
      },
      {
        front: "aprobaron",
        back: "approved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IeO94IVy4n",
      },
      {
        front: "aprobaste",
        back: "you passed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "teS6rr5quF",
      },
      {
        front: "aprobé",
        back: "I approved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jzrl159fk0",
      },
      {
        front: "balonmano",
        back: "handball",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iwYlREA1oI",
      },
      {
        front: "carreras",
        back: "careers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m8ZJcNuwpG",
      },
      {
        front: "copa",
        back: "Cup",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0YIACE871E",
      },
      {
        front: "corredora",
        back: "runner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vlphLLaKzt",
      },
      {
        front: "corredoras",
        back: "runners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "57LZZph0Rg",
      },
      {
        front: "corredores",
        back: "runners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2bUyNrAxxF",
      },
      {
        front: "cuaderno",
        back: "notebook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yjvxTHC07b",
      },
      {
        front: "dormí",
        back: "I slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OyAo1EqS4q",
      },
      {
        front: "entendimos",
        back: "we understood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fxNo7u8kL9",
      },
      {
        front: "entendiste",
        back: "you understood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Uq37mnd8aP",
      },
      {
        front: "equipo",
        back: "equipment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zt7HECF5bd",
      },
      {
        front: "equipos",
        back: "teams",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VzU58ukZuZ",
      },
      {
        front: "gana",
        back: "win",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n9gKSD6Rmq",
      },
      {
        front: "ganar",
        back: "win",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MNLbL4E9ue",
      },
      {
        front: "ganas",
        back: "desire",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P1blNVInlz",
      },
      {
        front: "ganaste",
        back: "Won",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5EeHOoQoZP",
      },
      {
        front: "historia",
        back: "history",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ojM6ew3dtt",
      },
      {
        front: "kilómetro",
        back: "kilometer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jvDPDNXSBZ",
      },
      {
        front: "kilómetros",
        back: "kilometres",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ky7giZbldR",
      },
      {
        front: "lavamos",
        back: "we wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pJdWAONQ5u",
      },
      {
        front: "lavar",
        back: "wash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zenzg8vJE5",
      },
      {
        front: "lavaste",
        back: "you washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iJNuBWugzN",
      },
      {
        front: "lavé",
        back: "washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pUf3p82B64",
      },
      {
        front: "leyeron",
        back: "they read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u5nX4vF96f",
      },
      {
        front: "leyó",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G6pvonOZ3v",
      },
      {
        front: "leímos",
        back: "we read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4GXjXzJqew",
      },
      {
        front: "leíste",
        back: "did you read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gtgVJF9kTz",
      },
      {
        front: "libro de texto",
        back: "Text book",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "peguxB6xgg",
      },
      {
        front: "libros de texto",
        back: "textbooks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FhoLqjCbTb",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiamos",
        back: "we clean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uiMOeci8pA",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiar",
        back: "clean up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u79H9LXc3p",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiaste",
        back: "you cleaned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EEvcnqk3sS",
      },
      {
        front: "limpié",
        back: "I cleaned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HoRkE06Nfe",
      },
      {
        front: "química",
        back: "chemistry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oxkIvYXD5x",
      },
      {
        front: "tazón",
        back: "mug",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YRZxZDDl7p",
      },
      {
        front: "tocamos",
        back: "we touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LrmYsrXXea",
      },
      {
        front: "tocar",
        back: "touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YmsWyFBzdF",
      },
      {
        front: "tocó",
        back: "touched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nJgT9Hlt3z",
      },
      {
        front: "tomamos",
        back: "we take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dydd2WaDl4",
      },
      {
        front: "tomaron",
        back: "they took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mDvPIImQda",
      },
      {
        front: "tomaste",
        back: "do you drink tea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TuVIGLwnub",
      },
      {
        front: "tomé",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VKgxF05wV7",
      },
      {
        front: "tomó",
        back: "I take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YVFRsPtgrq",
      },
      {
        front: "varias",
        back: "several",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z8nICfTaKA",
      },
      {
        front: "varios",
        back: "several",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fxddGenPyJ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "igpMJHJEkP",
    title: "Unit 58",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "artista",
        back: "artist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ICyL4dHJZJ",
      },
      {
        front: "artistas",
        back: "artists",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PPQYFLAf4Y",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudaba",
        back: "helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e7ziRDO2P3",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudaban",
        back: "they helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AUUq6OYJTH",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudabas",
        back: "you helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h0GtRT4sXB",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudábamos",
        back: "we helped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kKRfpZUUQj",
      },
      {
        front: "bailaba",
        back: "danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u0sKINrSXj",
      },
      {
        front: "bailaban",
        back: "they danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N6o06PhlbW",
      },
      {
        front: "bailabas",
        back: "you danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "827dLYWBxO",
      },
      {
        front: "bailar",
        back: "to dance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VG1PHiF6nD",
      },
      {
        front: "bailarina",
        back: "dancer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D6JWGW6DwF",
      },
      {
        front: "bailarinas",
        back: "ballerinas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HdhFw0IMfb",
      },
      {
        front: "bailarín",
        back: "dancer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZyEajKaxZe",
      },
      {
        front: "bailábamos",
        back: "we danced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lNSvMDz7u0",
      },
      {
        front: "campo",
        back: "countryside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rQcZ2lNTeS",
      },
      {
        front: "campos",
        back: "fields",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QYEhNw6FYG",
      },
      {
        front: "castillo",
        back: "castle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UN2ORuZoVy",
      },
      {
        front: "cenaba",
        back: "dined",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ml4ra4Srws",
      },
      {
        front: "cenaban",
        back: "dined",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZHJGmk7mC9",
      },
      {
        front: "cenábamos",
        back: "we had dinner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bwN64nsBRz",
      },
      {
        front: "guerra",
        back: "war",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I8HsSTObxa",
      },
      {
        front: "guerras",
        back: "wars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gN5Tvfe2fT",
      },
      {
        front: "hablaba",
        back: "she spoke",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LLAfZCCbyp",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar",
        back: "to talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IbXOGsnndE",
      },
      {
        front: "hablábamos",
        back: "we talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Iaa0UkBlr8",
      },
      {
        front: "había una vez",
        back: "once Upon a time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kCoRzKwBsW",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta",
        back: "until",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IXOXgFsbJ2",
      },
      {
        front: "intenta",
        back: "try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OikMYhu4rC",
      },
      {
        front: "intentaba",
        back: "tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PTyH3Balg6",
      },
      {
        front: "intentaban",
        back: "they were trying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aOmiwocuff",
      },
      {
        front: "intentabas",
        back: "you were trying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V9Ydy7woPw",
      },
      {
        front: "intentar",
        back: "attempt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aadj2C0mgK",
      },
      {
        front: "intentábamos",
        back: "we tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MudjX8bWlo",
      },
      {
        front: "lentamente",
        back: "slowly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rHDvI8Bztj",
      },
      {
        front: "lloraba",
        back: "cried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hKrGnlSjaV",
      },
      {
        front: "lloraban",
        back: "they cried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9nnfno2mRr",
      },
      {
        front: "llorabas",
        back: "you cried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LvscTA7NND",
      },
      {
        front: "llorar",
        back: "cry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fwLQ9qSEL0",
      },
      {
        front: "mar",
        back: "sea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1FpPTAXPTD",
      },
      {
        front: "mares",
        back: "seas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ICD0SSgPo",
      },
      {
        front: "montaña",
        back: "mountain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vZefq9N5RY",
      },
      {
        front: "montañas",
        back: "mountains",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4KQsZW00zA",
      },
      {
        front: "oveja",
        back: "sheep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w0fooCYbsX",
      },
      {
        front: "ovejas",
        back: "sheep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v2sAuB76wz",
      },
      {
        front: "reina",
        back: "Queen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4zHo8R9x2c",
      },
      {
        front: "reinas",
        back: "queens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vR6ORqD4c2",
      },
      {
        front: "rey",
        back: "king",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vrCtPrnLbS",
      },
      {
        front: "reyes",
        back: "Kings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hHtCGFJICC",
      },
      {
        front: "rezaba",
        back: "prayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5GHgubVtR3",
      },
      {
        front: "rezaban",
        back: "they prayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mZ2xEBCflW",
      },
      {
        front: "rezabas",
        back: "you prayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B3pQhyYcm7",
      },
      {
        front: "rezar",
        back: "pray",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kUiGARlNH3",
      },
      {
        front: "rezábamos",
        back: "we prayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ks0VCGlVuV",
      },
      {
        front: "salones",
        back: "halls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tbm6O6HiqI",
      },
      {
        front: "salón",
        back: "living room",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x3aNaZOEQz",
      },
      {
        front: "sola",
        back: "alone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uFJQBjmKJ4",
      },
      {
        front: "solas",
        back: "alone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nFIJtJT9o0",
      },
      {
        front: "solo",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e6gkqXLeJi",
      },
      {
        front: "solos",
        back: "alone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fMmVeXkmx9",
      },
      {
        front: "sortija",
        back: "ring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PkwABxBfwp",
      },
      {
        front: "sortijas",
        back: "rings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MfictDpKVl",
      },
      {
        front: "tocaba",
        back: "touched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7l0gOOYE9f",
      },
      {
        front: "tocaban",
        back: "they touched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SEM6OAocdd",
      },
      {
        front: "tocabas",
        back: "you touched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Udt6GpsU4E",
      },
      {
        front: "tocar",
        back: "touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y3THpbKI1u",
      },
      {
        front: "tocábamos",
        back: "we played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YNfEDYFgNj",
      },
      {
        front: "violines",
        back: "violins",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hXJxloh5CR",
      },
      {
        front: "violín",
        back: "fiddle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WctXqKfc5Z",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "xrPlDvKIVQ",
    title: "Unit 58",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acompañaba",
        back: "accompanied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t5Wx2ef7o2",
      },
      {
        front: "acompañaban",
        back: "accompanied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QNZzRjTdgm",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzaban",
        back: "they had lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fJ5zBgOUfD",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzabas",
        back: "you had lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3eVkT6gPuV",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzar",
        back: "to have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TtQG5kqoxz",
      },
      {
        front: "almorzábamos",
        back: "we had lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4VoYGIfNiQ",
      },
      {
        front: "caminaba",
        back: "walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E1kcqLzvpp",
      },
      {
        front: "caminaban",
        back: "they walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tRNHP3wxS5",
      },
      {
        front: "caminábamos",
        back: "we were walking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oXhLAPFAYS",
      },
      {
        front: "compraba",
        back: "bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MMPDsXZQmx",
      },
      {
        front: "compraban",
        back: "they bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eHawwTc4fl",
      },
      {
        front: "comprabas",
        back: "you bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G3xhHYWdWp",
      },
      {
        front: "comprábamos",
        back: "we bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1rryuGQHoU",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaba",
        back: "talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JpXXzY5t7r",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaban",
        back: "they talked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ryFlWaZNEe",
      },
      {
        front: "correr",
        back: "rush",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FrlaEhorn1",
      },
      {
        front: "corría",
        back: "ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "75Czz54i1p",
      },
      {
        front: "corríamos",
        back: "we ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B5beYqvpZ4",
      },
      {
        front: "corrían",
        back: "they ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x1qKU50lMA",
      },
      {
        front: "corrías",
        back: "you ran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YAcBqY4dq1",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidaba",
        back: "cared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "stMQIKZaWX",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidabas",
        back: "you took care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ziT6BT1U26",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidar",
        back: "look after",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ov7FGERQ6S",
      },
      {
        front: "descansaba",
        back: "rested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5T5RgVX3Y8",
      },
      {
        front: "descansaban",
        back: "rested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "haqsf6PGun",
      },
      {
        front: "descansábamos",
        back: "we rested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T6XkJXdDPD",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujos animados",
        back: "Cartoon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZJXbYHtfmw",
      },
      {
        front: "dormir",
        back: "to sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xrm7WaKY2F",
      },
      {
        front: "dormíamos",
        back: "we slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DHipAbApou",
      },
      {
        front: "dormías",
        back: "you were sleeping",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "61Ev3GVxVL",
      },
      {
        front: "dulces",
        back: "sweets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ARauXhDI9v",
      },
      {
        front: "escribía",
        back: "wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jp20KK8yr0",
      },
      {
        front: "escribían",
        back: "were writing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gr1B27soEN",
      },
      {
        front: "escribías",
        back: "you wrote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kfaLjnDjeq",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiaban",
        back: "they studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KoUOlIy9gv",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiar",
        back: "to study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l8BqpGToPm",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiábamos",
        back: "we studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6whirEHGtb",
      },
      {
        front: "ganar",
        back: "win",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AnIfyYyo7I",
      },
      {
        front: "geografía",
        back: "geography",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "efp6RWbecd",
      },
      {
        front: "gustaba",
        back: "liked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rQwlB6fs3Q",
      },
      {
        front: "gustaban",
        back: "they liked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N343GeUQLS",
      },
      {
        front: "gustar",
        back: "like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ku1WeTbt9M",
      },
      {
        front: "iba",
        back: "I was going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MX80iyLL7p",
      },
      {
        front: "iban",
        back: "were going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PWRPRPg8kQ",
      },
      {
        front: "ibas",
        back: "you were going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EnclbPuXUC",
      },
      {
        front: "lavaba",
        back: "washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zPy1ulNh7h",
      },
      {
        front: "lavábamos",
        back: "we washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8CqsEDtA08",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiaban",
        back: "they cleaned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bU55ik2ZN6",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiabas",
        back: "you cleaned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VE3GUSVUHU",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiábamos",
        back: "we cleaned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aALluHNqOC",
      },
      {
        front: "mecánica",
        back: "mechanics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "92EYmXZHnb",
      },
      {
        front: "mecánicas",
        back: "mechanical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6IaGqD750F",
      },
      {
        front: "mecánico",
        back: "mechanic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GMyKuzcwW7",
      },
      {
        front: "mecánicos",
        back: "mechanics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X7XQ3Wrku7",
      },
      {
        front: "patio de juego",
        back: "play ground",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rEdU2C99zt",
      },
      {
        front: "patios de juego",
        back: "playgrounds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iSsmWFGxmj",
      },
      {
        front: "recibir",
        back: "to receive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m2c8sBqHE2",
      },
      {
        front: "recibía",
        back: "received",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4rpboeTt9l",
      },
      {
        front: "recibían",
        back: "received",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7W7M1GplQf",
      },
      {
        front: "refresco",
        back: "soft drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KpKXbAS1Nm",
      },
      {
        front: "refrescos",
        back: "refreshments",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tXeoBMXqRi",
      },
      {
        front: "tomaban",
        back: "they drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8WDhMjaoiM",
      },
      {
        front: "tomabas",
        back: "you drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eKZNDvE6vG",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r8jd0hiPX1",
      },
      {
        front: "tomábamos",
        back: "we drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3gWRi9QKkl",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajabas",
        back: "you worked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g9lGuTdw71",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajando",
        back: "working",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IoJiTGR0z4",
      },
      {
        front: "íbamos",
        back: "we were going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zv1HvfKPw1",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "UPROZsJwl4",
    title: "Unit 59",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "agradables",
        back: "nice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KTKzvNFFIQ",
      },
      {
        front: "asientos",
        back: "seating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TGQbjRiQlz",
      },
      {
        front: "bienvenida",
        back: "welcome",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hwbyscve89",
      },
      {
        front: "bienvenido",
        back: "Welcome",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JHTugegxTY",
      },
      {
        front: "capital",
        back: "capital",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UKBMHX8A0o",
      },
      {
        front: "capitales",
        back: "capitals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hQ44jelgU1",
      },
      {
        front: "catedral",
        back: "Cathedral",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IIE8n3EuHE",
      },
      {
        front: "coche",
        back: "car",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xHll2dPjrX",
      },
      {
        front: "coches",
        back: "cars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4uazcFWte3",
      },
      {
        front: "confortable",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wWAFNEaV6g",
      },
      {
        front: "confortables",
        back: "comfortable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AJwU62YB3n",
      },
      {
        front: "en todas partes",
        back: "everywhere",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0RHioPK2ip",
      },
      {
        front: "equipaje",
        back: "Baggage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3bpo3GBfox",
      },
      {
        front: "estadio",
        back: "stadium",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h6DwTKMaLG",
      },
      {
        front: "estadios",
        back: "stadiums",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vvnI2S1Jlx",
      },
      {
        front: "helicóptero",
        back: "helicopter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ox2iJ99S1q",
      },
      {
        front: "idea",
        back: "idea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U88FRWrwoA",
      },
      {
        front: "ideas",
        back: "ideas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rj9PGb6NiT",
      },
      {
        front: "identificación",
        back: "ID",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AqmUHWKAQk",
      },
      {
        front: "internacional",
        back: "international",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hPr4md5PIh",
      },
      {
        front: "internacionales",
        back: "international",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "im5xyair76",
      },
      {
        front: "isla",
        back: "island",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6QgqH6tjIc",
      },
      {
        front: "islas",
        back: "islands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mxq8dcDAzC",
      },
      {
        front: "planea",
        back: "plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bh6L4tyWcp",
      },
      {
        front: "planeamos",
        back: "we plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R4qVCtsECx",
      },
      {
        front: "planean",
        back: "plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9tFV3DaTL0",
      },
      {
        front: "planear",
        back: "to plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FwIEufd4Gc",
      },
      {
        front: "planeas",
        back: "you plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ifjz2OL7qP",
      },
      {
        front: "planeo",
        back: "glide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jPD8GsTOX3",
      },
      {
        front: "regresamos",
        back: "we came back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k6TyTuUud8",
      },
      {
        front: "regresan",
        back: "return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3RDo2oP43u",
      },
      {
        front: "regresaron",
        back: "they returned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CJylKgZ8Ro",
      },
      {
        front: "regresaste",
        back: "You come back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RklauScm5S",
      },
      {
        front: "regreso",
        back: "he came back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8grqlKGRpI",
      },
      {
        front: "reserva",
        back: "booking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E68cBnxKbR",
      },
      {
        front: "reservamos",
        back: "we reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yyYaMEO89u",
      },
      {
        front: "reservan",
        back: "reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TQ8j8l4UOS",
      },
      {
        front: "reservar",
        back: "Reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wml5M1oqkg",
      },
      {
        front: "reservaron",
        back: "reserved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cy54D01akn",
      },
      {
        front: "reservas",
        back: "Bookings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gr0qmHwXPH",
      },
      {
        front: "reservaste",
        back: "you booked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kTzoDX7w2Z",
      },
      {
        front: "reservo",
        back: "reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qAkHXBmVQx",
      },
      {
        front: "reservó",
        back: "booked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2DovJZqlBM",
      },
      {
        front: "servicios",
        back: "services",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2BKBKHb8Lv",
      },
      {
        front: "tranvía",
        back: "trolley car",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "teskfjZ132",
      },
      {
        front: "turista",
        back: "tourist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jQPvsM22TZ",
      },
      {
        front: "vuelos",
        back: "flights",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zNhIiA3iTl",
      },
      {
        front: "ópera",
        back: "Opera",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RVgQYi4BNi",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "8La4E1nMR6",
    title: "Unit 60",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "asaba",
        back: "roasted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DyDseskgnD",
      },
      {
        front: "asabas",
        back: "asabas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QYPSeW5r4E",
      },
      {
        front: "cafetería",
        back: "coffee shop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rKaJhDDisi",
      },
      {
        front: "cafeterías",
        back: "coffee shops",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jv3VgiFkF8",
      },
      {
        front: "carretera",
        back: "road",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WtyYQanfCr",
      },
      {
        front: "ciencias",
        back: "sciences",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CMGMtoSjS2",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinaba",
        back: "cooked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZpeyuFNPF6",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunaba",
        back: "had breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rXcVVmhTa2",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunaban",
        back: "they had breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cYx1ArmEv7",
      },
      {
        front: "desayunábamos",
        back: "we had breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UQMN9SYBqD",
      },
      {
        front: "diario",
        back: "diary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8yMbM0J9zK",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujaba",
        back: "drew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FEXHHdpqM0",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujaban",
        back: "they drew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rXMGrmsa6d",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujabas",
        back: "you drew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R5upixzu0s",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujábamos",
        back: "we were drawing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FPt6ehjKXe",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutaba",
        back: "enjoyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o7Ndcongzv",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutar",
        back: "to enjoy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AZjf512X2l",
      },
      {
        front: "disfrutábamos",
        back: "we enjoyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vmFJyBYKN8",
      },
      {
        front: "entra",
        back: "enters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T4I1SPGUVd",
      },
      {
        front: "entrar",
        back: "get in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sDuMnqeOEP",
      },
      {
        front: "entras",
        back: "you enter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SBcKGMg3Mg",
      },
      {
        front: "entró",
        back: "I enter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BxvIe6pr89",
      },
      {
        front: "limonada",
        back: "lemonade",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "buFEc7jViZ",
      },
      {
        front: "manejaba",
        back: "was driving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2JS2EU2ieq",
      },
      {
        front: "manejaban",
        back: "they drove",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dzPVMKJiJQ",
      },
      {
        front: "manejar",
        back: "handle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BsWk4SMb1y",
      },
      {
        front: "mercado",
        back: "market",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F2Ti7pw1xF",
      },
      {
        front: "mercados",
        back: "markets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M9HZUx4rYR",
      },
      {
        front: "miraba",
        back: "looked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6HHpM302lN",
      },
      {
        front: "miraban",
        back: "they looked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3HKlNNL0SX",
      },
      {
        front: "monas",
        back: "cute",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VVabv4aCei",
      },
      {
        front: "mono",
        back: "bow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Lff3Gd6qKf",
      },
      {
        front: "monos",
        back: "monkeys",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iKa1bEg3wY",
      },
      {
        front: "océano",
        back: "ocean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lGyRiRM6sI",
      },
      {
        front: "pescaba",
        back: "fished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HX7Pt6u3Ee",
      },
      {
        front: "pescaban",
        back: "they fished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yp75vOgQ7I",
      },
      {
        front: "pescar",
        back: "to fish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k4oQumfBY0",
      },
      {
        front: "rata",
        back: "rat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A7mK4XOctm",
      },
      {
        front: "ratas",
        back: "rats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lARoWgh1xZ",
      },
      {
        front: "reparaba",
        back: "repaired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uwPeM9G9pt",
      },
      {
        front: "reparaban",
        back: "repaired",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HXIjnqXM1v",
      },
      {
        front: "reparar",
        back: "fix",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XBwMuI1GE8",
      },
      {
        front: "reparó",
        back: "repair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qA3P5Zq3GE",
      },
      {
        front: "rugby",
        back: "rugby",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MdHYCbNfLf",
      },
      {
        front: "tambor",
        back: "drum",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hW3huIj9pB",
      },
      {
        front: "tambores",
        back: "drums",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I2GK2hd5iu",
      },
      {
        front: "tía",
        back: "aunt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VUXUZLLy42",
      },
      {
        front: "tías",
        back: "aunts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bZtx6z5cCo",
      },
      {
        front: "tíos",
        back: "uncles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MlIzCZ7bY2",
      },
      {
        front: "usaba",
        back: "used",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mlUHHIN2eg",
      },
      {
        front: "video",
        back: "video",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BNNNeaoZYA",
      },
      {
        front: "videos",
        back: "videos",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aSteABy7lL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "pRBHjhtHVR",
    title: "Unit 60",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cajones",
        back: "drawers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T7UXCaYVIY",
      },
      {
        front: "cajón",
        back: "drawer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IzUCee0KlL",
      },
      {
        front: "casada",
        back: "married",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ya9IGfzIPy",
      },
      {
        front: "casado",
        back: "married",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vwKVfrrRls",
      },
      {
        front: "enfadadas",
        back: "angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qH7g6ddQ5a",
      },
      {
        front: "enfadado",
        back: "angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zTfYwKyt7X",
      },
      {
        front: "enfadados",
        back: "angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r1yUHtRHsG",
      },
      {
        front: "estaba",
        back: "was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7cefY9tUc0",
      },
      {
        front: "estaban",
        back: "They were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cEOFcskvtP",
      },
      {
        front: "estabas",
        back: "you were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mqAuvIENOC",
      },
      {
        front: "estar",
        back: "to be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uQJHwth1KM",
      },
      {
        front: "estábamos",
        back: "we were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9kE11E4PJj",
      },
      {
        front: "excepto",
        back: "except",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TYQ26ARr7f",
      },
      {
        front: "fresca",
        back: "fresh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dJYEqRRkxg",
      },
      {
        front: "frescas",
        back: "fresh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "51RxfWHXZC",
      },
      {
        front: "frescos",
        back: "fresh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zoiSxJWCFx",
      },
      {
        front: "gafas de sol",
        back: "Sunglasses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S1Q3PZfDci",
      },
      {
        front: "interesadas",
        back: "interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aMZ5gTfK3l",
      },
      {
        front: "interesado",
        back: "interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Klu8TGhHXd",
      },
      {
        front: "interesados",
        back: "interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "706qBl9ds1",
      },
      {
        front: "invitada",
        back: "guest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sTnONq3ANA",
      },
      {
        front: "invitado",
        back: "guest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZEHqHC8Qua",
      },
      {
        front: "invitados",
        back: "guests",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mOSLtKnnNc",
      },
      {
        front: "loco",
        back: "crazy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5NSgRvNum8",
      },
      {
        front: "locos",
        back: "crazy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4UeglVFCKj",
      },
      {
        front: "mangos",
        back: "mangoes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L0nVPYnQvH",
      },
      {
        front: "mojada",
        back: "wet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KRSeb43pNg",
      },
      {
        front: "mojadas",
        back: "wet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VKB37gMon7",
      },
      {
        front: "mojado",
        back: "wet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SjketvoKJ0",
      },
      {
        front: "mojados",
        back: "wet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KKtgZKBsg9",
      },
      {
        front: "motor",
        back: "engine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D9a1wbkZvT",
      },
      {
        front: "motores",
        back: "engines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EjaUC9NTii",
      },
      {
        front: "nietas",
        back: "granddaughters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0kfLgSvuOQ",
      },
      {
        front: "nieto",
        back: "grandchild",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d5iNnDahmO",
      },
      {
        front: "paraguas",
        back: "umbrella",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hY0NGHQayi",
      },
      {
        front: "probablemente",
        back: "probably",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pdlXpSk9wL",
      },
      {
        front: "romper",
        back: "break",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FfqhSw9Q6a",
      },
      {
        front: "rompieron",
        back: "broke up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P7sN5slgEK",
      },
      {
        front: "rompiste",
        back: "you broke",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l9NC1yHUDX",
      },
      {
        front: "rompí",
        back: "I broke up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xzj8m5cHlH",
      },
      {
        front: "rota",
        back: "broken",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CT7GZ5lhYR",
      },
      {
        front: "rotas",
        back: "broken",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SLlfyJv9BX",
      },
      {
        front: "roto",
        back: "broken",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nRDeZsnFJ5",
      },
      {
        front: "satisfecha",
        back: "satisfied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AvoYfWc4cW",
      },
      {
        front: "satisfechas",
        back: "satisfied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R8IZvch6wp",
      },
      {
        front: "satisfecho",
        back: "satisfied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J84A8I1z6P",
      },
      {
        front: "satisfechos",
        back: "satisfied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eYWrEarU4r",
      },
      {
        front: "secas",
        back: "dry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q1PD3zp3gm",
      },
      {
        front: "secos",
        back: "dry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0S8pCK6r1N",
      },
      {
        front: "sin duda",
        back: "undoubtedly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KLjtY8H1VZ",
      },
      {
        front: "soleada",
        back: "sunny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7JDYyViVzg",
      },
      {
        front: "soleadas",
        back: "sunny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qxojZHKhJ3",
      },
      {
        front: "soleados",
        back: "sunny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mutGeP04jy",
      },
      {
        front: "traje de baño",
        back: "Swimwear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PoUhXDyFSO",
      },
      {
        front: "trajes de baño",
        back: "swimsuits",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zEQFG6rYhN",
      },
      {
        front: "vecina",
        back: "neighbor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KRJyKDfNC0",
      },
      {
        front: "vecinas",
        back: "neighbors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TO6RQgoDoy",
      },
      {
        front: "vecinos",
        back: "neighbours",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YPusJajSHA",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "rjDkMIT9JE",
    title: "Unit 61",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adentro",
        back: "inside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rIvEOZ2SNX",
      },
      {
        front: "afuera",
        back: "outside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y6cGpLYHwc",
      },
      {
        front: "carpeta",
        back: "file",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bgTXwSOZna",
      },
      {
        front: "carpetas",
        back: "folders",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bm4D8pGjZj",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinera",
        back: "cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IZo2izTh4O",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinero",
        back: "Cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hLER6jzYKa",
      },
      {
        front: "cocineros",
        back: "chefs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O8koMEZiVC",
      },
      {
        front: "compañía",
        back: "company",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sQvsJkPd77",
      },
      {
        front: "compañías",
        back: "companies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QiCe8OrPgp",
      },
      {
        front: "completando",
        back: "completing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RHW8N2s42x",
      },
      {
        front: "completaron",
        back: "completed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7orZJfWIrp",
      },
      {
        front: "completaste",
        back: "you completed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nMHxkXP9pi",
      },
      {
        front: "diciendo",
        back: "saying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a56NnBqGet",
      },
      {
        front: "director",
        back: "director",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1m31DH3K9G",
      },
      {
        front: "directoras",
        back: "directors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6STscfoInS",
      },
      {
        front: "durmiendo",
        back: "sleeping",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YEHMm9ojtW",
      },
      {
        front: "edificio",
        back: "building",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s9TXW4SSna",
      },
      {
        front: "edificios",
        back: "buildings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eByqVlcWHr",
      },
      {
        front: "empresaria",
        back: "businesswoman",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wIU2zCrvv1",
      },
      {
        front: "empresarias",
        back: "businesswomen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GOKV21fqxs",
      },
      {
        front: "empresario",
        back: "entrepreneur",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IrzfgPPYXg",
      },
      {
        front: "empresarios",
        back: "businessmen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eZsx02zLVw",
      },
      {
        front: "gerente",
        back: "manager",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jGBH3ogJjO",
      },
      {
        front: "gerentes",
        back: "managers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TIF8NCo05n",
      },
      {
        front: "horario",
        back: "schedule",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l1ZrVEkWLo",
      },
      {
        front: "llamada",
        back: "call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OV4xffJJSa",
      },
      {
        front: "llamadas",
        back: "calls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "48IxdsfGnF",
      },
      {
        front: "muriendo",
        back: "dying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pLNkTavXKh",
      },
      {
        front: "oyendo",
        back: "hearing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vrEoOS1ny3",
      },
      {
        front: "pedir",
        back: "ask for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WvNONgdRY9",
      },
      {
        front: "pidiendo",
        back: "asking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ryU3irBaO",
      },
      {
        front: "pintor",
        back: "painter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LG5MTyJj9j",
      },
      {
        front: "pintora",
        back: "painter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vamJGvI6Ya",
      },
      {
        front: "pintoras",
        back: "female painters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8h5G7WvhT0",
      },
      {
        front: "pintores",
        back: "painters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "swbt37ubsN",
      },
      {
        front: "presidenta",
        back: "Chairwoman",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qJ4QIUtRep",
      },
      {
        front: "presidentas",
        back: "female presidents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kx69xMe8Dw",
      },
      {
        front: "presidente",
        back: "President",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QqA6BN6laW",
      },
      {
        front: "presidentes",
        back: "presidents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GlUj3FztwE",
      },
      {
        front: "programa",
        back: "Program",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FQU1YMsGJj",
      },
      {
        front: "programas",
        back: "programs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iShbXMe0sr",
      },
      {
        front: "repetir",
        back: "to repeat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KaQtrswESr",
      },
      {
        front: "repitiendo",
        back: "repeating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8zbSlIxC7w",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajadora",
        back: "worker",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1mRoUXmRNj",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajadoras",
        back: "workers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XXzo5vxZxi",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajadores",
        back: "workers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qlPVO7CryM",
      },
      {
        front: "trayendo",
        back: "bringing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J6eodMOD1Q",
      },
      {
        front: "yendo",
        back: "going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwSOGyt6dc",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "G83xsZFwtk",
    title: "Unit 62",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pasttense41",
        back: "pasttense41",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1rWj3aUASB",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense42",
        back: "pasttense42",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6etTPbGhqg",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense43",
        back: "pasttense43",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RLUZ6mn1S4",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense",
        back: "pasttense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "druw6TeVPI",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "PTStsENdZ1",
    title: "Unit 62",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "amaban",
        back: "they loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g5PLRIh7Hh",
      },
      {
        front: "amar",
        back: "to love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3pCqg1l1lC",
      },
      {
        front: "collar",
        back: "necklace",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c98eeacpW1",
      },
      {
        front: "conocer",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qu8gRDA6cT",
      },
      {
        front: "conocía",
        back: "knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qzH9XLZcBI",
      },
      {
        front: "conocían",
        back: "they knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fe2ecgHDUl",
      },
      {
        front: "corazones",
        back: "hearts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YpXhGppVka",
      },
      {
        front: "corazón",
        back: "heart",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WjUhY81lAd",
      },
      {
        front: "cree",
        back: "believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HBHpJi3Kp9",
      },
      {
        front: "creemos",
        back: "we believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OxAmvgzZPk",
      },
      {
        front: "creen",
        back: "believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lbSPusVJ0o",
      },
      {
        front: "creer",
        back: "to believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HReE9KbDvg",
      },
      {
        front: "creo",
        back: "I believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B8BCYLdj9N",
      },
      {
        front: "creía",
        back: "believed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mKSIHdbDBi",
      },
      {
        front: "creíamos",
        back: "we believed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qaFSjUYuf9",
      },
      {
        front: "creías",
        back: "did you believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uXHgZhIVdJ",
      },
      {
        front: "encantaba",
        back: "loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ox4n4NLleE",
      },
      {
        front: "encantaban",
        back: "they loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MaDRe8Y92H",
      },
      {
        front: "estar de acuerdo",
        back: "agree",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MjYzACv5UY",
      },
      {
        front: "interesaba",
        back: "interested",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v3hAIggJ4G",
      },
      {
        front: "interesarse",
        back: "interest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iqJUiJ6hd8",
      },
      {
        front: "leones",
        back: "lions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w4ceSRrqfi",
      },
      {
        front: "león",
        back: "Lion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "co2vvL459k",
      },
      {
        front: "magia",
        back: "Magic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "78rerEzFxJ",
      },
      {
        front: "me llamaba",
        back: "called me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e2KbIDCeF1",
      },
      {
        front: "naturaleza",
        back: "nature",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eAV8n7oNvo",
      },
      {
        front: "naturalezas",
        back: "natures",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n1cQXpopmt",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitaba",
        back: "needed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xGOUX0lhWg",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitaban",
        back: "they needed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sv1v3zHpDm",
      },
      {
        front: "odiaba",
        back: "I hated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aDQMfVDA4l",
      },
      {
        front: "odiaban",
        back: "they hated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XDYzKEbpxH",
      },
      {
        front: "oro",
        back: "Prayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tmg9pO48E4",
      },
      {
        front: "pato",
        back: "duck",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ssYv5itT75",
      },
      {
        front: "patos",
        back: "Ducks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I9oUFg0ZXj",
      },
      {
        front: "preferir",
        back: "to prefer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iVmFMHcjL8",
      },
      {
        front: "prefería",
        back: "preferred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2VSajsw22H",
      },
      {
        front: "preferían",
        back: "they preferred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XnPyuGPyD5",
      },
      {
        front: "preferías",
        back: "you preferred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yrOfBuWtjd",
      },
      {
        front: "propia",
        back: "own",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kFiN71OuiJ",
      },
      {
        front: "propias",
        back: "own",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2w7VFwyuLw",
      },
      {
        front: "propio",
        back: "own",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TlxMWKtyds",
      },
      {
        front: "propios",
        back: "own",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "shrVBrur9J",
      },
      {
        front: "puente",
        back: "bridge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tp3Gk76HfB",
      },
      {
        front: "puentes",
        back: "bridges",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zFWv6m4xGP",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oJuZG5Mn6w",
      },
      {
        front: "quería",
        back: "wanted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TZAZUvIcwi",
      },
      {
        front: "se llamaba",
        back: "it was called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0d6QbURc0t",
      },
      {
        front: "se llamaban",
        back: "They were called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i98086jw7O",
      },
      {
        front: "serpiente",
        back: "snake",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IbeD44GYLV",
      },
      {
        front: "serpientes",
        back: "snakes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h4SyrVpQ45",
      },
      {
        front: "silvestres",
        back: "wild",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BXFg2LD1v7",
      },
      {
        front: "simple",
        back: "simple",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "39rzT2XRRQ",
      },
      {
        front: "visitantes",
        back: "visitors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VhVpAkmlCb",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "u1tzGHAab9",
    title: "Unit 63",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "colinas",
        back: "hills",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pdVu61Lrqh",
      },
      {
        front: "conocida",
        back: "known",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hhtVGm4ZIm",
      },
      {
        front: "conocido",
        back: "acquaintance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Omb39XJFtv",
      },
      {
        front: "conocidos",
        back: "acquaintances",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PQ2DuCytIy",
      },
      {
        front: "de acuerdo",
        back: "ok",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A05slTyOB5",
      },
      {
        front: "decidir",
        back: "to decide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8oyZkxlC3M",
      },
      {
        front: "decidiste",
        back: "you decided",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S98YLfI48z",
      },
      {
        front: "decidió",
        back: "He decided",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OJt5u5hk8o",
      },
      {
        front: "decidí",
        back: "I decided",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IFvWZMpKIN",
      },
      {
        front: "miles",
        back: "Thousands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B6RQNvIWJA",
      },
      {
        front: "ocurrieron",
        back: "occurred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wxEFZWCDjF",
      },
      {
        front: "ocurrir",
        back: "to occure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hmwBAzhXf1",
      },
      {
        front: "ocurrió",
        back: "It occurred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "khRefNwJNe",
      },
      {
        front: "por fin",
        back: "finally",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "obgDxU3ler",
      },
      {
        front: "preparamos",
        back: "we prepare",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LoRPUW8YL2",
      },
      {
        front: "preparar",
        back: "set up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VXKCkXdY0w",
      },
      {
        front: "prepararon",
        back: "prepared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8opEGT3XIC",
      },
      {
        front: "preparaste",
        back: "you prepared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Pwg2GGpRnX",
      },
      {
        front: "preparé",
        back: "I prepared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SuEB4QErD5",
      },
      {
        front: "preparó",
        back: "prepared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SOrEYWpSH9",
      },
      {
        front: "principio",
        back: "principle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KJXqtKriTX",
      },
      {
        front: "principios",
        back: "beginning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bES3zUZaUW",
      },
      {
        front: "pude",
        back: "could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bgg2Tqa8Zt",
      },
      {
        front: "pudiste",
        back: "you could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B0P3XYAHL1",
      },
      {
        front: "pudo",
        back: "could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VoBNH8hrsF",
      },
      {
        front: "puse",
        back: "I put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Br1k5AxuMf",
      },
      {
        front: "pusiste",
        back: "you put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KXlD1ckaQZ",
      },
      {
        front: "puso",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rOOVGa7kim",
      },
      {
        front: "razones",
        back: "reasons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "38YUcM59Fy",
      },
      {
        front: "razón",
        back: "reason",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8KOXoAIxwd",
      },
      {
        front: "siglo",
        back: "century",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wxECIbYIRB",
      },
      {
        front: "supe",
        back: "I knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l7Stljrtno",
      },
      {
        front: "supiste",
        back: "did you know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v6D607LN2I",
      },
      {
        front: "supo",
        back: "he knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VBDZv5jXKy",
      },
      {
        front: "veces",
        back: "times",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NcTYpwLzNK",
      },
      {
        front: "vez",
        back: "time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5sqhU7OUk7",
      },
      {
        front: "área",
        back: "area",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LwYszB0Q3j",
      },
      {
        front: "áreas",
        back: "areas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6Qj8VuFAZi",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "PAecxA34Rp",
    title: "Unit 64",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrirla",
        back: "open it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hr8X1xV1qk",
      },
      {
        front: "abrirlo",
        back: "open it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8J9y8SxgOm",
      },
      {
        front: "abrirlos",
        back: "open them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4eDc84Ci8h",
      },
      {
        front: "beberla",
        back: "drink it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qfRyAgGYG2",
      },
      {
        front: "beberlas",
        back: "drink them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gPzUPyD24P",
      },
      {
        front: "beberlo",
        back: "drink it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ME3z7qehX8",
      },
      {
        front: "beberlos",
        back: "drink them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZdhU1IsrKp",
      },
      {
        front: "cebolla",
        back: "onion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "izSnus2jhn",
      },
      {
        front: "cebollas",
        back: "onions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sp0hpDWvuw",
      },
      {
        front: "champiñones",
        back: "mushrooms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7tLSc6frCo",
      },
      {
        front: "comerla",
        back: "eat it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u8kpvqzLiB",
      },
      {
        front: "comerlas",
        back: "eat them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U7JZQJqpXL",
      },
      {
        front: "comerlo",
        back: "eat it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ORsUyhcj4q",
      },
      {
        front: "comerlos",
        back: "eat them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L25W14C619",
      },
      {
        front: "comprar",
        back: "purchase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "txKkJhAGP1",
      },
      {
        front: "comprarlas",
        back: "buy them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U98NXmI2tQ",
      },
      {
        front: "comprarlo",
        back: "buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wvTXqWWZWu",
      },
      {
        front: "comprarlos",
        back: "buy them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MLSQKs9O1n",
      },
      {
        front: "en oferta",
        back: "in offer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Dbj2Z3qxAC",
      },
      {
        front: "gastar",
        back: "to spend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vGqMKaoJlT",
      },
      {
        front: "jamones",
        back: "hams",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IWvDB3HmC8",
      },
      {
        front: "jamón",
        back: "ham",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QI5iX0EUn8",
      },
      {
        front: "kilogramo",
        back: "kilogram",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mZdMnipefc",
      },
      {
        front: "lata",
        back: "can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "deWTVPahI5",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarlas",
        back: "wash them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eekcDoXsgO",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarlo",
        back: "wash it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qUPNrhUGoi",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarlos",
        back: "wash them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PGJe9guQtf",
      },
      {
        front: "limón",
        back: "lemon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GwN5OAIWBH",
      },
      {
        front: "lista",
        back: "list",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gAmTJQz1sk",
      },
      {
        front: "listas",
        back: "ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XPNvlnFBcj",
      },
      {
        front: "litro",
        back: "liter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sX8N5uXHO9",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitar",
        back: "need",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HtZrcdyZ3W",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitarla",
        back: "need her",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wBgGS5C02n",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitarlas",
        back: "need them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wjZqPStTLW",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitarlo",
        back: "need it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Defx5qilFo",
      },
      {
        front: "necesitarlos",
        back: "need them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8nYs1EnetW",
      },
      {
        front: "pedirla",
        back: "ask for it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IZO3hNqWef",
      },
      {
        front: "pedirlas",
        back: "ask for them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tlItP6u7xi",
      },
      {
        front: "pedirlo",
        back: "asking for it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mntjI6o4im",
      },
      {
        front: "pera",
        back: "pear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yhHRSLTm9O",
      },
      {
        front: "peras",
        back: "pears",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1KJumURAgh",
      },
      {
        front: "pimienta",
        back: "Pepper",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RW7DftYssJ",
      },
      {
        front: "prepararla",
        back: "prepare it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gXLiMlfyuJ",
      },
      {
        front: "prepararlo",
        back: "set it up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pWfEbmTUKt",
      },
      {
        front: "prepararlos",
        back: "prepare them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FSDrRScseM",
      },
      {
        front: "variedad",
        back: "variety",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oqzyrBuemC",
      },
      {
        front: "variedades",
        back: "varieties",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aJXfFi9Jw0",
      },
      {
        front: "y",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ffpn2ZEgmq",
      },
      {
        front: "medio",
        back: "and a half",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EulKjCjaJH",
      },
      {
        front: "yogur",
        back: "yogurt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "srUgafbVuf",
      },
      {
        front: "yogures",
        back: "yogurts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Py5WwhgYJB",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "aJyll2yob9",
    title: "Unit 64",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "almorcé",
        back: "I lunched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JX6u3578lu",
      },
      {
        front: "bufanda",
        back: "scarf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AgeQZtfDuW",
      },
      {
        front: "bufandas",
        back: "scarves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "suisJYVIZE",
      },
      {
        front: "calcetines",
        back: "socks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yj5YAt2wBG",
      },
      {
        front: "calcetín",
        back: "sock",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QTCWJvTddy",
      },
      {
        front: "corbata",
        back: "tie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g6EGbnmfII",
      },
      {
        front: "corbatas",
        back: "ties",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aConnCBSUz",
      },
      {
        front: "diaria",
        back: "daily",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ikb8G74G3d",
      },
      {
        front: "diarias",
        back: "daily",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yx48z9ibAi",
      },
      {
        front: "dormiste",
        back: "you slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dwJJPvdAjl",
      },
      {
        front: "durmieron",
        back: "they slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FIdgUftt8H",
      },
      {
        front: "durmió",
        back: "slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XIByG87HYS",
      },
      {
        front: "maquillaje",
        back: "make-up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TfVZ2mt3xR",
      },
      {
        front: "me acosté",
        back: "I went to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sHDj9bjVyS",
      },
      {
        front: "me desperté",
        back: "I woke up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ne8ZMWHINK",
      },
      {
        front: "me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gCgsifzHUX",
      },
      {
        front: "duché",
        back: "I showered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HqQd3uYwjc",
      },
      {
        front: "me lavé",
        back: "I washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PA2MrrKjLW",
      },
      {
        front: "me probé",
        back: "i tried myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qm6C5YTn35",
      },
      {
        front: "me quedé",
        back: "I stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AnVYT3wEyA",
      },
      {
        front: "me reuní",
        back: "I met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jr7tCh4onf",
      },
      {
        front: "mermelada",
        back: "jam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OF7ZgEMZST",
      },
      {
        front: "nos acostamos",
        back: "we go to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3d2J1Aa9yW",
      },
      {
        front: "nos despertamos",
        back: "we wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6a3ObStJ7n",
      },
      {
        front: "nos duchamos",
        back: "we showered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xH7E5RFsOP",
      },
      {
        front: "nos preocupamos",
        back: "we care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DLuyVdyqsK",
      },
      {
        front: "nos probamos",
        back: "we tried ourselves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eduOwEcNuD",
      },
      {
        front: "nos quedamos",
        back: "we stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yPPIg2ugBO",
      },
      {
        front: "nos reunimos",
        back: "we met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xfRH1GiKSw",
      },
      {
        front: "pasta",
        back: "pasta",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VkUN9TKrc3",
      },
      {
        front: "peine",
        back: "comb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "57Qw74eity",
      },
      {
        front: "perfecta",
        back: "perfect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iMN61SQvtD",
      },
      {
        front: "perfecto",
        back: "perfect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hvJwe2fHzn",
      },
      {
        front: "perfectos",
        back: "perfect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VHdQMsBjjq",
      },
      {
        front: "se acostaron",
        back: "they went to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kHlFGE9Cit",
      },
      {
        front: "se acostó",
        back: "went to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AtPyPzTIpD",
      },
      {
        front: "se despertaron",
        back: "they woke up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KnetY3u0A2",
      },
      {
        front: "se despertó",
        back: "he woke up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HmuT5AhkYL",
      },
      {
        front: "se ducharon",
        back: "they showered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ql4IrERWQs",
      },
      {
        front: "se duchó",
        back: "took a shower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rYDwsM3tid",
      },
      {
        front: "se lavaron",
        back: "They were washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "owDgi1zKU8",
      },
      {
        front: "se lavó",
        back: "He washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5vzlLFoYP3",
      },
      {
        front: "se preocuparon",
        back: "they worried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iomjPzMIw7",
      },
      {
        front: "se preocupó",
        back: "he worried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mytNFnoxDF",
      },
      {
        front: "se probaron",
        back: "they tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x5aljrTD85",
      },
      {
        front: "se probó",
        back: "it was tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YAeTY3Hsga",
      },
      {
        front: "se quedaron",
        back: "they remained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LlPZ5cAyox",
      },
      {
        front: "se quedó",
        back: "he stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vZ3deCA0kL",
      },
      {
        front: "se reunieron",
        back: "They met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KNw7KOMvm4",
      },
      {
        front: "se reunió",
        back: "met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yajdkp3LxI",
      },
      {
        front: "suaves",
        back: "soft",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e6VpAJFTRa",
      },
      {
        front: "suéter",
        back: "sweater",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S3xCpmt2Vc",
      },
      {
        front: "suéters",
        back: "sweaters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jAb122hLZx",
      },
      {
        front: "te acostaste",
        back: "you went to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "etwu4W1THf",
      },
      {
        front: "te despertaste",
        back: "you woke up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T2SHm9uWdz",
      },
      {
        front: "te duchaste",
        back: "you showered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ymlguUvXm7",
      },
      {
        front: "te lavaste",
        back: "you washed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tNpER03COq",
      },
      {
        front: "te probaste",
        back: "you tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uDaosnOFRQ",
      },
      {
        front: "te quedaste",
        back: "you stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ivUy9ifz9h",
      },
      {
        front: "te reuniste",
        back: "you met",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NITllNbg00",
      },
      {
        front: "tostada",
        back: "toast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iMQnlcSRJH",
      },
      {
        front: "tostadas",
        back: "toasts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T9N1R50t2o",
      },
      {
        front: "traje",
        back: "costume",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hrAdzqPMXT",
      },
      {
        front: "trajes",
        back: "suits",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xEhk2MCo32",
      },
      {
        front: "uniforme",
        back: "uniform",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4YCGJ7AgUM",
      },
      {
        front: "uniformes",
        back: "uniforms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JVsxLRF53V",
      },
      {
        front: "vestirse",
        back: "get dressed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FL8gsEZquY",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "VKUj8Fkc3P",
    title: "Unit 65",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "avanzada",
        back: "advanced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gUcpCf8zoZ",
      },
      {
        front: "avanzado",
        back: "advanced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PtQHfbFf1B",
      },
      {
        front: "calendario",
        back: "calendar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "otk8PczuZo",
      },
      {
        front: "calendarios",
        back: "calendars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DcpCOfQCZa",
      },
      {
        front: "claramente",
        back: "clearly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5SLCpVnB0Y",
      },
      {
        front: "compañera",
        back: "partner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G9rwwfVZG1",
      },
      {
        front: "compañeras",
        back: "companions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0yqr2HnteW",
      },
      {
        front: "compañero",
        back: "companion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ajzDZhUpag",
      },
      {
        front: "compañeros",
        back: "classmates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hjroFRYEHi",
      },
      {
        front: "consejo",
        back: "tip",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nyQVvbTrg2",
      },
      {
        front: "consejos",
        back: "tips",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y6GMt96sxS",
      },
      {
        front: "dar",
        back: "give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ia6mJ1SoGi",
      },
      {
        front: "darle",
        back: "give him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aE35Bz9cF1",
      },
      {
        front: "darme",
        back: "give me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kgXgeUZWG5",
      },
      {
        front: "darte",
        back: "to give you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UivdUhwVB9",
      },
      {
        front: "decirles",
        back: "tell them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uWAgqspjr8",
      },
      {
        front: "decirme",
        back: "tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NM0WJEaJmz",
      },
      {
        front: "decirnos",
        back: "tell us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nhSLH5IxdV",
      },
      {
        front: "detalle",
        back: "detail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "75gP6qjGdg",
      },
      {
        front: "detalles",
        back: "details",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IB3kMwD9bz",
      },
      {
        front: "diferencia",
        back: "difference",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xx8XPUFwdN",
      },
      {
        front: "diferencias",
        back: "differences",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NRKXp7GM5r",
      },
      {
        front: "estuche",
        back: "case",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N2dZ05PiZO",
      },
      {
        front: "explica",
        back: "Explain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K1h6O88mYM",
      },
      {
        front: "explicando",
        back: "explaining",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XM5IUBjI53",
      },
      {
        front: "explicar",
        back: "explain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jpZVwJFPOE",
      },
      {
        front: "explicaron",
        back: "they explained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H3qjIGN0Ay",
      },
      {
        front: "explicas",
        back: "you explain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nrp0vfZjQt",
      },
      {
        front: "explicó",
        back: "explained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MlifhS6lzQ",
      },
      {
        front: "expliqué",
        back: "I explained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9SZYrqzOj4",
      },
      {
        front: "les",
        back: "them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IZ6CUCXuCf",
      },
      {
        front: "libro de ejercicios",
        back: "workbook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HHKAZIkdno",
      },
      {
        front: "libros de ejercicios",
        back: "exercise books",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3ubFArnpCz",
      },
      {
        front: "mochila",
        back: "backpack",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hcNhHEaoQb",
      },
      {
        front: "mochilas",
        back: "backpacks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TqVuQWnEcj",
      },
      {
        front: "nivel",
        back: "level",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wviUXA7I3w",
      },
      {
        front: "niveles",
        back: "levels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3r0qmvqGhI",
      },
      {
        front: "regla",
        back: "ruler",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ZCgZG4Z4I",
      },
      {
        front: "reglas",
        back: "rules",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yOtT4hkTMV",
      },
      {
        front: "te",
        back: "tea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2nib86BSl6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "oQrwY3VJjv",
    title: "Unit 66",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "objects21",
        back: "objects21",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OcEtT4yij9",
      },
      {
        front: "objects22",
        back: "objects22",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QXGxuK3ZoU",
      },
      {
        front: "objects23",
        back: "objects23",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IyPtK8EaXB",
      },
      {
        front: "objects",
        back: "objects",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f6HSut7Cis",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "KH91v1PGMi",
    title: "Unit 67",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "antes",
        back: "before",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NwxKLHrEdI",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendido",
        back: "learned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R2oCCOr63P",
      },
      {
        front: "bastante",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xnIPwmtJ7L",
      },
      {
        front: "comido",
        back: "Eaten",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ll8uOYpF5N",
      },
      {
        front: "electricidad",
        back: "electricity",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BcajRLYg4F",
      },
      {
        front: "estado",
        back: "condition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ws5HAJ5nUQ",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiado",
        back: "studied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tt1lSHnscU",
      },
      {
        front: "extraña",
        back: "strange",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wa4fFpA63U",
      },
      {
        front: "extraño",
        back: "weird",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lyXNhrY7n5",
      },
      {
        front: "fuego",
        back: "fire",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F9L2noaDtj",
      },
      {
        front: "fuegos",
        back: "fires",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JWj1pj2Juw",
      },
      {
        front: "ha",
        back: "ha",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nc5OKLeY9D",
      },
      {
        front: "has",
        back: "have you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7iIaF0dQvd",
      },
      {
        front: "he",
        back: "I have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "68Dik6l2l9",
      },
      {
        front: "nacional",
        back: "national",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BirEgHSKyK",
      },
      {
        front: "nacionales",
        back: "national",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9nVTaJHzAb",
      },
      {
        front: "obrera",
        back: "worker",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ESnBKvTGYs",
      },
      {
        front: "obrero",
        back: "worker",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MQhlCOtzBC",
      },
      {
        front: "peligro",
        back: "hazard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y01DQN62qC",
      },
      {
        front: "peligros",
        back: "dangers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VNFkbJZeF3",
      },
      {
        front: "recibido",
        back: "received",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jgsKmtC1CJ",
      },
      {
        front: "salvajes",
        back: "wild",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v1etUZREFS",
      },
      {
        front: "terrible",
        back: "terrible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0gax8KTJtL",
      },
      {
        front: "todavía",
        back: "yet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CwILuej3y2",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajado",
        back: "worked up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eMvGCToatB",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "iLSWg0jx5c",
    title: "Unit 67",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a lo largo de",
        back: "throughout",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n4TGxC80mR",
      },
      {
        front: "a lo largo del",
        back: "along the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tw3xBRPrjj",
      },
      {
        front: "acampaba",
        back: "he was camping",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BkgKc4DIn6",
      },
      {
        front: "acampando",
        back: "camping",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0SiaNdKShF",
      },
      {
        front: "acampas",
        back: "you camp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ktpnWckCGb",
      },
      {
        front: "bádminton",
        back: "badminton",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D0DoI60Thi",
      },
      {
        front: "cartas",
        back: "cards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y2hQOH9ANR",
      },
      {
        front: "colecciona",
        back: "collect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1uHsFqRbEO",
      },
      {
        front: "coleccionaba",
        back: "collected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wTOGgdbDFf",
      },
      {
        front: "coleccionabas",
        back: "you collected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H6peDytQ0L",
      },
      {
        front: "coleccionan",
        back: "collect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FNu4ICZJUg",
      },
      {
        front: "cometa",
        back: "kite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wuUK3RwJeo",
      },
      {
        front: "cometas",
        back: "kites",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qa3P9MARR8",
      },
      {
        front: "dibujos",
        back: "drawings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZsFZ0c9pus",
      },
      {
        front: "esquiar",
        back: "ski",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JYXE30cphe",
      },
      {
        front: "estampillas",
        back: "stamps",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IZO6EU40eA",
      },
      {
        front: "gorra",
        back: "Cap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LIzd4GXxdP",
      },
      {
        front: "hockey",
        back: "hockey",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eIyLb22gIf",
      },
      {
        front: "maravillosas",
        back: "wonderful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H5ubKn3ls3",
      },
      {
        front: "maravilloso",
        back: "marvelous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sVAl9TNMQG",
      },
      {
        front: "me",
        back: "I",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iXfPaKpZsN",
      },
      {
        front: "navegaba",
        back: "was sailing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ckxaPNSfYQ",
      },
      {
        front: "navegamos",
        back: "we sail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O4ESrZ5iMK",
      },
      {
        front: "navegué",
        back: "I sailed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dNlHkgXxGD",
      },
      {
        front: "pop",
        back: "pop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P3IzYccuoh",
      },
      {
        front: "postal",
        back: "Postcard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tdGZba3cHF",
      },
      {
        front: "prestar",
        back: "to loan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NbC12UD8Yq",
      },
      {
        front: "prestas",
        back: "lend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EHtzbFiTGJ",
      },
      {
        front: "prestaste",
        back: "you lent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dSdniQHg4l",
      },
      {
        front: "presto",
        back: "presto",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iRebHvRw20",
      },
      {
        front: "presté",
        back: "lent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L40B19svjf",
      },
      {
        front: "raqueta",
        back: "racket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3gpFpCcmnw",
      },
      {
        front: "rompecabezas",
        back: "puzzle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6IFds5fBKw",
      },
      {
        front: "tanto",
        back: "so much",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UJYxP7WrLj",
      },
      {
        front: "tantos",
        back: "so many",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GpUzfhNF0T",
      },
      {
        front: "te",
        back: "tea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Km4zPCnUui",
      },
      {
        front: "velero",
        back: "sailboat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0AWDaijYGO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "CGowKgqat4",
    title: "Unit 68",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abran",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XRrfX7ai33",
      },
      {
        front: "abren",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k7zE472qTT",
      },
      {
        front: "beban",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sRlMurTi31",
      },
      {
        front: "beben",
        back: "they drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7qD9sBXPnL",
      },
      {
        front: "brazalete",
        back: "bracelet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k7UOTXBipU",
      },
      {
        front: "brazaletes",
        back: "bangles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VjPXfXmdTG",
      },
      {
        front: "cheque",
        back: "check",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dAmrPXWbpK",
      },
      {
        front: "coman",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rPKGrgX62l",
      },
      {
        front: "comen",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NT7Ozqff4E",
      },
      {
        front: "compran",
        back: "they buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CtEprQzS4h",
      },
      {
        front: "compren",
        back: "buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y6cU0MRN3x",
      },
      {
        front: "cuál quiere",
        back: "which one do you want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5AuCS67Kpu",
      },
      {
        front: "cuál quieres",
        back: "which one do you want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IK2iHsOSxR",
      },
      {
        front: "cuáles quiere",
        back: "which ones do you want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Brl8vdZklx",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo quiere",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9KV2IAlt0y",
      },
      {
        front: "pagar",
        back: "how would you like to pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ow1ZFshV1r",
      },
      {
        front: "cómo quieres pagar",
        back: "how do you want to pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kmTuKFyeba",
      },
      {
        front: "decidan",
        back: "decide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1fwFWJFpbE",
      },
      {
        front: "deciden",
        back: "decide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VoLxkyEE3U",
      },
      {
        front: "gratis",
        back: "free",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IAlknXApuF",
      },
      {
        front: "hacen",
        back: "make",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VMhH9L8290",
      },
      {
        front: "hagan",
        back: "do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gGvp7CbpH8",
      },
      {
        front: "me la llevo",
        back: "I'll take it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "40o7LiCnsm",
      },
      {
        front: "me las llevo",
        back: "I'll take them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZSf2nkXmF9",
      },
      {
        front: "me lo llevo",
        back: "I'll take it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nUViAMeH2p",
      },
      {
        front: "me los llevo",
        back: "I will take them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tXlpPTM6JZ",
      },
      {
        front: "otra",
        back: "other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IraNbh8hq9",
      },
      {
        front: "otras",
        back: "others",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ho5TI4J9XV",
      },
      {
        front: "otro",
        back: "other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ryisv8ay6b",
      },
      {
        front: "otros",
        back: "others",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0eLrMFuxKi",
      },
      {
        front: "perfume",
        back: "fragrance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YxJNnLWOLE",
      },
      {
        front: "perfumes",
        back: "perfume",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kR3B10MFtl",
      },
      {
        front: "pijama",
        back: "Pijama",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TPe1xNPvC7",
      },
      {
        front: "pijamas",
        back: "pajamas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cKuOOVqfSW",
      },
      {
        front: "recibo",
        back: "receipt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aLIVB9YheX",
      },
      {
        front: "recibos",
        back: "receipts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Or8rl0V5G7",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajan",
        back: "they work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4itLM9ze8p",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajen",
        back: "work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nkxrkgm6Ro",
      },
      {
        front: "van",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GHZzpnm4Ae",
      },
      {
        front: "vayan",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7zJ8LTfrkg",
      },
      {
        front: "vendedoras",
        back: "saleswomen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vAKH3wIV4f",
      },
      {
        front: "vendedores",
        back: "sellers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lAjxprC9Ra",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "myxk2fNhTT",
    title: "Unit 68",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "actriz",
        back: "actress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pZmL2j9ln7",
      },
      {
        front: "cantantes",
        back: "singers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aoGIrpGS9m",
      },
      {
        front: "cliente",
        back: "customer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GdevZmbTpD",
      },
      {
        front: "concejo municipal",
        back: "city Council",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ATxsrf2YJX",
      },
      {
        front: "conductor",
        back: "driver",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iS9QlLVRbO",
      },
      {
        front: "conductora",
        back: "driver",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VTL0jZq3F8",
      },
      {
        front: "conductoras",
        back: "drivers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "un82kMqC5N",
      },
      {
        front: "conductores",
        back: "drivers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VLvuX3y9JP",
      },
      {
        front: "copiaba",
        back: "copied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4M8wNWmg9x",
      },
      {
        front: "copiamos",
        back: "we copied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rbhf6mOWxf",
      },
      {
        front: "copiando",
        back: "copying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mwd7JLeDzQ",
      },
      {
        front: "copiaste",
        back: "you copied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qd8VCl5NQq",
      },
      {
        front: "correo",
        back: "mail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HuayKMhiJT",
      },
      {
        front: "departamento",
        back: "department",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hjBcl94VZp",
      },
      {
        front: "departamentos",
        back: "departments",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BlS0Yz0mNI",
      },
      {
        front: "descargamos",
        back: "we download",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EPPjbDwbEg",
      },
      {
        front: "descargando",
        back: "downloading",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YIuOsze0Mw",
      },
      {
        front: "descargaste",
        back: "you downloaded",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lIi76aFj9q",
      },
      {
        front: "descargué",
        back: "downloaded",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ml3fo3Hkeb",
      },
      {
        front: "descargó",
        back: "discharge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QuQU5jX9Xl",
      },
      {
        front: "fotógrafa",
        back: "photographer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eFCo9TBNSE",
      },
      {
        front: "fotógrafas",
        back: "female photographers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XYYAU6Obg5",
      },
      {
        front: "fotógrafo",
        back: "photographer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aAyur3bpuE",
      },
      {
        front: "fotógrafos",
        back: "photographers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PTbdh58uxT",
      },
      {
        front: "física",
        back: "physical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QISIqih1ls",
      },
      {
        front: "ganaba",
        back: "won",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3rSSVFfHP3",
      },
      {
        front: "ganaban",
        back: "they won",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W4LSgYwsG0",
      },
      {
        front: "ganabas",
        back: "you won",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e9ZbInBfM7",
      },
      {
        front: "ganar",
        back: "win",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s0QBPd2WTi",
      },
      {
        front: "ganó",
        back: "won",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cd8IkTJOpa",
      },
      {
        front: "impresora",
        back: "printing machine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7sZhreVBXd",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiador",
        back: "cleaner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RapgEABRbx",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiadora",
        back: "cleaner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hw64FZdtuJ",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiadoras",
        back: "cleaners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nuwzHTQAIb",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiadores",
        back: "cleaners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3K6CVYeQhr",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiando",
        back: "Cleaning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZpbdMcVKrb",
      },
      {
        front: "madera",
        back: "wood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZLiWEmngK2",
      },
      {
        front: "ocupación",
        back: "occupation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eKBFh2mXbK",
      },
      {
        front: "personal",
        back: "staff",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cO6RocKojk",
      },
      {
        front: "pienso que deberías",
        back: "i think you should",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fl8STjOook",
      },
      {
        front: "recepcionista",
        back: "receptionist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rYFCvxF1WQ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "28Yvmyknh8",
    title: "Unit 69",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "alejada",
        back: "far away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dmFpAAWCgi",
      },
      {
        front: "alejadas",
        back: "far away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HswiHWkavI",
      },
      {
        front: "alejado",
        back: "away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pBsl7PV5e0",
      },
      {
        front: "alejados",
        back: "away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vBIsnLJd17",
      },
      {
        front: "auxilio",
        back: "help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vZp6jgxjxn",
      },
      {
        front: "caernos",
        back: "fall down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Swjo20FnZa",
      },
      {
        front: "caerte",
        back: "fall down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AHTPioTltG",
      },
      {
        front: "cambio",
        back: "change",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SJ6hsE9Zqz",
      },
      {
        front: "cambios",
        back: "changes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2mwB6ByNyN",
      },
      {
        front: "cerebro",
        back: "brain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z1CpE1xVk8",
      },
      {
        front: "cerebros",
        back: "brains",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oJa6xDSJad",
      },
      {
        front: "comer mucho",
        back: "eat a lot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U6rrj4xdpS",
      },
      {
        front: "en forma",
        back: "fit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n3B2gAcS9G",
      },
      {
        front: "fácilmente",
        back: "easily",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SirgjHqxQT",
      },
      {
        front: "gravemente",
        back: "seriously",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uBhP0zMdx3",
      },
      {
        front: "horrible",
        back: "horrible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QovBWqBcLX",
      },
      {
        front: "inmediatamente",
        back: "immediately",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nlpyoeOFAa",
      },
      {
        front: "me olvido",
        back: "I forget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2lUlEV32fm",
      },
      {
        front: "me veo",
        back: "I look",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YpuMVTltFE",
      },
      {
        front: "medicina",
        back: "medicine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7D0YmdJvsK",
      },
      {
        front: "medicinas",
        back: "medicines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t8rChYyTKq",
      },
      {
        front: "molesta",
        back: "upset",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BAcB9UycRz",
      },
      {
        front: "molestas",
        back: "annoying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XRpYfOeSZf",
      },
      {
        front: "molesto",
        back: "annoying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "exhNaI3HhK",
      },
      {
        front: "molestos",
        back: "annoying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tMZkE46Pmj",
      },
      {
        front: "muerta",
        back: "dead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u1z3nb6vHe",
      },
      {
        front: "muertas",
        back: "dead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x8NsaZdzHW",
      },
      {
        front: "muerto",
        back: "dead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tywAYM1TxO",
      },
      {
        front: "muertos",
        back: "dead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "665hok90hH",
      },
      {
        front: "nacer",
        back: "be born",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r9zp5zDJqZ",
      },
      {
        front: "nos olvidamos",
        back: "we forgot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wwBhLNEll7",
      },
      {
        front: "nos vemos",
        back: "See ya",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AyViuQnGtb",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidarnos",
        back: "forget us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ouEGxjdXL",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidarse",
        back: "forget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MeOf9gws9y",
      },
      {
        front: "pelo",
        back: "hair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fP1twmxCHL",
      },
      {
        front: "reírme",
        back: "laugh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "htkdpy4cnB",
      },
      {
        front: "reírnos",
        back: "laugh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aHQi2wo4SQ",
      },
      {
        front: "reírse",
        back: "laugh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9Tse8sKym9",
      },
      {
        front: "reírte",
        back: "laugh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oXict3Zr9t",
      },
      {
        front: "rápidamente",
        back: "quickly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bYSIVhEtcO",
      },
      {
        front: "sangre",
        back: "blood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YQ48OJaKt1",
      },
      {
        front: "se olvida",
        back: "forget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j4cjb7nRjQ",
      },
      {
        front: "se olvidaron",
        back: "they forgot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ccQ6mr87Rv",
      },
      {
        front: "se ve",
        back: "it looks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5WA3MZIHu9",
      },
      {
        front: "se ven",
        back: "they look",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uGk8pa2gGC",
      },
      {
        front: "te olvidas",
        back: "you forget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AKTsXmd87Z",
      },
      {
        front: "te ves",
        back: "you look",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VtgUJjDVUF",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajar mucho",
        back: "work a lot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P1hJgC21fC",
      },
      {
        front: "usual",
        back: "usual",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j8BJ64B32x",
      },
      {
        front: "vendaje",
        back: "bandage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dPjgM0OiY1",
      },
      {
        front: "vernos",
        back: "see us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B9OARBade0",
      },
      {
        front: "verse",
        back: "see each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nde1kcTwJW",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "G6TD05o9B0",
    title: "Unit 69",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ama de casa",
        back: "Housewife",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nu3gZaM8RJ",
      },
      {
        front: "amas de casa",
        back: "Housewives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HryrwtX14J",
      },
      {
        front: "armario",
        back: "cupboard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "szaAOHTKjl",
      },
      {
        front: "batería",
        back: "drums",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R2KlY5P3bK",
      },
      {
        front: "baterías",
        back: "batteries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gAe5uLJusf",
      },
      {
        front: "casi",
        back: "almost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pFhiI2G5HP",
      },
      {
        front: "castaño",
        back: "Brown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y4qqaiXndh",
      },
      {
        front: "cita",
        back: "appointment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GTBDjutF8z",
      },
      {
        front: "escúter",
        back: "scooter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1f2Tx1D0Wv",
      },
      {
        front: "fútbol americano",
        back: "football",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7z9mcKIb0O",
      },
      {
        front: "globo",
        back: "balloon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zSviMnfe3v",
      },
      {
        front: "globos",
        back: "balloons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NbLI4bds2B",
      },
      {
        front: "había",
        back: "there was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jjDf1aI6DD",
      },
      {
        front: "hacía",
        back: "towards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rV2JAgWFP2",
      },
      {
        front: "hacíamos",
        back: "we did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kBs2CHF3Vl",
      },
      {
        front: "hacían",
        back: "they did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yTYeDDryAu",
      },
      {
        front: "hacías",
        back: "you did",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XVln2coBjI",
      },
      {
        front: "liso",
        back: "smooth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uRDNvLxbyX",
      },
      {
        front: "luego",
        back: "later",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PaLwjlzZJW",
      },
      {
        front: "mientras",
        back: "While",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vdEm8oedvk",
      },
      {
        front: "patinaba",
        back: "skated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eptj4Rz07t",
      },
      {
        front: "patinaban",
        back: "they skated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kf3VVTmdkl",
      },
      {
        front: "patinabas",
        back: "you skated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z1qWKEccsi",
      },
      {
        front: "patinar",
        back: "rollerblading",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h1MDb5yVTC",
      },
      {
        front: "patines",
        back: "roller skates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SjjnCcw4GY",
      },
      {
        front: "patinábamos",
        back: "we skated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CYO5BT5VxD",
      },
      {
        front: "patín",
        back: "roller skate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b7XyAc16wE",
      },
      {
        front: "payaso",
        back: "clown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dTQ2Li9PF2",
      },
      {
        front: "payasos",
        back: "clowns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VOXPPCQhvM",
      },
      {
        front: "póster",
        back: "poster",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tOqMRbmbIb",
      },
      {
        front: "pósteres",
        back: "posters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q17hC65qS2",
      },
      {
        front: "veía",
        back: "saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CKYp68IQdQ",
      },
      {
        front: "veíamos",
        back: "we saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7j1ySRJsde",
      },
      {
        front: "veían",
        back: "they saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MNBZqDiA1F",
      },
      {
        front: "veías",
        back: "you saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6Q3ECbk08j",
      },
      {
        front: "zanahorias",
        back: "carrots",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t8BeLe04vr",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "VpHG93owxO",
    title: "Unit 70",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ahorrar",
        back: "save",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tK9KqZ3LTO",
      },
      {
        front: "alquilar",
        back: "rent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "naIl8Ep2XV",
      },
      {
        front: "alrededor del",
        back: "around the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UMLT6oyiYr",
      },
      {
        front: "así que",
        back: "so",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YXUmbOPG4g",
      },
      {
        front: "autopista",
        back: "highway",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7GCFcLjbfv",
      },
      {
        front: "avenida",
        back: "avenue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hh8T88dw0E",
      },
      {
        front: "avenidas",
        back: "avenues",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d6K9hYT13k",
      },
      {
        front: "cálido",
        back: "warm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sQPastPlqI",
      },
      {
        front: "empaqué",
        back: "packing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dllrm8tScF",
      },
      {
        front: "encantaría",
        back: "would love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MtuA2aPPJS",
      },
      {
        front: "encantarían",
        back: "they would love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TGRtFcwa7A",
      },
      {
        front: "euro",
        back: "euro",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n8D3fzSVfK",
      },
      {
        front: "gasolina",
        back: "gasoline",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6Vdd9Ou3Cr",
      },
      {
        front: "irte",
        back: "go away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HT4i5NDS39",
      },
      {
        front: "mapa",
        back: "Map",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ilxVJT9a9E",
      },
      {
        front: "mapas",
        back: "maps",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2EnEWl605I",
      },
      {
        front: "me voy",
        back: "leave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pSsuXz1AZV",
      },
      {
        front: "nos vamos",
        back: "Let's go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7yIZ6rUIQC",
      },
      {
        front: "profunda",
        back: "deep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ao91UFbqqZ",
      },
      {
        front: "profundo",
        back: "deep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hyh7lo0Nzl",
      },
      {
        front: "resto",
        back: "rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a7PhK02QE2",
      },
      {
        front: "se va",
        back: "it goes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c1tK1wA7zE",
      },
      {
        front: "se van",
        back: "they go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yjRtlY1llq",
      },
      {
        front: "sería una buena idea",
        back: "It would be a good idea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qL9dcjFD0g",
      },
      {
        front: "soñamos",
        back: "we dream",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "29rIRCfnYx",
      },
      {
        front: "sueña",
        back: "it sounds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7JwfjawIWP",
      },
      {
        front: "sueño",
        back: "sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ibQ3m9HQG",
      },
      {
        front: "te vas",
        back: "you go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dZmjSW0FdQ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "bs3euKRD0e",
    title: "Unit 71",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acaba de",
        back: "just",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9ImQ5dCqcI",
      },
      {
        front: "acabamos de",
        back: "we just",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SVFPTrM7zx",
      },
      {
        front: "acaban de",
        back: "just finished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9AvezsfpWR",
      },
      {
        front: "acabas de",
        back: "you just",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fqrsRk7A14",
      },
      {
        front: "acabo de",
        back: "just",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8pY29Bvv2M",
      },
      {
        front: "boles",
        back: "bowls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4V4rcKA6Ed",
      },
      {
        front: "cancelar",
        back: "Cancel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ui4YF3AQko",
      },
      {
        front: "estante",
        back: "shelf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4Qr42Pz3Kw",
      },
      {
        front: "estantes",
        back: "shelves",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "srN4qstEeI",
      },
      {
        front: "fregadero",
        back: "sink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PouzYWVQ7H",
      },
      {
        front: "garaje",
        back: "garage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ubybzIEZSi",
      },
      {
        front: "gritando",
        back: "Screaming",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8IlrCwZvWl",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar de",
        back: "talk about",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U9FPp1G2Ea",
      },
      {
        front: "joyas",
        back: "jewels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yczO9iDuaP",
      },
      {
        front: "lavamanos",
        back: "handwash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oqIRtX5vEB",
      },
      {
        front: "melones",
        back: "melons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rr5YedRMBD",
      },
      {
        front: "melón",
        back: "cantaloupe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DjqAMSd859",
      },
      {
        front: "pararme",
        back: "stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d4FwJsTnpL",
      },
      {
        front: "pararnos",
        back: "stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y37fd36DLJ",
      },
      {
        front: "pararse",
        back: "stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rkKIB59tgu",
      },
      {
        front: "pararte",
        back: "stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wmmi1PrUwR",
      },
      {
        front: "recién",
        back: "newly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EiDQegwwec",
      },
      {
        front: "rosadas",
        back: "pink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X5rw1PFN35",
      },
      {
        front: "secar",
        back: "dry off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uyXuX6ptXA",
      },
      {
        front: "secaste",
        back: "you dried up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ElfObCrBCT",
      },
      {
        front: "seco",
        back: "dried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2FgV3w87Jb",
      },
      {
        front: "secó",
        back: "dried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hid4OhVHgL",
      },
      {
        front: "sequé",
        back: "I know that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ekpuKLNsT0",
      },
      {
        front: "techo",
        back: "ceiling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KEepS2aunn",
      },
      {
        front: "techos",
        back: "roofs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UtXghzSQ4Z",
      },
      {
        front: "termina",
        back: "ends",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AcDii9xCuV",
      },
      {
        front: "terminar",
        back: "end up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f3xwxcAeM9",
      },
      {
        front: "terminaron",
        back: "finished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z3TbAXAsQE",
      },
      {
        front: "terminaste",
        back: "You finished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ib6gz04FXB",
      },
      {
        front: "termino",
        back: "term",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iSOViLN7F8",
      },
      {
        front: "terminé",
        back: "I finished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i0GRiktvqf",
      },
      {
        front: "terminó",
        back: "term",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EYGc2vX51j",
      },
      {
        front: "tortillas",
        back: "tortillas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZNaWekE4NU",
      },
      {
        front: "vender",
        back: "sell",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nvtQQotVd8",
      },
      {
        front: "vendieron",
        back: "sold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wHx4Z6RfIM",
      },
      {
        front: "ventilador",
        back: "fan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PnIxMhlfiL",
      },
      {
        front: "vestida",
        back: "clothed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "balr45hDuK",
      },
      {
        front: "vestidas",
        back: "clothed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1HENorw54w",
      },
      {
        front: "vestido",
        back: "dress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5QDiB65ojR",
      },
      {
        front: "vestir",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5CKmuzYtrv",
      },
      {
        front: "vestir+prpers",
        back: "dress+prpers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "chYoe76kyc",
      },
      {
        front: "vestirme",
        back: "get dressed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ToGJ93XQof",
      },
      {
        front: "vestirnos",
        back: "get dressed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t7mGx51kaD",
      },
      {
        front: "vestirte",
        back: "get dressed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8brxdBtTmp",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "u12q6zbbQE",
    title: "Unit 71",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "asunto",
        back: "affair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tb51fWS4Hi",
      },
      {
        front: "asuntos",
        back: "affairs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bbUqOa1QOD",
      },
      {
        front: "añade",
        back: "Add",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rmOkjE5GDw",
      },
      {
        front: "añadir",
        back: "Add",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ATdFCf2tAl",
      },
      {
        front: "añado",
        back: "I add",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FK6779eUtK",
      },
      {
        front: "clara",
        back: "clear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nj9KGJwcMe",
      },
      {
        front: "claras",
        back: "clear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d01WPyEwJY",
      },
      {
        front: "claro",
        back: "Clear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HNdAy6ccLE",
      },
      {
        front: "contacto",
        back: "Contact",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lDyyfeFYOv",
      },
      {
        front: "contactos",
        back: "contacts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XX1LhpJgMA",
      },
      {
        front: "di",
        back: "gave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eCkKf1KJAm",
      },
      {
        front: "dieron",
        back: "they gave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "558yhzQdpR",
      },
      {
        front: "digital",
        back: "digital",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1V6rGhHFpd",
      },
      {
        front: "digitales",
        back: "digital",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hyI6mGjD2c",
      },
      {
        front: "dimos",
        back: "we gave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PgFblTSQR8",
      },
      {
        front: "dio",
        back: "gave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NCrTeFB9lc",
      },
      {
        front: "diste",
        back: "you gave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wZEgsn0cN3",
      },
      {
        front: "e",
        back: "and",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BVPCPeQEVD",
      },
      {
        front: "ellas se",
        back: "they know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "njFMpWWf2N",
      },
      {
        front: "ellos se",
        back: "they know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OeR8vbWdug",
      },
      {
        front: "enteramos",
        back: "we found out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sJilMOWmlB",
      },
      {
        front: "enteraron",
        back: "found out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uCffpRa4x2",
      },
      {
        front: "enterarse",
        back: "find out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cNA9Mmk05i",
      },
      {
        front: "enteraste",
        back: "did you find out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ic0sRKzYna",
      },
      {
        front: "enteré",
        back: "I found out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f4iu4QS3N5",
      },
      {
        front: "enteró",
        back: "whole",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UcTZ2C7nzc",
      },
      {
        front: "estudio",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qT3v6kkLPK",
      },
      {
        front: "estudios",
        back: "studies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5GNNIBjFCP",
      },
      {
        front: "formulario",
        back: "form",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UYNs6RYyTr",
      },
      {
        front: "querer decir",
        back: "mean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hLpwlcPpP0",
      },
      {
        front: "quería decir",
        back: "I wanted to say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kn1MroZSOr",
      },
      {
        front: "quiere decir",
        back: "means",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "roZ0P6N2Z8",
      },
      {
        front: "quieren decir",
        back: "They mean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vvAP0dr058",
      },
      {
        front: "quieres decir",
        back: "you mean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FW5XqBdn6D",
      },
      {
        front: "salida",
        back: "exit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MdvW3ow82i",
      },
      {
        front: "salidas",
        back: "Departures",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Puis42ktO7",
      },
      {
        front: "se",
        back: "I know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U6xUtczc9H",
      },
      {
        front: "se la",
        back: "I know the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KKVoLixr2r",
      },
      {
        front: "se las",
        back: "I know them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eRONp5aRUD",
      },
      {
        front: "se los",
        back: "I know them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hm44HvHmEa",
      },
      {
        front: "software",
        back: "software",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ySqp5Fxj7L",
      },
      {
        front: "tú",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H4PMYRDcUA",
      },
      {
        front: "se",
        back: "you know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wk7nuAn9IA",
      },
      {
        front: "web",
        back: "Web",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tEeCypNnWh",
      },
      {
        front: "él se",
        back: "he knows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e2SpHUaSYn",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "SldZ3B0PB3",
    title: "Unit 72",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "past tense 51",
        back: "past tense 51",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yADAhewlvI",
      },
      {
        front: "past tense 52",
        back: "past tense 52",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QETgk37dEc",
      },
      {
        front: "past tense 53",
        back: "past tense 53",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tvOXalhxNW",
      },
      {
        front: "past tense",
        back: "past tense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RDJDAUxKnC",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "cbSQfQ9HFO",
    title: "Unit 73",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "biología",
        back: "biology",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S07nZDi3xE",
      },
      {
        front: "comprado",
        back: "bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zZNX9pnoIb",
      },
      {
        front: "conocido",
        back: "acquaintance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DZjkaJTt1t",
      },
      {
        front: "cualquier lugar",
        back: "any place",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c5r0sUm7fs",
      },
      {
        front: "dicho",
        back: "saying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cEzELu1hM7",
      },
      {
        front: "estrella",
        back: "star",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wPO98Bt9vg",
      },
      {
        front: "estrellas",
        back: "stars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AyM0b3UBJS",
      },
      {
        front: "guía",
        back: "guide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9sw4FMcPmB",
      },
      {
        front: "hecho",
        back: "done",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "odCP6tgoDE",
      },
      {
        front: "luna",
        back: "Moon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NsqPevisAs",
      },
      {
        front: "metas",
        back: "goals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y8vu9PSCwO",
      },
      {
        front: "multitud",
        back: "crew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CSSBoybQ51",
      },
      {
        front: "negativa",
        back: "negative",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JMxRt49r1Z",
      },
      {
        front: "negativo",
        back: "negative",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9mKtTNH8Zu",
      },
      {
        front: "pedido",
        back: "order",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pdEf4NgeLp",
      },
      {
        front: "policía",
        back: "policeman",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vtN2EMCWSp",
      },
      {
        front: "por cierto",
        back: "by the way",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4hCwK55rkE",
      },
      {
        front: "ruta",
        back: "route",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GWo1moASUT",
      },
      {
        front: "rutas",
        back: "routes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JXa3g74AGO",
      },
      {
        front: "señal",
        back: "sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wBIrZVEVed",
      },
      {
        front: "señales",
        back: "signs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ba3GuHsiOq",
      },
      {
        front: "sonido",
        back: "sound",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QaBDd7p7Zk",
      },
      {
        front: "surfea",
        back: "surf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zjl661xeXF",
      },
      {
        front: "surfean",
        back: "surf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JGuliqazeG",
      },
      {
        front: "surfear",
        back: "to surf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y8pc9LmKG7",
      },
      {
        front: "surfeo",
        back: "I surf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i7B9rsrF3k",
      },
      {
        front: "tal",
        back: "such",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7WQVrweHil",
      },
      {
        front: "tales",
        back: "such",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XkqYLSeqwx",
      },
      {
        front: "tenido",
        back: "Dyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2i3gXaZQQa",
      },
      {
        front: "vaya",
        back: "wow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UBQCEsMrfK",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "VO53ln0lXA",
    title: "Unit 73",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abuelita",
        back: "granny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bCNW8M8pHf",
      },
      {
        front: "abuelitos",
        back: "grandparents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q7FFCmgKw1",
      },
      {
        front: "aconseja",
        back: "advise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ATowV2O3Xx",
      },
      {
        front: "aconsejan",
        back: "advise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GMMdNUCIed",
      },
      {
        front: "aconsejas",
        back: "do you advise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pXDuQH6Blm",
      },
      {
        front: "aconsejo",
        back: "I advise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zJQLRtL3R1",
      },
      {
        front: "adulta",
        back: "adult",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4NpjHRH0Fn",
      },
      {
        front: "adulto",
        back: "adult",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZQkatPiZuu",
      },
      {
        front: "bajita",
        back: "short",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K9q0SLwNvF",
      },
      {
        front: "bajitas",
        back: "short",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "muoVDDabmT",
      },
      {
        front: "bajito",
        back: "short",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5VxPDveeYj",
      },
      {
        front: "bistec",
        back: "steak",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yS2TAwJhjY",
      },
      {
        front: "casaron",
        back: "got married",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kwhcO9Upi6",
      },
      {
        front: "crecieron",
        back: "they grew up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eiaym3eSax",
      },
      {
        front: "crecimos",
        back: "we grew up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5KzmmkCrud",
      },
      {
        front: "creciste",
        back: "you grew up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NQSP6TTjSQ",
      },
      {
        front: "creció",
        back: "grew up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2pUWvNDa4H",
      },
      {
        front: "crecí",
        back: "I grew up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ryjvzgH6AI",
      },
      {
        front: "gatito",
        back: "little cat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lo2EE9LWlH",
      },
      {
        front: "genial",
        back: "brilliant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YQ993sgbSF",
      },
      {
        front: "graduada",
        back: "graduated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "52VvlTiw3j",
      },
      {
        front: "graduado",
        back: "graduate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UvM4gV6KH2",
      },
      {
        front: "graduados",
        back: "graduates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CwQGSLhWya",
      },
      {
        front: "hermanito",
        back: "little brother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wMJrFsF06u",
      },
      {
        front: "igual",
        back: "Same",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SFkXSZPLCD",
      },
      {
        front: "iguales",
        back: "equal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PWpAaJgi9Q",
      },
      {
        front: "jalea",
        back: "jelly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YTDhKXOPoi",
      },
      {
        front: "llevarme bien",
        back: "get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wUxVBMRuoR",
      },
      {
        front: "llevarnos bien",
        back: "to get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QMFThrQmy6",
      },
      {
        front: "llevarse bien",
        back: "get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jN7Ju70H9n",
      },
      {
        front: "llevarte bien",
        back: "get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YkKW3VrHsk",
      },
      {
        front: "me llevaba bien",
        back: "I got along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oMWkbCvhCr",
      },
      {
        front: "me llevo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EIH1H8k4Xf",
      },
      {
        front: "bien",
        back: "I get on well",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ohECTrakm5",
      },
      {
        front: "mesita",
        back: "small table",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yTuM0LOXiq",
      },
      {
        front: "normal",
        back: "normal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sjmsrqrrDa",
      },
      {
        front: "nos casamos",
        back: "We married",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DlSN7tjFNG",
      },
      {
        front: "nos llevamos bien",
        back: "we get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rIZYQr62PS",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeñita",
        back: "tiny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hZ6k1oMIhr",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeñito",
        back: "tiny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gYF6kSK2xt",
      },
      {
        front: "pequeñitos",
        back: "little ones",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JgOlS5FcHW",
      },
      {
        front: "perrito",
        back: "puppy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BgY22Emn65",
      },
      {
        front: "pesca",
        back: "fishing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i2UgTrNnjE",
      },
      {
        front: "poquito",
        back: "a little",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nWFFB2LOK3",
      },
      {
        front: "ratones",
        back: "mice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sVY7K64SC3",
      },
      {
        front: "ratón",
        back: "mouse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4cdAY0mt8C",
      },
      {
        front: "rosa",
        back: "pink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "21vv7A9OD2",
      },
      {
        front: "se casan",
        back: "they marry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lWo7LNSyoe",
      },
      {
        front: "se casó",
        back: "got married",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k96kfY8qWC",
      },
      {
        front: "se llevan bien",
        back: "get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LISIqj1bK2",
      },
      {
        front: "se llevaron bien",
        back: "They got along well",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mN1aPlHGEt",
      },
      {
        front: "se llevó bien",
        back: "got along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2SCYHRL5qN",
      },
      {
        front: "soltera",
        back: "single",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6HnX05ZJNx",
      },
      {
        front: "soltero",
        back: "single",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yQNfrqib9b",
      },
      {
        front: "solteros",
        back: "singles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WwLG2NsTDq",
      },
      {
        front: "te casas",
        back: "You get married",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kjWcPUEhlD",
      },
      {
        front: "te llevabas bien",
        back: "you got along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KyukdZDcqi",
      },
      {
        front: "te llevas bien",
        back: "you get along",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WQUHlvJBDq",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ff8Ns8K8sg",
    title: "Unit 74",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "anchas",
        back: "wide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WEBwydcdQJ",
      },
      {
        front: "anchos",
        back: "widths",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cv0jK4Yjny",
      },
      {
        front: "andén",
        back: "platform",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qf0pu6Qthp",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadra",
        back: "block",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "amZDSLkwRr",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadras",
        back: "blocks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mbda55QvaI",
      },
      {
        front: "cuero",
        back: "leather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J2XYAtMKeJ",
      },
      {
        front: "escaleras",
        back: "stairs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TmLrXwcFwz",
      },
      {
        front: "esquina",
        back: "corner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V0PcajpMbH",
      },
      {
        front: "ferrocarril",
        back: "railway",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zzsh9Q4Qb6",
      },
      {
        front: "me perdí",
        back: "i got lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtKwb856ch",
      },
      {
        front: "me subo",
        back: "I get on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fp303J6Bwl",
      },
      {
        front: "norte",
        back: "north",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3QzGtuIQru",
      },
      {
        front: "nos perdimos",
        back: "we got lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MAjR4wgyV0",
      },
      {
        front: "nos subimos",
        back: "we got on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9jOrVagvPr",
      },
      {
        front: "para",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vq8rMF1ggy",
      },
      {
        front: "paramos",
        back: "we stopped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kV3AUy0GtD",
      },
      {
        front: "paras",
        back: "stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IFduzbZPuk",
      },
      {
        front: "paro",
        back: "unemployment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "REMPYN8KIf",
      },
      {
        front: "perderme",
        back: "lose myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F6mQ5eWFAH",
      },
      {
        front: "perdernos",
        back: "get lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UJEEsvUqOQ",
      },
      {
        front: "perderse",
        back: "be lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ggr2QmWXoa",
      },
      {
        front: "perderte",
        back: "lose you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GHoliKrSuV",
      },
      {
        front: "plástico",
        back: "plastic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UNlYfon8ux",
      },
      {
        front: "se cree",
        back: "It is believed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sBRkWQGMUY",
      },
      {
        front: "se dice",
        back: "It is said that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BXUDVCJ5kp",
      },
      {
        front: "se habla",
        back: "is spoken",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BbeP6P0Jz7",
      },
      {
        front: "se hacen",
        back: "are made",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VcTn10OSbP",
      },
      {
        front: "se necesitan",
        back: "are needed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qp3mE2PKrD",
      },
      {
        front: "se ofrece",
        back: "is offered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qWrZcYgRjZ",
      },
      {
        front: "se ofrecen",
        back: "are offered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ghg28ifvw5",
      },
      {
        front: "se usa",
        back: "it's used",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6FQPZ3Y7P8",
      },
      {
        front: "se vende",
        back: "for Sale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vQoFO2gtLq",
      },
      {
        front: "se venden",
        back: "for sale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rg062LmS2J",
      },
      {
        front: "subirme",
        back: "get on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rkMtKz3Rsv",
      },
      {
        front: "subirnos",
        back: "get on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zy8YRRE99I",
      },
      {
        front: "subirse",
        back: "get on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lNPRs2YH9t",
      },
      {
        front: "subirte",
        back: "get on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VPrkJpdrQX",
      },
      {
        front: "subiste",
        back: "you went up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HhPrhgs3Ah",
      },
      {
        front: "sur",
        back: "south",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "REyMfqjM6d",
      },
      {
        front: "te perdiste",
        back: "you got lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OjNA9H2o4b",
      },
      {
        front: "te subes",
        back: "you climb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pa4J6Rz937",
      },
      {
        front: "toallas",
        back: "towels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fKK3UaQ5HB",
      },
      {
        front: "turismo",
        back: "sightseeing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KQhGmKGkxO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "LdkWmPjkzF",
    title: "Unit 75",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "basurero",
        back: "garbage collector",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F4uNfaLho0",
      },
      {
        front: "borrador",
        back: "draft",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VJ167uARIp",
      },
      {
        front: "borradores",
        back: "erasers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X0gAPfdsdS",
      },
      {
        front: "básica",
        back: "basic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HM6LexX2ed",
      },
      {
        front: "básicas",
        back: "basic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jMcjdx53nU",
      },
      {
        front: "básico",
        back: "essential",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "80UayLFR3L",
      },
      {
        front: "básicos",
        back: "basic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2IYWIbyI74",
      },
      {
        front: "corta",
        back: "short",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "761z8PzkaX",
      },
      {
        front: "cortan",
        back: "they cut",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ENZrjM09Pn",
      },
      {
        front: "cortaré",
        back: "i will cut",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5VIeeVG9Xf",
      },
      {
        front: "corto",
        back: "short",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wqGE75bfUA",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadrados",
        back: "squares",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kGISbnRUqK",
      },
      {
        front: "curso",
        back: "grade",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6T2TyFeSTd",
      },
      {
        front: "deletrear",
        back: "spell out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u6NHSdrRgr",
      },
      {
        front: "espacio",
        back: "space",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lgDVuWxQ9p",
      },
      {
        front: "espacios",
        back: "spaces",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KorOaiJ45C",
      },
      {
        front: "estantería",
        back: "shelving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bP2yb3M6UL",
      },
      {
        front: "incluso",
        back: "even",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FzBs4zOeXh",
      },
      {
        front: "matemáticas",
        back: "math",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gy1VkmLUSv",
      },
      {
        front: "me apuro",
        back: "I hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yu9m6gSuqv",
      },
      {
        front: "medias",
        back: "tights",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "COQ2cPBVBP",
      },
      {
        front: "menos",
        back: "less",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "biulqmnXWW",
      },
      {
        front: "nos apuramos",
        back: "we hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZG7tvPEEtz",
      },
      {
        front: "ortografía",
        back: "orthography",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VIsVyLLcsr",
      },
      {
        front: "principiante",
        back: "beginner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JNm4WAXAe8",
      },
      {
        front: "principiantes",
        back: "beginners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PK8RXYayUK",
      },
      {
        front: "reprobamos",
        back: "we fail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sgGHim688L",
      },
      {
        front: "reprobar",
        back: "fail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KdAkCclOVF",
      },
      {
        front: "reprobé",
        back: "I failed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NUpZsXbK2b",
      },
      {
        front: "reprobó",
        back: "reprobate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VFH7qbHw73",
      },
      {
        front: "reprueban",
        back: "fail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tZ3VRlqnec",
      },
      {
        front: "repruebas",
        back: "fail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KOLOXTYP2c",
      },
      {
        front: "repruebo",
        back: "I fail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rIVoMvKsKl",
      },
      {
        front: "se apura",
        back: "he hurries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lv3TWAJAbT",
      },
      {
        front: "se apuran",
        back: "they hurry up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kL8mZim8ve",
      },
      {
        front: "segundo",
        back: "second",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rv7Y1zON0J",
      },
      {
        front: "segundos",
        back: "seconds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I8MiydyVwV",
      },
      {
        front: "si",
        back: "Yeah",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e7qCeQCmg4",
      },
      {
        front: "suficiente",
        back: "enough",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eKyS24t46Y",
      },
      {
        front: "suficientes",
        back: "enough",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xUsMWImJAi",
      },
      {
        front: "suma",
        back: "addition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Go1yBqWJg8",
      },
      {
        front: "te apuras",
        back: "hurry up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GV0N8aHfn7",
      },
      {
        front: "tijeras",
        back: "pair of scissors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qd1qWSe8rT",
      },
      {
        front: "vocabulario",
        back: "vocabulary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ykeGT1GTCN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "el7kqpzJ1o",
    title: "Unit 75",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adivinaremos",
        back: "we will guess",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OqBHKDvMok",
      },
      {
        front: "cierto",
        back: "certain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ff2FmDohuF",
      },
      {
        front: "comer",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WVyCQE7DdN",
      },
      {
        front: "comeremos",
        back: "we will eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MbtZeHKMOV",
      },
      {
        front: "comerá",
        back: "will eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VLNlKH9RYy",
      },
      {
        front: "comerán",
        back: "will eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SbpMJQVXph",
      },
      {
        front: "comerás",
        back: "you will eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wxNg0hQK7P",
      },
      {
        front: "comeré",
        back: "I will eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qkfuFdyssP",
      },
      {
        front: "competencia",
        back: "competence",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4KFF61ntCz",
      },
      {
        front: "competencias",
        back: "skills",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B0uUB70LTW",
      },
      {
        front: "de moda",
        back: "Fashion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mJ0zuzjtqB",
      },
      {
        front: "de todas formas",
        back: "anyway",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qWfFre0TFm",
      },
      {
        front: "eléctrica",
        back: "electrical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3x259uG3ql",
      },
      {
        front: "eléctricas",
        back: "electrical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UQ04jQRv3G",
      },
      {
        front: "eléctrico",
        back: "electric",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xcHvhfYoqY",
      },
      {
        front: "eléctricos",
        back: "electrical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kHxhDxbbSp",
      },
      {
        front: "en realidad",
        back: "in reality",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NHh8gAeH9s",
      },
      {
        front: "error",
        back: "mistake",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KMuH0MTSPa",
      },
      {
        front: "errores",
        back: "mistakes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XuoAvJSLpl",
      },
      {
        front: "estar",
        back: "to be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zrKRgIKxgX",
      },
      {
        front: "estaremos",
        back: "we will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bsodMCVhZa",
      },
      {
        front: "estará",
        back: "will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FtEjdHdy2P",
      },
      {
        front: "estarán",
        back: "they will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2GgtOxJpMI",
      },
      {
        front: "estarás",
        back: "you will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OrInrW1xY4",
      },
      {
        front: "estaré",
        back: "I will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JfPMG7ABWn",
      },
      {
        front: "etcétera",
        back: "and so on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GHySCoHLAX",
      },
      {
        front: "finalmente",
        back: "Finally",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lrGp61pV9x",
      },
      {
        front: "futuro",
        back: "future",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5we2xMnAP1",
      },
      {
        front: "ganador",
        back: "winner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eU7AvhNT0t",
      },
      {
        front: "ganadora",
        back: "winner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CRQwRsz09f",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar",
        back: "to talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2o4gcIM1ID",
      },
      {
        front: "hablaré",
        back: "I'll talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OyhqBJXC47",
      },
      {
        front: "irán",
        back: "Iran",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3gsBZa4FWk",
      },
      {
        front: "irás",
        back: "you will go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZPjhKkCzBo",
      },
      {
        front: "mejorar",
        back: "improve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "adxv7XPgn8",
      },
      {
        front: "mejoraremos",
        back: "we will improve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AVpXD6SxtI",
      },
      {
        front: "mejorará",
        back: "upgrade to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "11M7vKeQL5",
      },
      {
        front: "mejorarán",
        back: "will improve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TN0DH61RBN",
      },
      {
        front: "nos volveremos",
        back: "we will return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fuZhB7rgjZ",
      },
      {
        front: "objetivo",
        back: "target",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nAdb4fm3kd",
      },
      {
        front: "objetivos",
        back: "objectives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zrp3rhYbcZ",
      },
      {
        front: "posiblemente",
        back: "possibly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "81LGwVUCMy",
      },
      {
        front: "se volverá",
        back: "It will become in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jHQV7rQb5U",
      },
      {
        front: "se volverán",
        back: "they will become",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IEYnvsjzfv",
      },
      {
        front: "seremos",
        back: "we will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BTKuNf6DjT",
      },
      {
        front: "será",
        back: "will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4uJX4wltJ0",
      },
      {
        front: "serán",
        back: "will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CN5xDg8X1i",
      },
      {
        front: "serás",
        back: "you will",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UcxZ5qxxSv",
      },
      {
        front: "seré",
        back: "I will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cgKkwpLDw0",
      },
      {
        front: "suerte",
        back: "lucky",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bl40XYnlOv",
      },
      {
        front: "tal vez",
        back: "maybe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xlvaUT1Yno",
      },
      {
        front: "te volverás",
        back: "you will become",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SXL4ZoPGHq",
      },
      {
        front: "trata",
        back: "treats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RPyEvz5pJ8",
      },
      {
        front: "trataba",
        back: "tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yo5xi7ki0X",
      },
      {
        front: "tratando",
        back: "treating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9i5fmncoIQ",
      },
      {
        front: "trataremos",
        back: "we will try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OjpzxvyQ1g",
      },
      {
        front: "tratarán",
        back: "will try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zbHLtkkvxL",
      },
      {
        front: "tratarás",
        back: "you will try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zupj4dRUYF",
      },
      {
        front: "trato",
        back: "deal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4yFCvocNqd",
      },
      {
        front: "título",
        back: "title",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WAzFE4ZqGe",
      },
      {
        front: "títulos",
        back: "Titles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u3eArpJva1",
      },
      {
        front: "vivir",
        back: "to live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q7CmnkcXGv",
      },
      {
        front: "vivirás",
        back: "you will live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1EIofAhS1L",
      },
      {
        front: "viviré",
        back: "I will live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LFU2VBRc9C",
      },
      {
        front: "volverme",
        back: "turn me back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "44vNsx6BRc",
      },
      {
        front: "volvernos",
        back: "turn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F8aj2w1fcT",
      },
      {
        front: "volverse",
        back: "become",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GJRmcnqhIM",
      },
      {
        front: "volverte",
        back: "turn you back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8wa5fnxy9",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "r60WiUm0mV",
    title: "Unit 76",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "anillo",
        back: "ring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s5gnfiucPJ",
      },
      {
        front: "anillos",
        back: "rings",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WUsgl5eoj0",
      },
      {
        front: "apagaba",
        back: "turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wSF6lh7yEL",
      },
      {
        front: "apagaban",
        back: "turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G6dNj9Zdob",
      },
      {
        front: "apagar",
        back: "to turn off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z1UEKkiH0Q",
      },
      {
        front: "apagábamos",
        back: "we turned off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZUS4fnpGgp",
      },
      {
        front: "atractivo",
        back: "attractive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qFGvibsL5x",
      },
      {
        front: "atractivos",
        back: "attractive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PZH2DulW57",
      },
      {
        front: "beberemos",
        back: "we will drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0Kpw2VD5Er",
      },
      {
        front: "beberá",
        back: "will drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cxFwtqd20X",
      },
      {
        front: "beberán",
        back: "they will drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jYsD3owXFo",
      },
      {
        front: "beberás",
        back: "you will drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RNtbPETwMk",
      },
      {
        front: "beberé",
        back: "I will drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "57FMwNVq3w",
      },
      {
        front: "bebía",
        back: "drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DRW3YJlYpP",
      },
      {
        front: "bebíamos",
        back: "we drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pWBfM1TvOZ",
      },
      {
        front: "bebían",
        back: "drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TmmBsNqSJk",
      },
      {
        front: "bebías",
        back: "drank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oi87BpM2v0",
      },
      {
        front: "cantaba",
        back: "sang",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DVF1NjXcpf",
      },
      {
        front: "cantabas",
        back: "you sang",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "COCcx7uAfC",
      },
      {
        front: "conducir",
        back: "to drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SEDK0JcLgj",
      },
      {
        front: "doble",
        back: "double",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WrKjvRGxen",
      },
      {
        front: "dorada",
        back: "golden",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0GLHBIMqCF",
      },
      {
        front: "doradas",
        back: "golden",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4llhs88ui2",
      },
      {
        front: "dorado",
        back: "golden",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w08ScH9q6M",
      },
      {
        front: "encendía",
        back: "turned on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u8QeYIroB9",
      },
      {
        front: "encendíamos",
        back: "we lit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CDLZQCH1BN",
      },
      {
        front: "encendían",
        back: "lit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rpNSZEm2Oj",
      },
      {
        front: "encendías",
        back: "you lit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hgg4KoEZDK",
      },
      {
        front: "entraba",
        back: "came in",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J6HHK2Ymvh",
      },
      {
        front: "entrábamos",
        back: "we entered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IxIXOpwoPP",
      },
      {
        front: "enviamos",
        back: "we send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fi3nBfV65u",
      },
      {
        front: "enviar",
        back: "send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TVV0hALEBV",
      },
      {
        front: "envié",
        back: "I sent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qYDIgo9vRH",
      },
      {
        front: "escuchábamos",
        back: "we listened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eTwkZmw9Jo",
      },
      {
        front: "esperaba",
        back: "I expected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8hNVzv9W7x",
      },
      {
        front: "esquiaba",
        back: "skied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wDSxBUHQFg",
      },
      {
        front: "esquiaban",
        back: "they skied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f6gs6np2mo",
      },
      {
        front: "esquiábamos",
        back: "we skied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Os6hPepeTY",
      },
      {
        front: "fuerte",
        back: "strong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FTprJIIJw7",
      },
      {
        front: "fumaba",
        back: "used to smoke",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FGQakOUdjZ",
      },
      {
        front: "fumó",
        back: "smoked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O5iSaRk6Vf",
      },
      {
        front: "gastamos",
        back: "We spend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r8qtbQb0Nt",
      },
      {
        front: "gastaste",
        back: "you spent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ESQRHHPmfI",
      },
      {
        front: "gasto",
        back: "spent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s103G3TdAf",
      },
      {
        front: "gastó",
        back: "spent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5EJar2zSaN",
      },
      {
        front: "me acostaba",
        back: "I went to bed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NPvyVm6TlD",
      },
      {
        front: "me acostaré",
        back: "i will lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qlq0KWY6WD",
      },
      {
        front: "me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sYmesXel79",
      },
      {
        front: "fui",
        back: "I left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QAxfYOrURP",
      },
      {
        front: "me iba",
        back: "I was leaving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SWIB8tGaVI",
      },
      {
        front: "me iré",
        back: "I will go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "82WdRFdsMZ",
      },
      {
        front: "menos mal",
        back: "goodness",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UXGj3uzfXZ",
      },
      {
        front: "nadando",
        back: "swimming",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "njytjwQqa0",
      },
      {
        front: "nadábamos",
        back: "we swam",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XebqFrj246",
      },
      {
        front: "nos acostaremos",
        back: "we will lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ci1dkIY8oQ",
      },
      {
        front: "nos iremos",
        back: "we will go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nzxhi4GtaS",
      },
      {
        front: "rap",
        back: "rap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yXaGya7vQM",
      },
      {
        front: "real",
        back: "real",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E5rS9Ei7HJ",
      },
      {
        front: "reales",
        back: "real",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1ZSNFYdHVo",
      },
      {
        front: "rock",
        back: "rock",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IBz931Fhhb",
      },
      {
        front: "se acostaban",
        back: "they slept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EPzbYHqcs7",
      },
      {
        front: "se fue",
        back: "he went away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uVvM9USuCN",
      },
      {
        front: "se iba",
        back: "was going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9lCGXI2Ye2",
      },
      {
        front: "se iban",
        back: "They were leaving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ffegabl3Hq",
      },
      {
        front: "se irá",
        back: "it will go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "14ukgqRLJy",
      },
      {
        front: "te acostabas",
        back: "you lay down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i5tnmjvhXQ",
      },
      {
        front: "te acostarás",
        back: "you will lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PYsCimUEdO",
      },
      {
        front: "te fuiste",
        back: "you left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0nTSxrwZ29",
      },
      {
        front: "te ibas",
        back: "you were leaving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QIrZ0WORA3",
      },
      {
        front: "te irás",
        back: "you will leave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1hrBZpmFX7",
      },
      {
        front: "verdadera",
        back: "true",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eU9zGmNooS",
      },
      {
        front: "verdaderas",
        back: "true",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p7PZUglAHZ",
      },
      {
        front: "verdadero",
        back: "true",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fMplrnPT7k",
      },
      {
        front: "verdaderos",
        back: "true",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BGA0ecFBN3",
      },
      {
        front: "vestir",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kjYQV7V7oY",
      },
      {
        front: "vestíbulo",
        back: "lobby",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1rRQ6FGypW",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "fKNZI8tCOs",
    title: "Unit 77",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "commands1",
        back: "commands1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iwIbqieaGA",
      },
      {
        front: "commands2",
        back: "commands2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yds358N2ip",
      },
      {
        front: "commands3",
        back: "commands3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZSiCfnJNnf",
      },
      {
        front: "commands",
        back: "commands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BxYGqZVkfL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "VKq7QkAWXA",
    title: "Unit 77",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "almohadas",
        back: "pillows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DLx3VQ4ZzY",
      },
      {
        front: "alquiler",
        back: "rental",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tTK1MyPWy5",
      },
      {
        front: "ascensor",
        back: "lift",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K6Vyf3frZx",
      },
      {
        front: "botas montañeras",
        back: "mountaineering boots",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Co4YYi7sxv",
      },
      {
        front: "cancelaciones",
        back: "cancellations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vOzMglE6qm",
      },
      {
        front: "cancelación",
        back: "cancellation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PmuGEMCAC7",
      },
      {
        front: "cinturones",
        back: "belts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zti0eZ0AJy",
      },
      {
        front: "cinturón",
        back: "belt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uAbtIfmj8v",
      },
      {
        front: "contactar",
        back: "contact",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hZOwZACCo1",
      },
      {
        front: "contactaron",
        back: "contacted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SLpTk6BFuQ",
      },
      {
        front: "contacté",
        back: "contacted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w5TxZu7yyQ",
      },
      {
        front: "contactó",
        back: "Contact",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "19Ch2AHz6y",
      },
      {
        front: "crucé",
        back: "crossing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Hps2cyMutV",
      },
      {
        front: "cruzar",
        back: "Cross",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F4MvcTPN06",
      },
      {
        front: "cruzaron",
        back: "crossed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TbPSHkxjBB",
      },
      {
        front: "cruzaste",
        back: "you crossed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oPU0x4DmOQ",
      },
      {
        front: "efectivo",
        back: "cash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sNL3XvSS3e",
      },
      {
        front: "escalar",
        back: "climb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UAtE6eyBDv",
      },
      {
        front: "escalaremos",
        back: "we will climb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CkLFDMFX8r",
      },
      {
        front: "escalaron",
        back: "they climbed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l7cyaa7EVa",
      },
      {
        front: "escalaste",
        back: "you climbed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SaCySgzpQz",
      },
      {
        front: "este",
        back: "East",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TWiKUsz07b",
      },
      {
        front: "extranjero",
        back: "Foreign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MiwVdrzSMB",
      },
      {
        front: "extranjeros",
        back: "foreign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n7CQDFc4rf",
      },
      {
        front: "fila",
        back: "line",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GKb8gO4Gi3",
      },
      {
        front: "indicaciones",
        back: "indications",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9S7i2jAUIw",
      },
      {
        front: "manera",
        back: "way",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pCgKsb4vBU",
      },
      {
        front: "metro",
        back: "meter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOZJsqd6At",
      },
      {
        front: "neumático",
        back: "tire",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zbdx3q7GXt",
      },
      {
        front: "oeste",
        back: "West",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0A5ldZDZW6",
      },
      {
        front: "perderemos",
        back: "we will lose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jiAsLXQD9s",
      },
      {
        front: "perdimos",
        back: "we lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N97rxg15Fh",
      },
      {
        front: "perdió",
        back: "lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OHiXScluvl",
      },
      {
        front: "perdí",
        back: "I missed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eWDjfNuTIH",
      },
      {
        front: "plata",
        back: "silver",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xnpagzsKem",
      },
      {
        front: "sube",
        back: "goes up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3KCdyKQfcL",
      },
      {
        front: "subimos",
        back: "we climb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MRB7DJELB7",
      },
      {
        front: "subir",
        back: "increase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VOyz7RqlHb",
      },
      {
        front: "tenemos prisa",
        back: "We are in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NVmBh7UX6M",
      },
      {
        front: "tengo prisa",
        back: "I'm in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OtZubnZkAp",
      },
      {
        front: "tenía prisa",
        back: "I was in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T227tBEdw4",
      },
      {
        front: "tenías prisa",
        back: "you were in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "01QQBLcCna",
      },
      {
        front: "tiene prisa",
        back: "in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XEvcrMFVml",
      },
      {
        front: "tienen prisa",
        back: "they are in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cLVa3KrYxT",
      },
      {
        front: "tienes prisa",
        back: "hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "evE3EribNl",
      },
      {
        front: "tráfico",
        back: "traffic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9HscUVlyln",
      },
      {
        front: "volamos",
        back: "we fly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W6lzGHT3Hk",
      },
      {
        front: "vuela",
        back: "Flying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RrZ6vKAqP9",
      },
      {
        front: "vuelan",
        back: "they fly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C6MoWmsXq2",
      },
      {
        front: "vuelo",
        back: "flight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kffL1sXK1V",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "dF0bqvAWgd",
    title: "Unit 78",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "agradecer",
        back: "to thank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "27ixdH3VKT",
      },
      {
        front: "agradezco",
        back: "I appreciate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zIJHoUQS59",
      },
      {
        front: "aviso",
        back: "warning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mp8ewSzRXy",
      },
      {
        front: "bébela",
        back: "drink it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gZJ5gOAVew",
      },
      {
        front: "bébelo",
        back: "drink it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3U9o5MaWj6",
      },
      {
        front: "bébelos",
        back: "drink them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8pN8uHdpUq",
      },
      {
        front: "conduzco",
        back: "I drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l4hjkuM3zG",
      },
      {
        front: "corredor",
        back: "runner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uuZAcw4xED",
      },
      {
        front: "crema",
        back: "cream",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zpeiEQbkSI",
      },
      {
        front: "dame",
        back: "give to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S0zwTr28ZA",
      },
      {
        front: "desea",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H2hsJxJr2D",
      },
      {
        front: "desean",
        back: "wish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QwhrC31fZf",
      },
      {
        front: "deseas",
        back: "you want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qo7Os1fM0B",
      },
      {
        front: "deseo",
        back: "wish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CqSeEHcncp",
      },
      {
        front: "deseos",
        back: "wishes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pbgH3Cu7Rd",
      },
      {
        front: "dime",
        back: "tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "10gaD58GAc",
      },
      {
        front: "dámela",
        back: "give it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GVk3CILEQU",
      },
      {
        front: "dámelas",
        back: "give them to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hn6U3rrBCU",
      },
      {
        front: "dámelo",
        back: "give it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "28zZmLLmQj",
      },
      {
        front: "dámelos",
        back: "give them to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qWit5XEMhx",
      },
      {
        front: "dímelo",
        back: "tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dG1u6LMb5B",
      },
      {
        front: "guardar",
        back: "save",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QtZF4bDGbN",
      },
      {
        front: "guardas",
        back: "you keep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZL99NG6muI",
      },
      {
        front: "guardaste",
        back: "you saved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8IvZ2XVich",
      },
      {
        front: "guardo",
        back: "I keep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UNx8AFZUEt",
      },
      {
        front: "guardó",
        back: "saved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CJEFcWK44L",
      },
      {
        front: "hacia",
        back: "towards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DimAETCb6t",
      },
      {
        front: "llené",
        back: "I filled",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BRD5ybmkfo",
      },
      {
        front: "límpiala",
        back: "clean it up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l3e1aE5lXa",
      },
      {
        front: "límpialas",
        back: "clean them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4Xurcpdfth",
      },
      {
        front: "límpialo",
        back: "clean it up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d9A8fJdoEF",
      },
      {
        front: "límpialos",
        back: "clean them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "71MWZC1c80",
      },
      {
        front: "me puede decir",
        back: "can you tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VCqVMhaic4",
      },
      {
        front: "me puedes decir",
        back: "can you tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sBLp1tjfZ8",
      },
      {
        front: "ofrecer",
        back: "to offer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kbhc5wAZY1",
      },
      {
        front: "ofrecieron",
        back: "offered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gysvLqg6wf",
      },
      {
        front: "ofrezco",
        back: "I offer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bok9pDtqOr",
      },
      {
        front: "pedir prestado",
        back: "borrow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wedBzbOcLM",
      },
      {
        front: "pásamela",
        back: "pass it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L6SToDSdkT",
      },
      {
        front: "pásamelas",
        back: "pass them to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kAgsd1FDjC",
      },
      {
        front: "pásamelo",
        back: "pass it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4UvUueGIl5",
      },
      {
        front: "pásamelos",
        back: "pass them to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BHDmTQFlns",
      },
      {
        front: "tocaba",
        back: "touched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YyPm6kfuy2",
      },
      {
        front: "tocaste",
        back: "you touched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gol7jEdJGI",
      },
      {
        front: "toqué",
        back: "touch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yT1YVkP3SS",
      },
      {
        front: "tráemela",
        back: "bring it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ff0RfMdPPZ",
      },
      {
        front: "tráemelas",
        back: "bring them to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "czBPMGbClZ",
      },
      {
        front: "tráemelo",
        back: "bring it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "65Rm5Q5zMn",
      },
      {
        front: "tráemelos",
        back: "bring them to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sxPez3q1bI",
      },
      {
        front: "uva",
        back: "grape",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WDhO7oGMCa",
      },
      {
        front: "uvas",
        back: "grapes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uXkAumbLmT",
      },
      {
        front: "visita",
        back: "visit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SF4odapaBP",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "gEUHVX8j9p",
    title: "Unit 79",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ajo",
        back: "Garlic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tY5aHE4D8z",
      },
      {
        front: "asar",
        back: "roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8DBR503eL1",
      },
      {
        front: "asaremos",
        back: "we will roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nwNVuM0a97",
      },
      {
        front: "asará",
        back: "will roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B5u97YykV3",
      },
      {
        front: "asarán",
        back: "they will roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G3Rt2Y2pLE",
      },
      {
        front: "asarás",
        back: "you will roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rY9gTXKwP8",
      },
      {
        front: "asaré",
        back: "I will roast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m4x8HL3jYP",
      },
      {
        front: "desde",
        back: "since",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ICYNnaJ3In",
      },
      {
        front: "el uno al otro",
        back: "each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gOaGKfGwWL",
      },
      {
        front: "en línea",
        back: "online",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RPObwUUhL0",
      },
      {
        front: "enviamos",
        back: "we send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ynCihK5yGb",
      },
      {
        front: "envía",
        back: "send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "F7ENk8XCcF",
      },
      {
        front: "envías",
        back: "you send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9OY1D15LMO",
      },
      {
        front: "envío",
        back: "Shipping",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FMrpD7KjCi",
      },
      {
        front: "escenario",
        back: "scenery",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GyIVf09ZYw",
      },
      {
        front: "esquiamos",
        back: "we ski",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fpOXstxx5H",
      },
      {
        front: "esquía",
        back: "ski",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fcpTbqnZ4E",
      },
      {
        front: "esquían",
        back: "they ski",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0DU6TucN2O",
      },
      {
        front: "esquías",
        back: "you ski",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VAzd5fkTU3",
      },
      {
        front: "esquío",
        back: "I ski",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1s3aUtItXi",
      },
      {
        front: "felicitaciones",
        back: "Congratulations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZoyFC12aD1",
      },
      {
        front: "instrumento",
        back: "instrument",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S3Dfmmvg0T",
      },
      {
        front: "instrumentos",
        back: "instruments",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pygm6RsOte",
      },
      {
        front: "me cae",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NnPLnXmKQU",
      },
      {
        front: "bien",
        back: "I like him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xQviyov72M",
      },
      {
        front: "me cae mal",
        back: "I dislike",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lQS2SwkhLY",
      },
      {
        front: "mejor",
        back: "better",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "upPQckVukS",
      },
      {
        front: "musical",
        back: "musical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kr59hYSerA",
      },
      {
        front: "musicales",
        back: "musicals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4fWOBCdMU2",
      },
      {
        front: "nos abrazamos",
        back: "We hug",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kGWHwEonub",
      },
      {
        front: "nos amamos",
        back: "we love each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kpu9Fe0jla",
      },
      {
        front: "nos ayudamos",
        back: "we help us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e8zRT9ijj4",
      },
      {
        front: "nos besamos",
        back: "we kissed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BaJFmN3axd",
      },
      {
        front: "nos besaremos",
        back: "we will kiss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qYLQnMxZiA",
      },
      {
        front: "nos conocemos",
        back: "we know each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xbRWBxOJGB",
      },
      {
        front: "nos escribimos",
        back: "we write to each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MCLkTxA6qu",
      },
      {
        front: "nos odiamos",
        back: "we hate each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hU3zxp4ITW",
      },
      {
        front: "parlantes",
        back: "speakers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vjkkJdNmC0",
      },
      {
        front: "pertenecer",
        back: "to belong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HrOtMP7RN7",
      },
      {
        front: "pertenezco",
        back: "i belong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YShnhDPAJD",
      },
      {
        front: "picando",
        back: "stinging",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yDO6Q4onBl",
      },
      {
        front: "picar",
        back: "sting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9Hf7trW3u7",
      },
      {
        front: "rebanada",
        back: "slice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S5SttYrKNm",
      },
      {
        front: "rebanadas",
        back: "slices",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9CwW7qNQCC",
      },
      {
        front: "rica",
        back: "delicious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IufR9s2HF2",
      },
      {
        front: "ricas",
        back: "rich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3CT8HwCuJX",
      },
      {
        front: "rico",
        back: "rich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pokFk4SPql",
      },
      {
        front: "se abrazan",
        back: "they embrace",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i2VfTeCyJC",
      },
      {
        front: "se abrazaron",
        back: "They embraced",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9xFh5Q92le",
      },
      {
        front: "se amaban",
        back: "they loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ex0wWgjdY",
      },
      {
        front: "se aman",
        back: "they love each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m3mV9UPozb",
      },
      {
        front: "se amaron",
        back: "they loved each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hsGLuArn80",
      },
      {
        front: "se ayudan",
        back: "they help each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k0MAaNtDoy",
      },
      {
        front: "se ayudaron",
        back: "they helped each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H0bNj9mhAI",
      },
      {
        front: "se besaron",
        back: "they kissed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XeQ621AVL4",
      },
      {
        front: "se conocen",
        back: "they know each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8HUyfzhGty",
      },
      {
        front: "se escriben",
        back: "are written",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sVLOaFgztB",
      },
      {
        front: "se odian",
        back: "they hate each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "idGWjRnDIh",
      },
      {
        front: "se odiaron",
        back: "they hated each other",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ETnw7CPscL",
      },
      {
        front: "soul",
        back: "soul",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vd7njvb1oL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jARJkBm9xN",
    title: "Unit 79",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acamparemos",
        back: "we will camp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Zozb4tBR0",
      },
      {
        front: "acamparán",
        back: "they will camp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x2oTPBoYYo",
      },
      {
        front: "acamparé",
        back: "I will camp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XaG7DPfdmk",
      },
      {
        front: "aire",
        back: "air",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dRcuEc1x7r",
      },
      {
        front: "cielo",
        back: "sky",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GtnNrZyfiE",
      },
      {
        front: "conducir",
        back: "to drive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZPAXN9EgTQ",
      },
      {
        front: "conduje",
        back: "Drove",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p1EU7Cpu1i",
      },
      {
        front: "cubre",
        back: "it covers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "okAdGmPTmm",
      },
      {
        front: "cubrieron",
        back: "covered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ot7zCEkgPS",
      },
      {
        front: "cubrió",
        back: "covered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9EGfbJblhd",
      },
      {
        front: "descansaremos",
        back: "we will rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bgMzWdSUDG",
      },
      {
        front: "descansarán",
        back: "they will rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LK51Q1InOW",
      },
      {
        front: "descansaré",
        back: "I will rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "haGNp6A4lr",
      },
      {
        front: "especialmente",
        back: "especially",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L5egveOHy3",
      },
      {
        front: "grados",
        back: "degrees",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Uaajtwvu8N",
      },
      {
        front: "impermeable",
        back: "raincoat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mTpiOAc6GG",
      },
      {
        front: "inusual",
        back: "unusual",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cAj8qciV3C",
      },
      {
        front: "llover",
        back: "rain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tXe56vj6Mb",
      },
      {
        front: "llovía",
        back: "it was raining",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NEOuwxHlr7",
      },
      {
        front: "me quito",
        back: "I take off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "58Z2Vu2iJD",
      },
      {
        front: "navegaremos",
        back: "we will sail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QFk2ds59B2",
      },
      {
        front: "navegará",
        back: "will navigate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GynrioRO3X",
      },
      {
        front: "navegarán",
        back: "they will navigate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O38DYeVQQz",
      },
      {
        front: "navegaré",
        back: "i will sail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QOdQVZ3zR6",
      },
      {
        front: "nevaba",
        back: "it was snowing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hmBDvdS3C7",
      },
      {
        front: "nevar",
        back: "to snow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t4OLf2GheD",
      },
      {
        front: "nevará",
        back: "it will snow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BnJIqISmm9",
      },
      {
        front: "niebla",
        back: "fog",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K2Vr0FXCI1",
      },
      {
        front: "nos quitamos",
        back: "we take off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ISBV9WM0oJ",
      },
      {
        front: "nube",
        back: "cloud",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QQnvBi2SGn",
      },
      {
        front: "pantalones cortos",
        back: "Shorts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IRgmL4CVGx",
      },
      {
        front: "patada",
        back: "kick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fpJlvYhXGK",
      },
      {
        front: "patadas",
        back: "kicks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fm9TvdKAeM",
      },
      {
        front: "pescamos",
        back: "we fish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d4rfW3LNOI",
      },
      {
        front: "pescó",
        back: "fished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fj2AjiWRV5",
      },
      {
        front: "pesqué",
        back: "I fished",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vqkFhc5KC5",
      },
      {
        front: "quitarme",
        back: "take me away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2u4XW7lRKQ",
      },
      {
        front: "quitarnos",
        back: "take away from us",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zEFGFefkDt",
      },
      {
        front: "quitarse",
        back: "take off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zbAEHLi8WM",
      },
      {
        front: "quitarte",
        back: "take away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T5a4T54o4n",
      },
      {
        front: "quizás",
        back: "maybe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4i4ATUNnqL",
      },
      {
        front: "rueda",
        back: "wheel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C5LorpQsXI",
      },
      {
        front: "ruidosa",
        back: "noisy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RyuQOkzzMZ",
      },
      {
        front: "ruidoso",
        back: "noisy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aOVhnfbScK",
      },
      {
        front: "salta",
        back: "jump",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A6Cdnt81lT",
      },
      {
        front: "saltan",
        back: "they jump",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "27xwf7Edf2",
      },
      {
        front: "salto",
        back: "jump",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TLqel8Nimf",
      },
      {
        front: "se quita",
        back: "it is removed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mh1Te97LI3",
      },
      {
        front: "se quitan",
        back: "are removed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ajYO7gIOnX",
      },
      {
        front: "temperatura",
        back: "temperature",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YezsgTDysn",
      },
      {
        front: "tormenta",
        back: "storm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ca4nP3fVH",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "g35Sk0yYrS",
    title: "Unit 80",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a la venta",
        back: "for sale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vk7ZeEzFvo",
      },
      {
        front: "agregar",
        back: "add",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6tZu3CHQBB",
      },
      {
        front: "agregué",
        back: "I added",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LG5zt9qujB",
      },
      {
        front: "colección",
        back: "collection",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uWj2ESUyW4",
      },
      {
        front: "costo",
        back: "cost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OPvLvOTaJf",
      },
      {
        front: "descuento",
        back: "discount",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gyUSrtYzKz",
      },
      {
        front: "devolver",
        back: "return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4Lqh5axzUR",
      },
      {
        front: "escoger",
        back: "choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VfpVo21tIr",
      },
      {
        front: "escogerás",
        back: "you will choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jZVntNaOju",
      },
      {
        front: "escojo",
        back: "I choose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MZ7KmXEf6E",
      },
      {
        front: "gustarían",
        back: "would like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vAyHAOL6c7",
      },
      {
        front: "lana",
        back: "wool",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZcSiCfEsRq",
      },
      {
        front: "me lo quedo",
        back: "I'll take it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T4wQwtZkVh",
      },
      {
        front: "me quedaré con",
        back: "i will stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ppxjXE5P9N",
      },
      {
        front: "me quedo con",
        back: "I prefer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2hiKKBzyAC",
      },
      {
        front: "mezclar",
        back: "Mix",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wYy7Sl89Y4",
      },
      {
        front: "mitad",
        back: "half",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hrEwET8Z4D",
      },
      {
        front: "nos quedamos con",
        back: "we stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5cTph96LkS",
      },
      {
        front: "nos quedaremos con",
        back: "we will stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aZqCmAieYg",
      },
      {
        front: "oferta",
        back: "offer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7M2rRcRMv1",
      },
      {
        front: "pagué",
        back: "i paid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "br8gQRP4Tq",
      },
      {
        front: "pc",
        back: "pc",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "twR2Zpg83U",
      },
      {
        front: "propina",
        back: "tip",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h2E3aDsLYx",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarme con",
        back: "stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JhYUIjDZxQ",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarse con",
        back: "stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x0pr72Tlbc",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarte con",
        back: "stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwdCtLvi3y",
      },
      {
        front: "qué le gustaría para empezar",
        back: "what would you like to start",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oJ6pJJ8tXq",
      },
      {
        front: "qué le traigo",
        back: "what do I bring you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z4k3xYT8Zd",
      },
      {
        front: "qué te traigo",
        back: "what can i bring you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4yA6FMajMB",
      },
      {
        front: "salchicha",
        back: "hot dog",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ECLa9w5MKM",
      },
      {
        front: "salchichas",
        back: "sausages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nTLf97ieal",
      },
      {
        front: "se queda con",
        back: "you stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MYxtFrSQCe",
      },
      {
        front: "se quedaron con",
        back: "they stayed with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IherdpR7S4",
      },
      {
        front: "se quedó con",
        back: "he stayed with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PisTlf1Q5e",
      },
      {
        front: "segura",
        back: "safe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ue16DaINhr",
      },
      {
        front: "sin embargo",
        back: "however",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ydTgp6jjCT",
      },
      {
        front: "suficiente",
        back: "enough",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uqg1HbLDUI",
      },
      {
        front: "te quedarás con",
        back: "you will stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s0QCSfr9NL",
      },
      {
        front: "te quedas con",
        back: "you stay with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XiKBdJ1DIf",
      },
      {
        front: "trozo",
        back: "piece",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VOUe6LQy21",
      },
      {
        front: "trozos",
        back: "chunks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f0Mes3RreR",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "IPV4xNfiT4",
    title: "Unit 81",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acompañaremos",
        back: "we will accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9waCxm9dEw",
      },
      {
        front: "acompañará",
        back: "will accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eoIEsBZTwS",
      },
      {
        front: "acompañarán",
        back: "will accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OAq3jRRtvc",
      },
      {
        front: "acompañaré",
        back: "I will accompany",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "euAwC8wpFV",
      },
      {
        front: "anda",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JsO4SKE6Yp",
      },
      {
        front: "andamos",
        back: "we walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gLBWoHRsGE",
      },
      {
        front: "andan",
        back: "they walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rzenWj8VvE",
      },
      {
        front: "andar",
        back: "walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B6qZfx4MDM",
      },
      {
        front: "carrera",
        back: "career",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TACRDp9ho2",
      },
      {
        front: "clic",
        back: "click",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ckOiWNhTKZ",
      },
      {
        front: "compartir",
        back: "to share",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a13In8rNwF",
      },
      {
        front: "compartiremos",
        back: "we will share",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lvJu0c96ZZ",
      },
      {
        front: "compartiré",
        back: "i will share",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rlK7BiAnCO",
      },
      {
        front: "común",
        back: "common",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dv0vO9B5KZ",
      },
      {
        front: "construiremos",
        back: "we will build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MfwSmOAMen",
      },
      {
        front: "construirá",
        back: "will build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b5vLpr6eay",
      },
      {
        front: "construirán",
        back: "will build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YfuBo466Jn",
      },
      {
        front: "construiré",
        back: "i will build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QWhXTcIw8Q",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaremos",
        back: "we will talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ujVMxOIPFa",
      },
      {
        front: "conversarán",
        back: "they will talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oysdpMGMxh",
      },
      {
        front: "conversarás",
        back: "you will talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UGLSvL6iwg",
      },
      {
        front: "conversaré",
        back: "I will talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kkkbrZZVgD",
      },
      {
        front: "diseña",
        back: "designs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E1oZL9RMlL",
      },
      {
        front: "diseñar",
        back: "design",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xbMQnoOs0G",
      },
      {
        front: "diseñé",
        back: "i designed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZBp7mJwZcM",
      },
      {
        front: "diseñó",
        back: "design",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4buTgNKUKI",
      },
      {
        front: "exactamente",
        back: "exactly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TBJAqJoepd",
      },
      {
        front: "felicidades",
        back: "Congratulations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iRln5FDW40",
      },
      {
        front: "hoja",
        back: "leaf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p9o5oFPSQ2",
      },
      {
        front: "hojas",
        back: "sheets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1ycEEbboaW",
      },
      {
        front: "igual",
        back: "Same",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8hgGHpxjOq",
      },
      {
        front: "izquierda",
        back: "left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dizdMHPRj0",
      },
      {
        front: "la parte de abajo",
        back: "the bottom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SV0VekTxiH",
      },
      {
        front: "lado",
        back: "side",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uRRFuTqaBK",
      },
      {
        front: "libre",
        back: "free",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uf80nhxbbA",
      },
      {
        front: "me tumbo",
        back: "I lie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jDCItkVhkT",
      },
      {
        front: "me veré",
        back: "I'll see myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zSZavSFjfu",
      },
      {
        front: "modelo",
        back: "model",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wNo5x2Yqx3",
      },
      {
        front: "modelos",
        back: "Models",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H4nQQnGTyi",
      },
      {
        front: "nos tumbamos",
        back: "we lay down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EZBT9Fh2tO",
      },
      {
        front: "nos veremos",
        back: "see you later",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DIvMs6YGed",
      },
      {
        front: "organicé",
        back: "organized",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lMjXi3KNC5",
      },
      {
        front: "organizar",
        back: "organize",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ve5qpDqwxs",
      },
      {
        front: "organizas",
        back: "you organize",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EcAUdtm621",
      },
      {
        front: "organizaste",
        back: "you organized",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qHw6qBBqJu",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y3qvzluYRE",
      },
      {
        front: "querremos",
        back: "we will want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qdb7tP3tyx",
      },
      {
        front: "querrá",
        back: "will want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1On2qbV59D",
      },
      {
        front: "querrán",
        back: "they will want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AQQFdThShj",
      },
      {
        front: "querrás",
        back: "you will want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oKzdDfKAqz",
      },
      {
        front: "querré",
        back: "I will want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yzmvM6PQ6j",
      },
      {
        front: "recibir",
        back: "to receive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OGz9ftebqM",
      },
      {
        front: "recibiremos",
        back: "we will receive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VyevAiof6O",
      },
      {
        front: "recibirán",
        back: "will receive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zZhrVfT5ee",
      },
      {
        front: "recibirás",
        back: "you will receive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g79CoIInNO",
      },
      {
        front: "reservar",
        back: "Reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q3b0YPKXFL",
      },
      {
        front: "reservaremos",
        back: "we will reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IzOmj8bIVd",
      },
      {
        front: "reservará",
        back: "will reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K2ciGJr6Fx",
      },
      {
        front: "reservarán",
        back: "they will reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6TIcBxlxZh",
      },
      {
        front: "reservarás",
        back: "you will reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FtChEc8sXL",
      },
      {
        front: "reservaré",
        back: "I will book",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ypsasnpn57",
      },
      {
        front: "se tumba",
        back: "lies down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fFWJWF4mmR",
      },
      {
        front: "se tumban",
        back: "they lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bKWCODH4TW",
      },
      {
        front: "se verá",
        back: "it will be seen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uFJ4o3Wsuz",
      },
      {
        front: "sino",
        back: "otherwise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dxmGmFw7Oe",
      },
      {
        front: "te verás",
        back: "you will see you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hSXdLZ8sm2",
      },
      {
        front: "tipo",
        back: "type",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z5eWObaOMD",
      },
      {
        front: "tumbarme",
        back: "lie down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZgbfFooxeo",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ZwI2nuM01k",
    title: "Unit 81",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abajo",
        back: "below",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7G5aicafwa",
      },
      {
        front: "arriba",
        back: "up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T2tltGVst1",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadrada",
        back: "square",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XPxwBBiC9c",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadradas",
        back: "square",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "80rJ4m7dWk",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadrado",
        back: "square",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dWEs2kiHIX",
      },
      {
        front: "de todas maneras",
        back: "anyway",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "av4DLK9Mz7",
      },
      {
        front: "dirán",
        back: "they will say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jGc7qbZQmb",
      },
      {
        front: "frente",
        back: "front",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GuxV5XgOWn",
      },
      {
        front: "gabinete",
        back: "cabinet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lfwnKdJLBW",
      },
      {
        front: "gabinetes",
        back: "cabinets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0S8z5gA1CF",
      },
      {
        front: "habrá",
        back: "there will be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4OYmR1GEzr",
      },
      {
        front: "harán",
        back: "they will",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DxMUI7DlIi",
      },
      {
        front: "haré",
        back: "I will do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Za0dh1fXUp",
      },
      {
        front: "importa",
        back: "matter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nN8xofBhpV",
      },
      {
        front: "importar",
        back: "to import",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GR3QecTjTg",
      },
      {
        front: "importará",
        back: "will matter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yQW36tDqCa",
      },
      {
        front: "juego",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ArBawepbRZ",
      },
      {
        front: "lavaplatos",
        back: "dishwasher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "USfQJThO9b",
      },
      {
        front: "pantalla",
        back: "screen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7d2ovUQlgR",
      },
      {
        front: "podremos",
        back: "we will can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0N4PCdhpbH",
      },
      {
        front: "podrá",
        back: "may",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bRFRJn4OAj",
      },
      {
        front: "podrán",
        back: "will be able",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mNL2vS8mPr",
      },
      {
        front: "podrás",
        back: "you can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1PV3mRHGTv",
      },
      {
        front: "podré",
        back: "I will be able",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CgEGNwD60w",
      },
      {
        front: "pondrás",
        back: "You will put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bm10c9U6Ct",
      },
      {
        front: "pondré",
        back: "I will put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L8HkkfR5vR",
      },
      {
        front: "poner",
        back: "place",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zZ7kfGomBt",
      },
      {
        front: "redonda",
        back: "round",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cunyXWut2t",
      },
      {
        front: "redondas",
        back: "round",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1YEwgpMPTV",
      },
      {
        front: "redondo",
        back: "round",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ceyhW0mpat",
      },
      {
        front: "redondos",
        back: "round",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5dWZjNrXDF",
      },
      {
        front: "sabremos",
        back: "we will know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QRarhqDjzP",
      },
      {
        front: "sabrá",
        back: "will know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uiSzifPum9",
      },
      {
        front: "sabrán",
        back: "will know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DtuSgT1dY1",
      },
      {
        front: "sabrás",
        back: "you will know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MhcH3IxkYD",
      },
      {
        front: "sabré",
        back: "i will know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3OCrcxFLFg",
      },
      {
        front: "saldremos",
        back: "we will go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m24EAdA7uv",
      },
      {
        front: "saldrá",
        back: "will come out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lct28Mwnru",
      },
      {
        front: "salir",
        back: "go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6UNDTtKef1",
      },
      {
        front: "tal como",
        back: "such as",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TdxoU8mGWf",
      },
      {
        front: "techo",
        back: "ceiling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gpGEYyyiUX",
      },
      {
        front: "tendrán",
        back: "will have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hXtgVzrora",
      },
      {
        front: "tendrás",
        back: "you will have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RJLBEcsTAX",
      },
      {
        front: "tendré",
        back: "I will have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1mKXduHTM1",
      },
      {
        front: "tener",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ga3S5pxHmb",
      },
      {
        front: "trasera",
        back: "rear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AfsBe2HuC8",
      },
      {
        front: "trasero",
        back: "rear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HbmOtCWisi",
      },
      {
        front: "vendremos",
        back: "we will come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cMCl7H26EF",
      },
      {
        front: "vendrá",
        back: "will come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "34UyzLgSBE",
      },
      {
        front: "venir",
        back: "to come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "smbwdbEaQC",
      },
      {
        front: "vivo",
        back: "alive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DGoKr5B4k4",
      },
      {
        front: "vivos",
        back: "alive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NJNnwzdHXj",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0QYVund7N5",
    title: "Unit 82",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "futuretense1",
        back: "futuretense1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vWzvyiNaxe",
      },
      {
        front: "futuretense2",
        back: "futuretense2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2YyFAN8DYy",
      },
      {
        front: "futuretense3",
        back: "futuretense3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vFOpPxP3dB",
      },
      {
        front: "futuretense",
        back: "futuretense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I37h4cj4NT",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "GbBPkZyOAN",
    title: "Unit 83",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "contra",
        back: "against",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fplUc41zOy",
      },
      {
        front: "círculo",
        back: "circle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LmREDHxIgS",
      },
      {
        front: "círculos",
        back: "circles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qp8NWj0tCn",
      },
      {
        front: "devolvemos",
        back: "we give back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Eh07NiW9Wx",
      },
      {
        front: "devuelven",
        back: "return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AmLVLFrGVI",
      },
      {
        front: "devuelves",
        back: "you return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iRjsV6XO54",
      },
      {
        front: "devuelvo",
        back: "I return",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DghPcEnf1J",
      },
      {
        front: "dáselo",
        back: "give it to him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6lhS9AZRzD",
      },
      {
        front: "déselo",
        back: "give it to him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l8UOd35is8",
      },
      {
        front: "dígame",
        back: "tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lAKCkT5RR0",
      },
      {
        front: "dígamelo",
        back: "tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Er1Ll4I0La",
      },
      {
        front: "dígaselo",
        back: "tell him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WTTaOz4b9T",
      },
      {
        front: "díselo",
        back: "tell her",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2awZL7s8Gf",
      },
      {
        front: "empujando",
        back: "pushing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y7UHccJ6eZ",
      },
      {
        front: "empujar",
        back: "Push",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yq6R2wAlB5",
      },
      {
        front: "espero",
        back: "wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8PtnuRNdSy",
      },
      {
        front: "graba",
        back: "record",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3peRuXj4Iu",
      },
      {
        front: "grabando",
        back: "recording",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WTz2uV9cEU",
      },
      {
        front: "grabo",
        back: "I record",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6ZQn0vAQud",
      },
      {
        front: "hala",
        back: "hello",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TGT8mQ0Awn",
      },
      {
        front: "halar",
        back: "pull",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jDqJRPieAa",
      },
      {
        front: "incluir",
        back: "include",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WfCbU8bw9D",
      },
      {
        front: "lancé",
        back: "throw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kyoVAi1Oos",
      },
      {
        front: "lanzamos",
        back: "we launch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QZMYwJMYCo",
      },
      {
        front: "lanzar",
        back: "launch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MhLjUsxCTT",
      },
      {
        front: "lanzas",
        back: "spears",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3wp4g9Vo15",
      },
      {
        front: "medio",
        back: "medium",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wn0crqAtxD",
      },
      {
        front: "molesta",
        back: "upset",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YMEBuZ0BqD",
      },
      {
        front: "parte de atrás",
        back: "back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OATVGUlo4Z",
      },
      {
        front: "pusieron",
        back: "they put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9NbruSnwS7",
      },
      {
        front: "pusimos",
        back: "we put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hxRPS1izas",
      },
      {
        front: "repetimos",
        back: "we repeat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gBz94RmVYO",
      },
      {
        front: "repite",
        back: "repeat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tLEyrw96zn",
      },
      {
        front: "repiten",
        back: "repeat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rkm3shCQpQ",
      },
      {
        front: "repito",
        back: "I repeat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rXJQWVNm2b",
      },
      {
        front: "salga",
        back: "out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h7vs508Wyc",
      },
      {
        front: "supieron",
        back: "they knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MVMN4kI3ce",
      },
      {
        front: "supimos",
        back: "we found out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PwhUdn7EAx",
      },
      {
        front: "venga",
        back: "come on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l6ZbWj85VR",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ARBMLKea6K",
    title: "Unit 83",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aguacate",
        back: "avocado",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QglLXKhTxe",
      },
      {
        front: "aguacates",
        back: "avocados",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "86beBLIEAe",
      },
      {
        front: "anduve",
        back: "I walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7XSywuET25",
      },
      {
        front: "anduvieron",
        back: "they walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YqXkxwZXMX",
      },
      {
        front: "anduvimos",
        back: "We walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "27TYmTOPPm",
      },
      {
        front: "anduviste",
        back: "you walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v9SDkyodbB",
      },
      {
        front: "anduvo",
        back: "walked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SkxwrI3Rrh",
      },
      {
        front: "cadena",
        back: "string",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YTABUMzmsQ",
      },
      {
        front: "cadenas",
        back: "chains",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9gy0m7Bxt2",
      },
      {
        front: "clásica",
        back: "classical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r8RCDAypoa",
      },
      {
        front: "describir",
        back: "to describe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XO5UTHTpJo",
      },
      {
        front: "doblamos",
        back: "we fold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UmJxBD4J5O",
      },
      {
        front: "doblar",
        back: "Bend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tLBMHJxsqN",
      },
      {
        front: "doblas",
        back: "you fold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "REDE3xQjIH",
      },
      {
        front: "estacionar",
        back: "park",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L0LheykALt",
      },
      {
        front: "estacionaré",
        back: "i will park",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t2UcTCfuj3",
      },
      {
        front: "estacionaste",
        back: "you parked",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "itryQ66dvs",
      },
      {
        front: "perdidos",
        back: "lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cka2WEqlYa",
      },
      {
        front: "pudieron",
        back: "could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0CWiViLXlA",
      },
      {
        front: "pudimos",
        back: "we could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aqqQokKeHr",
      },
      {
        front: "quise",
        back: "I wanted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "agtEKgfuoB",
      },
      {
        front: "quisieron",
        back: "they wanted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aabNHTNWYf",
      },
      {
        front: "quisimos",
        back: "we wanted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a0lRsY4zIm",
      },
      {
        front: "quisiste",
        back: "did you want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JGlBKRKcm4",
      },
      {
        front: "quiso",
        back: "wanted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tM7CAc2WtY",
      },
      {
        front: "red",
        back: "grid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0xRYhJbZmY",
      },
      {
        front: "retrasamos",
        back: "we delay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6iELHSbukc",
      },
      {
        front: "retrasaste",
        back: "you delayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ocGRHwHsUG",
      },
      {
        front: "retrasó",
        back: "delay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s19MyzcgvB",
      },
      {
        front: "sal",
        back: "Salt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ztB16fafWV",
      },
      {
        front: "señala",
        back: "points",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "euyorz7MRg",
      },
      {
        front: "señalar",
        back: "point",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C0AXcHYvn8",
      },
      {
        front: "sonar",
        back: "Dream",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wUduHpxvtn",
      },
      {
        front: "ten",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AHtbwco4KE",
      },
      {
        front: "ven",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hkiDO9gJM0",
      },
      {
        front: "acá",
        back: "come here",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O7BNxG5Fp3",
      },
      {
        front: "vete",
        back: "go away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jqQ5B2DinB",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "iNiRUbGjwi",
    title: "Unit 84",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a ella le",
        back: "she",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aKe5km2N3D",
      },
      {
        front: "a ella le gusta",
        back: "she likes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qo2hSu9lEa",
      },
      {
        front: "a mí me",
        back: "to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HSvZVIogP6",
      },
      {
        front: "a mí",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "93H5zG5NoQ",
      },
      {
        front: "me gusta",
        back: "I like it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7KnSPgAgrb",
      },
      {
        front: "a ti te",
        back: "to you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "stYTEsLK3e",
      },
      {
        front: "a ti te gustan",
        back: "you like them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RybA9lGd6S",
      },
      {
        front: "a él le",
        back: "to him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7oCchS6jN3",
      },
      {
        front: "a él le gustan",
        back: "he likes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e99q6hm2ru",
      },
      {
        front: "centímetros",
        back: "centimeters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SvhpwUnlIV",
      },
      {
        front: "es segura",
        back: "it is safe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CiKWEa2KVK",
      },
      {
        front: "es seguro",
        back: "It is safe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yzoxRUwUYs",
      },
      {
        front: "es verde",
        back: "It is green",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2rNhOcXX6E",
      },
      {
        front: "estoy lista",
        back: "I'm ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KKiWWaoefq",
      },
      {
        front: "estoy listo",
        back: "I'm ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oreEozvdfZ",
      },
      {
        front: "estoy seguro",
        back: "I'm sure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EmoM77ZwHj",
      },
      {
        front: "está listo",
        back: "ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zKgSS56F74",
      },
      {
        front: "está rico",
        back: "It's good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0UMgdAFbBJ",
      },
      {
        front: "está segura",
        back: "is sure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D2LfMLct5z",
      },
      {
        front: "están listas",
        back: "they are ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HNwNwaK9nz",
      },
      {
        front: "están listos",
        back: "they are ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rLwiTwivCo",
      },
      {
        front: "están ricas",
        back: "they are rich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FgYnJti9LU",
      },
      {
        front: "están ricos",
        back: "They are tasty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u5Q4ktWATM",
      },
      {
        front: "están seguros",
        back: "are you sure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eOdPUzNeuv",
      },
      {
        front: "estás lista",
        back: "are you ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b76NoETW1q",
      },
      {
        front: "estás segura",
        back: "are you sure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5QG8GeWr81",
      },
      {
        front: "gramo",
        back: "gram",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SKoTodBKv1",
      },
      {
        front: "gramos",
        back: "grams",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QjkSTa9aPE",
      },
      {
        front: "le das",
        back: "you give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w83d0D0aDh",
      },
      {
        front: "le doy",
        back: "I give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "da4DmKCMWn",
      },
      {
        front: "le gusta",
        back: "likes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0p7ceNi145",
      },
      {
        front: "le gustan",
        back: "Likes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "76MTaQWJdG",
      },
      {
        front: "lista",
        back: "list",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "erO1TXSDat",
      },
      {
        front: "listo",
        back: "clever",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TQjHWYRrCS",
      },
      {
        front: "listos",
        back: "ready",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o56nUkb0wk",
      },
      {
        front: "me dice",
        back: "tells me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TPeuUrRf9I",
      },
      {
        front: "me gusta",
        back: "I like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ppaVw61MAh",
      },
      {
        front: "profesora",
        back: "professor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DLQN4nc4Zb",
      },
      {
        front: "profesoras",
        back: "teachers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8IKGf7wQCo",
      },
      {
        front: "profesores",
        back: "teachers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wSsAKCADW5",
      },
      {
        front: "rectas",
        back: "straight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B31txnwrMK",
      },
      {
        front: "recto",
        back: "right",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dFVe5L9A6i",
      },
      {
        front: "rico",
        back: "rich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NxvemcU0Yu",
      },
      {
        front: "ricos",
        back: "rich",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zx6JZs7aj0",
      },
      {
        front: "son seguros",
        back: "They're safe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h8FFHFUk1L",
      },
      {
        front: "son verdes",
        back: "they are green",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aGAGORjxjc",
      },
      {
        front: "te dicen",
        back: "they tell you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8ecHJf4P3G",
      },
      {
        front: "te gustan",
        back: "you like them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jT9q6GbGUJ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "nMFLRhUGhw",
    title: "Unit 84",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "amar",
        back: "to love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mc1M8fLc3u",
      },
      {
        front: "amaron",
        back: "they loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8UkWnHqUhn",
      },
      {
        front: "amaste",
        back: "you loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u0D4Zt753r",
      },
      {
        front: "amé",
        back: "I loved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "u9y1DkRNh7",
      },
      {
        front: "amó",
        back: "love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kE19WrUjwa",
      },
      {
        front: "construimos",
        back: "we build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Fz9lYaIGE",
      },
      {
        front: "construir",
        back: "build up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TdO7mSu6U7",
      },
      {
        front: "construye",
        back: "build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YAVuRCTvk3",
      },
      {
        front: "construyen",
        back: "build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dNoWh4yEKy",
      },
      {
        front: "construyes",
        back: "you build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "71tuiwoneA",
      },
      {
        front: "construyo",
        back: "I build",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "us86Ene4Kb",
      },
      {
        front: "costaron",
        back: "they cost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HO3NyyyIek",
      },
      {
        front: "costó",
        back: "cost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BO8GcUGnWI",
      },
      {
        front: "decir",
        back: "say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ymtGItKE0Z",
      },
      {
        front: "decía",
        back: "He said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i3lK5TnB0v",
      },
      {
        front: "decíamos",
        back: "we said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n7jyR6NTLh",
      },
      {
        front: "decían",
        back: "they were saying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oy4HgPpFg6",
      },
      {
        front: "decías",
        back: "you said",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9STxVb0jWI",
      },
      {
        front: "dejaste",
        back: "you left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SLSlnAVHcy",
      },
      {
        front: "dejé",
        back: "leave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i5OEQ5Sju9",
      },
      {
        front: "dejó",
        back: "let",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nBxr5uKcAC",
      },
      {
        front: "deliciosa",
        back: "delicious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IKRxmj61Of",
      },
      {
        front: "delicioso",
        back: "delicious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T979A81Z40",
      },
      {
        front: "destruimos",
        back: "we destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x3YUt2fUlY",
      },
      {
        front: "destruir",
        back: "destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KrFzplOUBS",
      },
      {
        front: "destruirá",
        back: "will destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eHbZZUXcjc",
      },
      {
        front: "destruirán",
        back: "will destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3yaeqqSkLT",
      },
      {
        front: "destruye",
        back: "destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pJRavQa68G",
      },
      {
        front: "destruyen",
        back: "destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4aTs5omIjA",
      },
      {
        front: "destruyes",
        back: "you destroy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EvmaP7LHWp",
      },
      {
        front: "destruyo",
        back: "He destroyed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wud9Qfwud6",
      },
      {
        front: "golpea",
        back: "hit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AH33c6TSrm",
      },
      {
        front: "golpear",
        back: "beat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0uh6tyBeh0",
      },
      {
        front: "golpeas",
        back: "you hit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nhIO7HK6y1",
      },
      {
        front: "incluimos",
        back: "we include",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mlAHGzc3JT",
      },
      {
        front: "incluyen",
        back: "include",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aaFULvauHG",
      },
      {
        front: "incluyes",
        back: "you include",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oJ4z81ChgV",
      },
      {
        front: "incluyo",
        back: "I include",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vNzVU0CmG8",
      },
      {
        front: "individual",
        back: "individual",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uebThme4FF",
      },
      {
        front: "individuales",
        back: "individual",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HEwo9TG1S2",
      },
      {
        front: "mantenemos",
        back: "we keep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O4Plm8hOq5",
      },
      {
        front: "mantener",
        back: "hold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5AyrYU2VEQ",
      },
      {
        front: "mantengo",
        back: "I keep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GpISFInTQG",
      },
      {
        front: "mantiene",
        back: "maintains",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a8bubwomRL",
      },
      {
        front: "mantienen",
        back: "keep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cVACMDneA1",
      },
      {
        front: "mantienes",
        back: "you keep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sy6VaKMFwF",
      },
      {
        front: "matar",
        back: "to kill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uut3pOngIr",
      },
      {
        front: "matarán",
        back: "they will kill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wuzhtMWeSr",
      },
      {
        front: "mataré",
        back: "i will kill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oaF5G0TL0B",
      },
      {
        front: "mató",
        back: "killed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q2chVgJQNF",
      },
      {
        front: "muchacha",
        back: "girl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1N4BtwdAHv",
      },
      {
        front: "muchachas",
        back: "Girls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r2JMotldKJ",
      },
      {
        front: "muchacho",
        back: "young guy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gfc03zj9ci",
      },
      {
        front: "muchachos",
        back: "boys",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tMiVTam7zw",
      },
      {
        front: "murió",
        back: "died",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bVBJPYC7Dx",
      },
      {
        front: "podía",
        back: "could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0BnucTLHTC",
      },
      {
        front: "podían",
        back: "they could",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ujJMixjscI",
      },
      {
        front: "puesta",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kt4yTYubHo",
      },
      {
        front: "puestas",
        back: "on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UZXCPR2p6F",
      },
      {
        front: "puestos",
        back: "stalls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4L19o9IAUc",
      },
      {
        front: "sabía",
        back: "knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ausdDmbs8i",
      },
      {
        front: "sabían",
        back: "they knew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5hGFGWrPsz",
      },
      {
        front: "soñaron",
        back: "they dreamed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SKdUXmGKSI",
      },
      {
        front: "soñaste",
        back: "you dreamed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N1ANg8bINm",
      },
      {
        front: "soñé",
        back: "i dreamed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nl8t8l421d",
      },
      {
        front: "soñó",
        back: "dreamed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZKDrDuY6UW",
      },
      {
        front: "suceder",
        back: "happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oGwTcgQsQH",
      },
      {
        front: "sucederá",
        back: "will happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "19RXtUmXl7",
      },
      {
        front: "sucederán",
        back: "will happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rGWtUTJB58",
      },
      {
        front: "suponemos",
        back: "we suppose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cnyuBxs0u6",
      },
      {
        front: "suponer",
        back: "suppose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "egZUkgpCAu",
      },
      {
        front: "supongo",
        back: "I suppose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QqxzU14yJT",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "6QyNwqlP4I",
    title: "Unit 85",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a través de",
        back: "via",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kRz36rqSG4",
      },
      {
        front: "a través del",
        back: "through the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p5zBKZwcC2",
      },
      {
        front: "agrega",
        back: "add",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0iWYvU2KAe",
      },
      {
        front: "asa",
        back: "handle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K33f2JNCj2",
      },
      {
        front: "compre",
        back: "I bought",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vON5VPizSF",
      },
      {
        front: "corte",
        back: "court",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8p1Gwij1Yd",
      },
      {
        front: "descanse",
        back: "rest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v0dTz2rmwi",
      },
      {
        front: "empuje",
        back: "push",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lzjcXWHo84",
      },
      {
        front: "envíe",
        back: "send",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c5cHicOvgC",
      },
      {
        front: "estacione",
        back: "park",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GIvq8Ghowk",
      },
      {
        front: "llene",
        back: "fill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1psa60Qm9t",
      },
      {
        front: "oigan",
        back: "listen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NClehmvgIj",
      },
      {
        front: "organiza",
        back: "organize",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p3kVdQBMoD",
      },
      {
        front: "pasa",
        back: "happens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h0RiC4rOFO",
      },
      {
        front: "pasar",
        back: "happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OcIMQjyM7M",
      },
      {
        front: "pongan",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BtHnU8eN2v",
      },
      {
        front: "prepara",
        back: "prepare",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IM5JC9UkCS",
      },
      {
        front: "prepare",
        back: "prepare",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lyqBZ39PfZ",
      },
      {
        front: "regrese",
        back: "I am back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zQhuOnvlps",
      },
      {
        front: "repare",
        back: "I fixed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mSCjdjcjr8",
      },
      {
        front: "reserve",
        back: "reserve",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YhJDVCBJCa",
      },
      {
        front: "salgan",
        back: "come out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mVyVrJNb9d",
      },
      {
        front: "seca",
        back: "dry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D46ooq2sQ6",
      },
      {
        front: "tengan",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mj3K10MGMj",
      },
      {
        front: "traigan",
        back: "bring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lU4t6ZKod6",
      },
      {
        front: "uso",
        back: "use",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PK7z7fcIds",
      },
      {
        front: "vengan",
        back: "come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZKE3TXk4sp",
      },
      {
        front: "zapatos deportivos",
        back: "sports shoes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ySAAF6uMFN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "eSRwfyOqJ9",
    title: "Unit 86",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a pie",
        back: "walking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CzG8chaD5I",
      },
      {
        front: "anual",
        back: "annual",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TlwplDHGHb",
      },
      {
        front: "barrio",
        back: "neighborhood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ca6Uq15GKJ",
      },
      {
        front: "barrios",
        back: "neighborhoods",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tdrVXFE1vS",
      },
      {
        front: "circo",
        back: "circus",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9d9aEwdGcl",
      },
      {
        front: "cola",
        back: "line",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y7dbWNV7cZ",
      },
      {
        front: "enorme",
        back: "enormous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VDo7wTSBTi",
      },
      {
        front: "enormes",
        back: "huge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2XcPyNLraN",
      },
      {
        front: "entera",
        back: "whole",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FHF1431R3L",
      },
      {
        front: "festival",
        back: "festival",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oUDAvOCCF0",
      },
      {
        front: "festivales",
        back: "festivals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pgNnfsKNgh",
      },
      {
        front: "frutería",
        back: "fruit store",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7I4otcaBpw",
      },
      {
        front: "habitante",
        back: "habitant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PDy3Sd24gQ",
      },
      {
        front: "las afueras",
        back: "the outskirts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MsxCXKcBlY",
      },
      {
        front: "mayoría",
        back: "most",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "heNnsyyin5",
      },
      {
        front: "monumento",
        back: "monument",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fKW7pvjkGf",
      },
      {
        front: "monumentos",
        back: "monuments",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y0RjXzigjd",
      },
      {
        front: "parque de atracciones",
        back: "theme park",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JMbVjqzUvT",
      },
      {
        front: "pasado mañana",
        back: "day after tomorrow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ig8xShfexy",
      },
      {
        front: "pasando",
        back: "going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JiISyHGncN",
      },
      {
        front: "pasar",
        back: "happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GZKqBpfcnb",
      },
      {
        front: "pensar",
        back: "to think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6SW0v4x9og",
      },
      {
        front: "piensan",
        back: "think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FSnYrE0BDb",
      },
      {
        front: "piensas",
        back: "do you think",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8wgFtIuLSV",
      },
      {
        front: "plaza",
        back: "square",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iPIS2zw628",
      },
      {
        front: "plazas",
        back: "plazas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4N8JhkWvV3",
      },
      {
        front: "principal",
        back: "major",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RQIfLe8FVQ",
      },
      {
        front: "principales",
        back: "main",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EtyXdTSgnj",
      },
      {
        front: "quiosco",
        back: "kiosk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7iIygHV6NA",
      },
      {
        front: "solamente",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NElOygSFN8",
      },
      {
        front: "terraza",
        back: "terrace",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B6bBfsuYCh",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Xssu5mSkfy",
    title: "Unit 87",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "amor",
        back: "love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BFbHg3XwMD",
      },
      {
        front: "autobiografía",
        back: "autobiography",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SXWJaaQfIc",
      },
      {
        front: "breve",
        back: "brief",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EFU5MJLKIL",
      },
      {
        front: "breves",
        back: "brief",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WiVO7NAeQg",
      },
      {
        front: "capítulo",
        back: "chapter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2dqawOJ5KB",
      },
      {
        front: "capítulos",
        back: "chapters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bDlNuTAq0h",
      },
      {
        front: "charlar",
        back: "to chat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O2i2tGCkX1",
      },
      {
        front: "ciencia ficción",
        back: "Science fiction",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0G9EDE6pCO",
      },
      {
        front: "creativa",
        back: "creative",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H6bAtlh7Vt",
      },
      {
        front: "creativo",
        back: "creative",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wK15H7YmRz",
      },
      {
        front: "empezarán",
        back: "they will start",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0IrD5wNomK",
      },
      {
        front: "escribir",
        back: "to write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N58TVZYc7c",
      },
      {
        front: "escribiremos",
        back: "we will write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PIwxt6UWvs",
      },
      {
        front: "escribirás",
        back: "you will write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QM9DkagC2A",
      },
      {
        front: "escritor",
        back: "writer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qmOFR9D70T",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiaremos",
        back: "will study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jyfFAwxHyi",
      },
      {
        front: "estudiarán",
        back: "they will study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6PjE3xEOA6",
      },
      {
        front: "firma",
        back: "signature",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YpmoH7qKEm",
      },
      {
        front: "firmamos",
        back: "we sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bAfRHRbjHE",
      },
      {
        front: "firman",
        back: "sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IxvpIn5IC0",
      },
      {
        front: "firmará",
        back: "will sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y8akU7r1Qe",
      },
      {
        front: "firmas",
        back: "firms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DMsbP1vVOy",
      },
      {
        front: "firme",
        back: "sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rZxyzNhXAQ",
      },
      {
        front: "firmo",
        back: "I sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ls0iToxVyE",
      },
      {
        front: "hispana",
        back: "hispanic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tift3ZPr8o",
      },
      {
        front: "hispanos",
        back: "hispanic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G0anHJAJNk",
      },
      {
        front: "leerlo",
        back: "reading it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uvkXhGXj0t",
      },
      {
        front: "leerán",
        back: "they will read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PMj0FF2RYv",
      },
      {
        front: "literatura",
        back: "literature",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C6lIdr2jKA",
      },
      {
        front: "llamarse",
        back: "called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UVL3D1jl50",
      },
      {
        front: "llamará",
        back: "call to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CuvY3PsLXN",
      },
      {
        front: "llamaré",
        back: "I will call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9WlUB6MHKb",
      },
      {
        front: "llegaremos",
        back: "we will arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ZqVsvqBVG",
      },
      {
        front: "llegará",
        back: "reach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DHhfiqSPXz",
      },
      {
        front: "llegaré",
        back: "I will arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tustYvLgP5",
      },
      {
        front: "novela",
        back: "novel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DGHXAx6DYf",
      },
      {
        front: "novelas",
        back: "novels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sz9AjSc0Yq",
      },
      {
        front: "poema",
        back: "poem",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dYtQh7XASf",
      },
      {
        front: "protagonistas",
        back: "protagonists",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "beUe7LH082",
      },
      {
        front: "párrafo",
        back: "paragraph",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ll1gcltBu3",
      },
      {
        front: "párrafos",
        back: "paragraphs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wZwSgmwA8S",
      },
      {
        front: "quedaremos",
        back: "we will stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jHnj93CXB0",
      },
      {
        front: "quedará",
        back: "will remain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ukPXuslRj7",
      },
      {
        front: "quedarás",
        back: "you will stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2g6MkX3HLE",
      },
      {
        front: "quedaré",
        back: "I will stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d9wRZBXW8N",
      },
      {
        front: "romántica",
        back: "romantic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cUWcnglH5I",
      },
      {
        front: "romántico",
        back: "Romantic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X3lfbtUOAr",
      },
      {
        front: "románticos",
        back: "romantic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RdH34MSVvs",
      },
      {
        front: "se llamará",
        back: "Will be called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tx8u0BYFsB",
      },
      {
        front: "se llamarán",
        back: "they will be called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XpYhOUe47v",
      },
      {
        front: "terminarás",
        back: "you will finish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YZoB8dHDqH",
      },
      {
        front: "terminaré",
        back: "I will finish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r3bPq7iZyT",
      },
      {
        front: "textos",
        back: "texts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q2sDYwcyzz",
      },
      {
        front: "traducirán",
        back: "will translate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QSo4qnkCVf",
      },
      {
        front: "traduciré",
        back: "I will translate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FULCMevAAr",
      },
      {
        front: "veremos",
        back: "we will see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KpPNnsD7sw",
      },
      {
        front: "verá",
        back: "you will see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "07rdhAJiJB",
      },
      {
        front: "verán",
        back: "they will see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7IG6tA2VCD",
      },
      {
        front: "verás",
        back: "you will see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L1hVmuknzD",
      },
      {
        front: "veré",
        back: "I will see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zG7iPEk44w",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "k6ddHxx2S4",
    title: "Unit 88",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "anteayer",
        back: "the day before yesterday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TjYv86YWoh",
      },
      {
        front: "arroba",
        back: "at sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UPjJUKCAv4",
      },
      {
        front: "blog",
        back: "Blog",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xnRQjK9hh3",
      },
      {
        front: "borramos",
        back: "we delete",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iwMUaZoygR",
      },
      {
        front: "borraste",
        back: "you erased",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hHh6dTNAKq",
      },
      {
        front: "borré",
        back: "I deleted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JucXS13f21",
      },
      {
        front: "buzón de",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uo0SIPelAa",
      },
      {
        front: "voz",
        back: "voicemail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RZZomEQVeH",
      },
      {
        front: "cable",
        back: "wire",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yRduO4eQAn",
      },
      {
        front: "chateamos",
        back: "we chat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OD6X8arTc0",
      },
      {
        front: "chatear",
        back: "chat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ge3BUUA0lv",
      },
      {
        front: "chatearon",
        back: "they chatted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RnmottSeLr",
      },
      {
        front: "chateaste",
        back: "you chatted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0z0Yw7uW7R",
      },
      {
        front: "chateó",
        back: "chatted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0pMbKuNeZj",
      },
      {
        front: "comunicarse",
        back: "communicate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6kbR9UvWND",
      },
      {
        front: "conectamos",
        back: "we connect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "koIL41fOss",
      },
      {
        front: "conectar",
        back: "connect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "muqR9SlTzo",
      },
      {
        front: "conectarme",
        back: "connect me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ys9LBEP3pO",
      },
      {
        front: "conectaron",
        back: "connected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DIWntFYFPe",
      },
      {
        front: "conecté",
        back: "i connected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9HaMMPgWEt",
      },
      {
        front: "conectó",
        back: "connected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RnHKcJu3au",
      },
      {
        front: "crea",
        back: "creates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pna0u7pEbj",
      },
      {
        front: "creamos",
        back: "we create",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hQ18larM7M",
      },
      {
        front: "crean",
        back: "create",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2f7jpXPpWp",
      },
      {
        front: "crear",
        back: "create",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o9RaWX6F9P",
      },
      {
        front: "creas",
        back: "you believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "12DbExDexi",
      },
      {
        front: "creo",
        back: "I believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ManfvLUg0L",
      },
      {
        front: "creé",
        back: "i created",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c6Jd4U3iO9",
      },
      {
        front: "creó",
        back: "I believe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ft3p465Dbx",
      },
      {
        front: "exacta",
        back: "exact",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SAC0jePOxz",
      },
      {
        front: "exactas",
        back: "exact",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ENuKlQR9uR",
      },
      {
        front: "experto",
        back: "expert",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uQ7CWfpI8q",
      },
      {
        front: "foro",
        back: "forum",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fmxGicpOHi",
      },
      {
        front: "informática",
        back: "computing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l2PoJDdxJT",
      },
      {
        front: "instalamos",
        back: "we install",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ucgdgdqy21",
      },
      {
        front: "instalar",
        back: "to install",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FsUxo2zTCl",
      },
      {
        front: "instalaron",
        back: "installed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lUayK0Har4",
      },
      {
        front: "instalaste",
        back: "you installed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QkdtlsjpBZ",
      },
      {
        front: "instaló",
        back: "installed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pbJs44OjBf",
      },
      {
        front: "intentaste",
        back: "you tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UUOpWcGVb1",
      },
      {
        front: "intentó",
        back: "tried",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vGDup5jdI1",
      },
      {
        front: "me conecté",
        back: "I connected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IhMKCrtaQ6",
      },
      {
        front: "publicidad",
        back: "advertising",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y8e8kjePFx",
      },
      {
        front: "publicidades",
        back: "advertisements",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0uqDTDNoKU",
      },
      {
        front: "página web",
        back: "Web page",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KTDaDlmMb1",
      },
      {
        front: "páginas web",
        back: "websites",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JQTevKNAP7",
      },
      {
        front: "quedaron",
        back: "were left",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IoQDy4GwaS",
      },
      {
        front: "quedé",
        back: "I stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zPiQZkqwaS",
      },
      {
        front: "quedó",
        back: "stayed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5YhCNKUKrH",
      },
      {
        front: "recordó",
        back: "remembered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mQhGGHLvU2",
      },
      {
        front: "se comunicaron",
        back: "they communicated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "39a2h2Ee3h",
      },
      {
        front: "se comunicó",
        back: "he has communicated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nqyPbSe7qM",
      },
      {
        front: "se conectaron",
        back: "they connected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iJwfXN4fW1",
      },
      {
        front: "soluciones",
        back: "solutions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Q3WIxDeUJc",
      },
      {
        front: "solución",
        back: "solution",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qyLFnwpYYw",
      },
      {
        front: "subieron",
        back: "went up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qtPx1YyjN0",
      },
      {
        front: "subió",
        back: "went up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z44kU09l2H",
      },
      {
        front: "subí",
        back: "I went up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wyHUoyJfqe",
      },
      {
        front: "tableta",
        back: "Tablet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HHvq6qofLn",
      },
      {
        front: "te comunicas",
        back: "you communicate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oHH4r24KIY",
      },
      {
        front: "tecnología",
        back: "technology",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CFgLfiO0Wo",
      },
      {
        front: "tecnologías",
        back: "technologies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3xUM6ttSpP",
      },
      {
        front: "tema",
        back: "theme",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "guHJeBFNT6",
      },
      {
        front: "temas",
        back: "topics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZG6hKqgdwe",
      },
      {
        front: "videojuego",
        back: "videogame",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fdMkyrXjAW",
      },
      {
        front: "videojuegos",
        back: "video game",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SW2TTkWfv6",
      },
      {
        front: "volvió",
        back: "went back",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yv2RzWwC3Y",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "E8iR4p9iLI",
    title: "Unit 89",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrazo",
        back: "hug",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "14WpOEFsts",
      },
      {
        front: "acepta",
        back: "you accept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CY5Fkf6GXZ",
      },
      {
        front: "aceptar",
        back: "to accept",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lfzEgLxGV1",
      },
      {
        front: "aceptaste",
        back: "you accepted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2OZq2LwGRw",
      },
      {
        front: "acepto",
        back: "I agree",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ci1Ar22QdN",
      },
      {
        front: "aceptó",
        back: "I agree",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zEk78IOLbm",
      },
      {
        front: "alegre",
        back: "cheerful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jlT3qbqAB0",
      },
      {
        front: "alegres",
        back: "happy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gqTTR2Thnq",
      },
      {
        front: "beso",
        back: "kiss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ukE0iZf4kN",
      },
      {
        front: "bodas",
        back: "wedding",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m5HzRFj7oU",
      },
      {
        front: "caracteres",
        back: "characters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7kEZOWdj8A",
      },
      {
        front: "carácter",
        back: "character",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FlZWORm6if",
      },
      {
        front: "carácteres",
        back: "characters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xMLKYN5BhJ",
      },
      {
        front: "celebramos",
        back: "we celebrated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jFp6MC9I94",
      },
      {
        front: "discoteca",
        back: "discotheque",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M5kFdEvGdV",
      },
      {
        front: "divorcio",
        back: "divorce",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W6i9C1ZL0i",
      },
      {
        front: "en el",
        back: "in it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "877aLgMGa9",
      },
      {
        front: "encantada",
        back: "Haunted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C0YYWyGazk",
      },
      {
        front: "encantadas",
        back: "enchanted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2JI9b9CTee",
      },
      {
        front: "encantados",
        back: "delighted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NVK53vmLTK",
      },
      {
        front: "estado civil",
        back: "marital status",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tBzhkf5xPO",
      },
      {
        front: "ex",
        back: "ex",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o4EN5SH9Cm",
      },
      {
        front: "excusa",
        back: "excuse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "znd9x0ZZf9",
      },
      {
        front: "excusas",
        back: "excuses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "caU0rwC7Lf",
      },
      {
        front: "hubo",
        back: "was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IXaNJ7raSq",
      },
      {
        front: "humor",
        back: "humor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tNinmT4fsd",
      },
      {
        front: "me puse",
        back: "i put on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "syo93eZO3V",
      },
      {
        front: "pareja",
        back: "couple",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qnMZrgtrNQ",
      },
      {
        front: "parejas",
        back: "couples",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lF9WNSGGdl",
      },
      {
        front: "paseo",
        back: "ride",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xNO7TOs168",
      },
      {
        front: "ponerse",
        back: "to put on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1RafQrchE2",
      },
      {
        front: "regalar",
        back: "give a present",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dPLnQkKB6D",
      },
      {
        front: "regaló",
        back: "present",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rhjb5DaQwF",
      },
      {
        front: "relación",
        back: "relationship",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ivlr0F0Ao6",
      },
      {
        front: "romance",
        back: "Romance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VqweDusR1T",
      },
      {
        front: "se puso",
        back: "put on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lRdhCTFEAR",
      },
      {
        front: "sueño",
        back: "sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sn9ucpjywV",
      },
      {
        front: "te pusiste",
        back: "you put on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PpZq2fqksu",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "1z89Pj9Dje",
    title: "Unit 90",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "actual",
        back: "current",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WpCPmBNgCO",
      },
      {
        front: "actualmente",
        back: "at the moment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CjrsQoUuRs",
      },
      {
        front: "artículo",
        back: "Article",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FhOYw0NEx5",
      },
      {
        front: "artículos",
        back: "articles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AezzluoenY",
      },
      {
        front: "causa",
        back: "cause",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PMkBnMp6Fb",
      },
      {
        front: "causas",
        back: "Causes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ys0vedkR2t",
      },
      {
        front: "causó",
        back: "caused",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2bbw8xEhUk",
      },
      {
        front: "crisis",
        back: "crisis",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PO0sfAKWI8",
      },
      {
        front: "curiosa",
        back: "curious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SyInvmwUpS",
      },
      {
        front: "curioso",
        back: "curious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1YMKMhPv5B",
      },
      {
        front: "daña",
        back: "hurts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kyg6grvEOe",
      },
      {
        front: "daño",
        back: "damage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cm4zatzkf3",
      },
      {
        front: "daños",
        back: "damage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DQaMRqECXn",
      },
      {
        front: "escapen",
        back: "escape",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jo5izTOavi",
      },
      {
        front: "escapó",
        back: "escaped",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9AaOdOEU2f",
      },
      {
        front: "frecuente",
        back: "frequent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PsP5iiunkb",
      },
      {
        front: "mundial",
        back: "world",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LYRrhMmZP6",
      },
      {
        front: "paz",
        back: "peace",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RT0RQF1GVw",
      },
      {
        front: "población",
        back: "population",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IeH9VkbVe5",
      },
      {
        front: "por el momento",
        back: "for the moment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gXraBRi0ai",
      },
      {
        front: "publicaron",
        back: "published",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2wRTXUQoZF",
      },
      {
        front: "publicó",
        back: "public",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oGZKhjJ43z",
      },
      {
        front: "reciente",
        back: "recent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wEawYvCcik",
      },
      {
        front: "recientemente",
        back: "Recently",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z1DkcIgTpV",
      },
      {
        front: "recientes",
        back: "recent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SIacoUqQTo",
      },
      {
        front: "según",
        back: "according to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rx2cSFZkNz",
      },
      {
        front: "silenciosa",
        back: "silent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NPxqWYgk6A",
      },
      {
        front: "silenciosamente",
        back: "silently",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nHFO6YjD2B",
      },
      {
        front: "silenciosas",
        back: "silent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "247W1i0PL9",
      },
      {
        front: "silencioso",
        back: "silent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ic42HoxnXd",
      },
      {
        front: "silenciosos",
        back: "silent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JvY6fClSGn",
      },
      {
        front: "situaciones",
        back: "situations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wMOzNb04XF",
      },
      {
        front: "situación",
        back: "situation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VWKXEOC36e",
      },
      {
        front: "título",
        back: "title",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hATkZec6Fz",
      },
      {
        front: "zona",
        back: "zone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5krf8NzKG4",
      },
      {
        front: "zonas",
        back: "zones",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9pQloWJt9H",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "FfPbqRyvuh",
    title: "Unit 91",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "antibiótico",
        back: "antibiotic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xug1VWXBAh",
      },
      {
        front: "antibióticos",
        back: "antibiotics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "affmB90VRl",
      },
      {
        front: "análisis de sangre",
        back: "blood test",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xBQZS4ihwb",
      },
      {
        front: "así",
        back: "So",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ISS6dyp6GL",
      },
      {
        front: "bastante",
        back: "pretty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K2vRUZQRWe",
      },
      {
        front: "bastantes",
        back: "quite a few",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tdPoMeyro5",
      },
      {
        front: "clínica",
        back: "clinic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Dl8BzQ7Hs9",
      },
      {
        front: "clínicas",
        back: "clinics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QVM1eH52rs",
      },
      {
        front: "codo",
        back: "elbow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rYdBOmfSMP",
      },
      {
        front: "codos",
        back: "elbows",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OPN4aX93iX",
      },
      {
        front: "dieta",
        back: "diet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NidKOGPrvL",
      },
      {
        front: "dietas",
        back: "subsistence allowance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CIime1kuzd",
      },
      {
        front: "doctor",
        back: "doctor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7SlLnU5VWA",
      },
      {
        front: "doctora",
        back: "doctor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dYZC1e1OBP",
      },
      {
        front: "doctoras",
        back: "female doctors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0WzF3cGg02",
      },
      {
        front: "doctores",
        back: "doctors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KXe3uKKXCf",
      },
      {
        front: "estrés",
        back: "stress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0MaDNhYU5m",
      },
      {
        front: "evitar",
        back: "to avoid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MTNZpYV66q",
      },
      {
        front: "farmacia",
        back: "pharmacy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lpWJJLfavI",
      },
      {
        front: "farmacias",
        back: "pharmacy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kFfHdIBX32",
      },
      {
        front: "lo",
        back: "it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vFPrsGQ9EU",
      },
      {
        front: "mareada",
        back: "dizzy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ah4H9SQsXX",
      },
      {
        front: "mareado",
        back: "dizzy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qRzXsTJGOY",
      },
      {
        front: "mayor",
        back: "higher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d6QOmllSEq",
      },
      {
        front: "me enfermo",
        back: "I get sick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oFnGuN8KOC",
      },
      {
        front: "me quemo",
        back: "I'm burning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YU5lnmfQEs",
      },
      {
        front: "mejor",
        back: "better",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gku2pdSEYt",
      },
      {
        front: "paciente",
        back: "patient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2kBWzhAul5",
      },
      {
        front: "pacientes",
        back: "patients",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOdKoYpsdv",
      },
      {
        front: "peor",
        back: "worse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PzIUK2RFhd",
      },
      {
        front: "peso",
        back: "weight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uAsfyqTRBA",
      },
      {
        front: "piel",
        back: "skin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dS9smIgXlW",
      },
      {
        front: "por suerte",
        back: "Fortunately",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2XqN9EXYaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "resfriadas",
        back: "colds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hkrMJI6DZ3",
      },
      {
        front: "resfriado",
        back: "a cold",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QRaVirORZw",
      },
      {
        front: "se enferma",
        back: "gets sick",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M4NyoA94rs",
      },
      {
        front: "se quemaron",
        back: "they burned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gpn2ArLW3R",
      },
      {
        front: "se quemó",
        back: "it burned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MTmsIxo7Mi",
      },
      {
        front: "tos",
        back: "cough",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QJ2DRrnR4W",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "mJ8tnWtZ3i",
    title: "Unit 92",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "decisiones",
        back: "decisions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ovWCulbBz",
      },
      {
        front: "descripciones",
        back: "descriptions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KOu9l32fYL",
      },
      {
        front: "descripción",
        back: "description",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rFPn2BxYGf",
      },
      {
        front: "discutir",
        back: "argue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WVYbjBq4ZC",
      },
      {
        front: "distinta",
        back: "different",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X3v57xZ3fw",
      },
      {
        front: "distintas",
        back: "different",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4X4tRzr8o2",
      },
      {
        front: "distinto",
        back: "distinct",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yfWFQikMwd",
      },
      {
        front: "distintos",
        back: "different",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L8MOdhmwRh",
      },
      {
        front: "experiencia",
        back: "experience",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "thPmbD2ml4",
      },
      {
        front: "experiencias",
        back: "experiences",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mhCtWW2JPq",
      },
      {
        front: "honesto",
        back: "honest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rlpbfyYPG9",
      },
      {
        front: "importancia",
        back: "importance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FfKIAerhv9",
      },
      {
        front: "imposible",
        back: "impossible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0i4hySUu1B",
      },
      {
        front: "incorrecto",
        back: "incorrect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LMNeGFtJ42",
      },
      {
        front: "necesaria",
        back: "necessary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0z6TokrWd5",
      },
      {
        front: "necesarias",
        back: "necessary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rLdtwjMXZx",
      },
      {
        front: "necesario",
        back: "necessary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GcxIn4SK0H",
      },
      {
        front: "necesarios",
        back: "necessary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cpWqKWAbbj",
      },
      {
        front: "o",
        back: "either",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rbbY82kGDy",
      },
      {
        front: "opciones",
        back: "options",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mYAkZBCPkQ",
      },
      {
        front: "opción",
        back: "option",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LA6auspXG6",
      },
      {
        front: "opiniones",
        back: "opinions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M7rZnCBYst",
      },
      {
        front: "opinión",
        back: "opinion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eYHgy5YfOi",
      },
      {
        front: "oportunidad",
        back: "chance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uUSLNCE7eh",
      },
      {
        front: "oportunidades",
        back: "opportunities",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "siLN5vJXAt",
      },
      {
        front: "para",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PmwVi0KuVy",
      },
      {
        front: "personal",
        back: "staff",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ba886BNgEV",
      },
      {
        front: "personales",
        back: "personal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J45KUk5uKP",
      },
      {
        front: "progreso",
        back: "progress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CglTo776sJ",
      },
      {
        front: "ventaja",
        back: "advantage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ksi8J3ML7o",
      },
      {
        front: "ventajas",
        back: "advantage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZSMtoNbYgP",
      },
      {
        front: "única",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gNAV9jIzUX",
      },
      {
        front: "único",
        back: "unique",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qiU5xB2o9v",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "x0JnWSPuOT",
    title: "Unit 93",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "algodón",
        back: "cotton",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MaVhCfXThy",
      },
      {
        front: "apretadas",
        back: "tight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m59MR3XReF",
      },
      {
        front: "apretados",
        back: "tight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tS4E3YISjM",
      },
      {
        front: "caja registradora",
        back: "cash register",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "162xs7VcTG",
      },
      {
        front: "cajero automático",
        back: "ATM",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NKJRo6ONhc",
      },
      {
        front: "cajeros automáticos",
        back: "ATMs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zNFWBtvKv9",
      },
      {
        front: "calidad",
        back: "quality",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MbAfpzgQFD",
      },
      {
        front: "calidades",
        back: "qualities",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GIErkM77Oh",
      },
      {
        front: "centro comercial",
        back: "mall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6kEnl98bSV",
      },
      {
        front: "centros comerciales",
        back: "malls",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eH6P29dC62",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        back: "from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qimm7UUgXY",
      },
      {
        front: "de talla única",
        back: "one size fits all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XvAlaFgYif",
      },
      {
        front: "diseño",
        back: "design",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tTE9qfX0YL",
      },
      {
        front: "falta",
        back: "lack",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aVDK0ommD7",
      },
      {
        front: "faltan",
        back: "missing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fl5Xe7UDsF",
      },
      {
        front: "fea",
        back: "ugly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jNnjWohdnD",
      },
      {
        front: "feas",
        back: "ugly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NQNvhsXY1J",
      },
      {
        front: "feo",
        back: "ugly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "057SVHSWnt",
      },
      {
        front: "feos",
        back: "ugly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TNHIVIKrcD",
      },
      {
        front: "gorro",
        back: "hat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AeXFVP1Det",
      },
      {
        front: "gorros",
        back: "caps",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ViRsBStBj",
      },
      {
        front: "importa",
        back: "matter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hZYz70BC8G",
      },
      {
        front: "importamos",
        back: "we matter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3S9seuk58N",
      },
      {
        front: "importan",
        back: "matter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z7fZz3NS3k",
      },
      {
        front: "importar",
        back: "to import",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CQfu3LzQpn",
      },
      {
        front: "importo",
        back: "I import",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cxE6P9VWpY",
      },
      {
        front: "informal",
        back: "informal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TrZaFCjgcH",
      },
      {
        front: "informales",
        back: "informal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1A7Lm1yABX",
      },
      {
        front: "llevan",
        back: "They carry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YDf0KLvSnO",
      },
      {
        front: "llevar",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DEkSuhbIYb",
      },
      {
        front: "llevas",
        back: "you carry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qJFFaJFkYI",
      },
      {
        front: "llevo",
        back: "he took",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A0xvx5PvGA",
      },
      {
        front: "original",
        back: "original",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X4oS8M9pXm",
      },
      {
        front: "originales",
        back: "original",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YVavD9vlhM",
      },
      {
        front: "por",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a6kpGeUPXQ",
      },
      {
        front: "ropa interior",
        back: "underwear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4c0pGPbdMJ",
      },
      {
        front: "sudadera",
        back: "hoodie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nWbEcdt7y6",
      },
      {
        front: "sudaderas",
        back: "sweatshirts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kQMK7l4YjW",
      },
      {
        front: "tamaño",
        back: "size",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TfAChPwMWs",
      },
      {
        front: "tamaños",
        back: "sizes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xvgx3fAKv6",
      },
      {
        front: "total",
        back: "total",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FUYHECbc1d",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tUUZt2pUKR",
    title: "Unit 94",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "commands21",
        back: "commands21",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ZMM5BYGHc",
      },
      {
        front: "commands22",
        back: "commands22",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jf1MpSrTGk",
      },
      {
        front: "commands23",
        back: "commands23",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VRT5ydQJqp",
      },
      {
        front: "commands",
        back: "commands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kDIuDc66Qu",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "eRczddc22n",
    title: "Unit 95",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abras",
        back: "open",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L6CYoC7b8R",
      },
      {
        front: "bebas",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DPkEbGzrbM",
      },
      {
        front: "cafetería",
        back: "coffee shop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PaoMcCscZM",
      },
      {
        front: "comas",
        back: "commas",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4EWEDkYiri",
      },
      {
        front: "compres",
        back: "buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BUrIMSXqep",
      },
      {
        front: "contaminada",
        back: "polluted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wgsVZBpzjC",
      },
      {
        front: "contaminado",
        back: "contaminated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aDFVK47bke",
      },
      {
        front: "currículum",
        back: "resume",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oolyk8yXuy",
      },
      {
        front: "embajada",
        back: "embassy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wxxi02TfaR",
      },
      {
        front: "entrevista",
        back: "interview",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YYKqGyHpek",
      },
      {
        front: "floreros",
        back: "vases",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AgT9xwtHCe",
      },
      {
        front: "fuente",
        back: "fountain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RQkvqkd8oC",
      },
      {
        front: "fuentes",
        back: "sources",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sRGcoJTBlZ",
      },
      {
        front: "hables",
        back: "talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eoNnW2CKEp",
      },
      {
        front: "huracanes",
        back: "hurricanes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JN4CEkyOdm",
      },
      {
        front: "huracán",
        back: "hurricane",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZSVuSSPPWE",
      },
      {
        front: "lleves",
        back: "take",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VmHkAz4Nte",
      },
      {
        front: "lluvias",
        back: "rainy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EkkFnszhRG",
      },
      {
        front: "presentación",
        back: "presentation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XkQ4QTeSbp",
      },
      {
        front: "rosas",
        back: "roses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3mYq1NFT9v",
      },
      {
        front: "subas",
        back: "go up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8YeVlynnV",
      },
      {
        front: "temporada",
        back: "season",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wl6cUcpMKI",
      },
      {
        front: "temporadas",
        back: "seasons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2LqoblT1mq",
      },
      {
        front: "viajes",
        back: "travels",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OXX0qqztmW",
      },
      {
        front: "visa",
        back: "visa",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d1Ozdb0ZRc",
      },
      {
        front: "visites",
        back: "visit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PkznIwnK2V",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "71ZCpSoGwB",
    title: "Unit 96",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "caer",
        back: "fall out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ks1Xrf0now",
      },
      {
        front: "campo",
        back: "countryside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FENj3ecZe3",
      },
      {
        front: "costa",
        back: "coast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0UQDO1ab4R",
      },
      {
        front: "costas",
        back: "coasts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aMqjQomJJt",
      },
      {
        front: "des",
        back: "des",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LbtQDYn2Ya",
      },
      {
        front: "desconocida",
        back: "unknown",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "buWU7mh3vY",
      },
      {
        front: "desconocido",
        back: "a stranger",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OwL5rcSwJs",
      },
      {
        front: "despertar",
        back: "wake",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1V7VLzZE64",
      },
      {
        front: "digas",
        back: "you say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "caXXx6EHQX",
      },
      {
        front: "exploras",
        back: "you explore",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LoX3490iOg",
      },
      {
        front: "frágil",
        back: "fragile",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TyExYXSfm1",
      },
      {
        front: "frágiles",
        back: "fragile",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ebPuYhdZmU",
      },
      {
        front: "galería",
        back: "Gallery",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6PWaHRqhwD",
      },
      {
        front: "grupo",
        back: "cluster",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b6uPgJeLri",
      },
      {
        front: "hagas",
        back: "you do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UQBrp7jZq6",
      },
      {
        front: "local",
        back: "local",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K4ut7aDKSE",
      },
      {
        front: "locales",
        back: "local",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jAZP3KbQvL",
      },
      {
        front: "oficina de correos",
        back: "post Office",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fodzWUTept",
      },
      {
        front: "polvo",
        back: "dust",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aV98nybFny",
      },
      {
        front: "polvos",
        back: "powder",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tFD3n9vHIJ",
      },
      {
        front: "pongas",
        back: "put",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d8skY1w84w",
      },
      {
        front: "regiones",
        back: "regions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "baiyv8ufCr",
      },
      {
        front: "región",
        back: "region",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SeED4TDEEv",
      },
      {
        front: "salgas",
        back: "come out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SKgtA8kWvR",
      },
      {
        front: "sentir",
        back: "to feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mb7zdnUrDV",
      },
      {
        front: "suelo",
        back: "I usually",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YBuPQGIhTs",
      },
      {
        front: "taxista",
        back: "cabbie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H2Pxm4UXtE",
      },
      {
        front: "taxistas",
        back: "taxi drivers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4meJyKTDFb",
      },
      {
        front: "tengas",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EWq1LzmaGk",
      },
      {
        front: "terremoto",
        back: "earthquake",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kHmRJc7urE",
      },
      {
        front: "terremotos",
        back: "earthquakes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2wW1iz393E",
      },
      {
        front: "tigre",
        back: "tiger",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hgceke8Bqt",
      },
      {
        front: "vayas",
        back: "go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hd1oX5pJk8",
      },
      {
        front: "vengas",
        back: "come on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SRmU22pJK0",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "N0cyJEVC68",
    title: "Unit 96",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "agencia",
        back: "agency",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "65Dt9A87iB",
      },
      {
        front: "antigua",
        back: "ancient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I7IFdn5gHB",
      },
      {
        front: "antiguas",
        back: "ancient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fRJhuT7H53",
      },
      {
        front: "antiguo",
        back: "ancient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2GVPdJkr6V",
      },
      {
        front: "antiguos",
        back: "ancient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "klt4gG8r2C",
      },
      {
        front: "conexión",
        back: "Connection",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VKFY5dy4jZ",
      },
      {
        front: "código postal",
        back: "Postal Code",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t1kMPMbwVP",
      },
      {
        front: "códigos postales",
        back: "zip codes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L6F6uyxqdj",
      },
      {
        front: "destino",
        back: "destiny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r3EOzcMM3R",
      },
      {
        front: "dirección",
        back: "direction",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FTkyJkALb0",
      },
      {
        front: "directo",
        back: "straight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gLFuylGixa",
      },
      {
        front: "directos",
        back: "direct",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Hdi0m3708",
      },
      {
        front: "distancia",
        back: "distance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7qh8KanwEH",
      },
      {
        front: "distancias",
        back: "distances",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VOHEJhWjT2",
      },
      {
        front: "dueña",
        back: "owner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RkuLSgcYxe",
      },
      {
        front: "dueñas",
        back: "owners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D4Ynb3MkJv",
      },
      {
        front: "dueño",
        back: "owner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4H09sO3bjy",
      },
      {
        front: "dueños",
        back: "owners",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EjTqrSlBEg",
      },
      {
        front: "espectacular",
        back: "spectacular",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3S0kK9YdBI",
      },
      {
        front: "espectaculares",
        back: "spectacular",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z9FxnsDWnQ",
      },
      {
        front: "estaciones",
        back: "seasons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vc4onbLZhT",
      },
      {
        front: "frontera",
        back: "border",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "al34SbiCVy",
      },
      {
        front: "fronteras",
        back: "borders",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LhnHqGMzfz",
      },
      {
        front: "hispanohablante",
        back: "Spanish-speaking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LDr210dMCO",
      },
      {
        front: "hispanohablantes",
        back: "Spanish speakers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x9ZspzjDJK",
      },
      {
        front: "itinerario",
        back: "itinerary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WG6VkZNWqc",
      },
      {
        front: "llegada",
        back: "arrival",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ossDTOjOpQ",
      },
      {
        front: "llegadas",
        back: "Arrivals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dOdA1gBTfZ",
      },
      {
        front: "milla",
        back: "mile",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LUTTKSCCGR",
      },
      {
        front: "millas",
        back: "miles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KO9p1L9HjN",
      },
      {
        front: "ruinas",
        back: "ruins",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vcyV7Sc4W3",
      },
      {
        front: "saber",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tDVYRFsbCz",
      },
      {
        front: "tour",
        back: "tour",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cpJddWJs6q",
      },
      {
        front: "típica",
        back: "typical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Pj9mZpwdHP",
      },
      {
        front: "típicos",
        back: "typical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nAvQn1uT5x",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "XPaVK21Sjp",
    title: "Unit 97",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adicional",
        back: "additional",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YVDLcS2CaC",
      },
      {
        front: "adicionales",
        back: "additional",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tl6K2Wjnbh",
      },
      {
        front: "aire acondicionado",
        back: "air conditioner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8QHhFyD9uJ",
      },
      {
        front: "alfombra",
        back: "carpet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fUqekhA1F2",
      },
      {
        front: "alfombras",
        back: "carpets",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8XuyaUezbW",
      },
      {
        front: "bien",
        back: "good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jJs7cLiZGJ",
      },
      {
        front: "botón",
        back: "button",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4dSx3ULQ99",
      },
      {
        front: "calefacción",
        back: "heating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OUwDGxFTCv",
      },
      {
        front: "cantidad",
        back: "amount",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2f5PQgQ2OF",
      },
      {
        front: "clásicas",
        back: "classic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xiP9mdegm0",
      },
      {
        front: "clásico",
        back: "classic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WDJFhh5TS7",
      },
      {
        front: "clásicos",
        back: "classics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CFwQIx0Nhf",
      },
      {
        front: "cobrar",
        back: "collect",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6Cg3ZYZUci",
      },
      {
        front: "cobraron",
        back: "charged",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TdWrqVHlmv",
      },
      {
        front: "comedor",
        back: "dining room",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PGnMVB0vdK",
      },
      {
        front: "deben",
        back: "must",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GRRr7MSYcL",
      },
      {
        front: "debo",
        back: "I shall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xBQfH1MKM3",
      },
      {
        front: "electrodomésticos",
        back: "home appliances",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q9kp3HZOu1",
      },
      {
        front: "entonces",
        back: "then",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vWE36e9soS",
      },
      {
        front: "estilo",
        back: "style",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hnkItjCbdF",
      },
      {
        front: "estilos",
        back: "styles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WDImpAT2oK",
      },
      {
        front: "forma",
        back: "form",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UR0baQc6MV",
      },
      {
        front: "formas",
        back: "shapes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i0FGqo2eTj",
      },
      {
        front: "material",
        back: "material",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fzalDV0YEa",
      },
      {
        front: "mediana",
        back: "median",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GfsOkQ67fE",
      },
      {
        front: "medianas",
        back: "medians",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CU9ispNRGi",
      },
      {
        front: "mediano",
        back: "medium",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "autxNjRVPQ",
      },
      {
        front: "medianos",
        back: "medium",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4gpCcqC2Ho",
      },
      {
        front: "mesa de noche",
        back: "nightstand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KlnKtdQW8A",
      },
      {
        front: "mesas de noche",
        back: "Night tables",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S24pxkd7Pi",
      },
      {
        front: "objeto",
        back: "object",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "86vMLxAy3O",
      },
      {
        front: "objetos",
        back: "objects",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "llL08kegIX",
      },
      {
        front: "por ciento",
        back: "percent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0DXK7ZDxkX",
      },
      {
        front: "renovaste",
        back: "you renewed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zdkGrav859",
      },
      {
        front: "secciones",
        back: "sections",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3vpXedn4Vu",
      },
      {
        front: "sección",
        back: "section",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qgMX8kviJV",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Jz5U2xocjj",
    title: "Unit 98",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ePS7gTzTFB",
      },
      {
        front: "activas",
        back: "active",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H0RR9Q8Ttz",
      },
      {
        front: "activo",
        back: "active",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YodcvBy1eE",
      },
      {
        front: "activos",
        back: "active",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tS3GoZeFLi",
      },
      {
        front: "al",
        back: "to the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OtUldmLflK",
      },
      {
        front: "al mismo tiempo",
        back: "at the same time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4eiC9OOqVt",
      },
      {
        front: "basura",
        back: "trash",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fujI5zk7z9",
      },
      {
        front: "cepillabas",
        back: "you brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "98UBWyK1jt",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        back: "from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S0sopqS3sY",
      },
      {
        front: "despertador",
        back: "alarm clock",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ILHYjfjfm6",
      },
      {
        front: "divertirme",
        back: "have fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RvksKhHRvn",
      },
      {
        front: "divertirte",
        back: "have fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qjZYydP4Mc",
      },
      {
        front: "ducharse",
        back: "get a shower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LZ5nQZjUT4",
      },
      {
        front: "gemela",
        back: "twin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7x20d1TM7f",
      },
      {
        front: "gemelo",
        back: "twin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jKjRTVUzMw",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarme",
        back: "wash myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n8WUCKJJId",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarse",
        back: "wash up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n1NOkfykp0",
      },
      {
        front: "lavarte",
        back: "wash yourself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hWQb6bomvq",
      },
      {
        front: "me maquillo",
        back: "I put on make up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nZWYPczcCl",
      },
      {
        front: "me preocupaba",
        back: "it worried me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3Ef1dqrR9m",
      },
      {
        front: "menos que",
        back: "less than",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JsMhEpqqmL",
      },
      {
        front: "más que",
        back: "more than",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X3qPAMEsXr",
      },
      {
        front: "nos cepillábamos",
        back: "we brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kkt9KA9EDz",
      },
      {
        front: "nos divertimos",
        back: "we had fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pPxDSgnIvY",
      },
      {
        front: "nos levantábamos",
        back: "we got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YtEdXZsJ6b",
      },
      {
        front: "nos relajamos",
        back: "we relax",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JTouQiPUqV",
      },
      {
        front: "ojo",
        back: "eye",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MTovoXIfVS",
      },
      {
        front: "relajarse",
        back: "relax",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "APfsWpGd9f",
      },
      {
        front: "rutina",
        back: "routine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aKFcqBsuTJ",
      },
      {
        front: "sacarla",
        back: "take it out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gJkL1fil3T",
      },
      {
        front: "sacas",
        back: "you take out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "82VNGwbLif",
      },
      {
        front: "se cepillaban",
        back: "they brushed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VF5vY8zILq",
      },
      {
        front: "se divierte",
        back: "have fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "94vN0J8z3v",
      },
      {
        front: "se levantaban",
        back: "they got up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "os5yHjNj11",
      },
      {
        front: "se preocupaba",
        back: "He cared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ijN62axelV",
      },
      {
        front: "se preocupaban",
        back: "they cared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l1b1tcuKaW",
      },
      {
        front: "tanto como",
        back: "as much as",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C7cZbhSW2u",
      },
      {
        front: "te diviertes",
        back: "do you have fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xvKsxuuCZF",
      },
      {
        front: "te maquillas",
        back: "do you make up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aLej0BgQNg",
      },
      {
        front: "tiempo libre",
        back: "leisure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o5qVDXxbUS",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tcDiv3sAWG",
    title: "Unit 99",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "commands31",
        back: "commands31",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a0w0IivSqU",
      },
      {
        front: "commands32",
        back: "commands32",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MK28Ca7RKa",
      },
      {
        front: "commands33",
        back: "commands33",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XFOLtIOu5w",
      },
      {
        front: "commands",
        back: "commands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2MebtIu3Hq",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "y5srn7crMQ",
    title: "Unit 100",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abogada",
        back: "a lawyer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oeg4jChS0o",
      },
      {
        front: "abogadas",
        back: "lawyers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8O2gq0kF1K",
      },
      {
        front: "abogado",
        back: "attorney",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wkf9Cd4wPn",
      },
      {
        front: "abogados",
        back: "lawyers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iTRWzB5aVf",
      },
      {
        front: "asistente",
        back: "attendee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y97PJwQVVd",
      },
      {
        front: "beneficio",
        back: "benefit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5xqsnadu7d",
      },
      {
        front: "beneficios",
        back: "Benefits",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G5WngXnXYZ",
      },
      {
        front: "búsqueda",
        back: "search",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TvFI7ixaYj",
      },
      {
        front: "búsquedas",
        back: "searches",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Qj4pZEzwfM",
      },
      {
        front: "calculadora",
        back: "calculator",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dHyS2RHiPx",
      },
      {
        front: "calculadoras",
        back: "calculators",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kjkw8NbkBS",
      },
      {
        front: "contabilidad",
        back: "accounting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eIbvMgbNvS",
      },
      {
        front: "copia",
        back: "copy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6oGMUehqBQ",
      },
      {
        front: "copias",
        back: "do you copy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VwIg0qxUCN",
      },
      {
        front: "dedicado",
        back: "dedicated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "032TreQu0V",
      },
      {
        front: "dedicarse",
        back: "dedicate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3bXWU6YqGm",
      },
      {
        front: "desorganizada",
        back: "disorganized",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aX8iUVEhpe",
      },
      {
        front: "desorganizadas",
        back: "disorganized",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V06ymKCwWU",
      },
      {
        front: "desorganizados",
        back: "disorganized",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NUDxD0YY1V",
      },
      {
        front: "empleada",
        back: "employee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3FTMHQEhxl",
      },
      {
        front: "empleadas",
        back: "employees",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0ZNbpdvRRL",
      },
      {
        front: "empleado",
        back: "employee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iMf2o7yYbF",
      },
      {
        front: "empleados",
        back: "staff",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hvGEZi3Zoh",
      },
      {
        front: "exporta",
        back: "export",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kRCFrnJo9N",
      },
      {
        front: "firma",
        back: "signature",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kpJfnAo6qm",
      },
      {
        front: "ley",
        back: "law",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w3pV6U9Vrv",
      },
      {
        front: "leyes",
        back: "laws",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B7PEJ0kt6e",
      },
      {
        front: "me dedico",
        back: "I dedicate myself",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ly0ofYm92b",
      },
      {
        front: "nos dedicamos",
        back: "Our services are",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WDjmpU5FaO",
      },
      {
        front: "producción",
        back: "production",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yGGgImi2qV",
      },
      {
        front: "producto",
        back: "product",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOJYCziLhY",
      },
      {
        front: "productos",
        back: "products",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "38yVLEpJK7",
      },
      {
        front: "profesional",
        back: "professional",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nzld50hYz7",
      },
      {
        front: "profesionales",
        back: "professionals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AISTf1sKLP",
      },
      {
        front: "profesiones",
        back: "Professions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XMCrd2DGH0",
      },
      {
        front: "profesión",
        back: "profession",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1ZGW317Yeq",
      },
      {
        front: "quien",
        back: "who",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hqhst8nXm1",
      },
      {
        front: "rol",
        back: "role",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "celXUvePyx",
      },
      {
        front: "roles",
        back: "roles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LryHjn7kno",
      },
      {
        front: "se dedica",
        back: "is dedicated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SpUf58Zr3g",
      },
      {
        front: "tercios",
        back: "thirds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DVgjQdd6qD",
      },
      {
        front: "valor",
        back: "worth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sB9N2sKzd5",
      },
      {
        front: "valores",
        back: "values",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ux8Dm3C6yZ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "4XTe5MdRX3",
    title: "Unit 101",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acuerdo",
        back: "agreement",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1vKvABlfiM",
      },
      {
        front: "acuerdos",
        back: "agreements",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tDX2wMr6uE",
      },
      {
        front: "administración",
        back: "administration",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oRqhUPeaWA",
      },
      {
        front: "agricultura",
        back: "farming",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JriUirraX0",
      },
      {
        front: "alcalde",
        back: "mayor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qGt5HDSx0F",
      },
      {
        front: "alcaldesa",
        back: "mayoress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "79TNCGE1zb",
      },
      {
        front: "arresto",
        back: "arrest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ptZNCp0hsK",
      },
      {
        front: "arrestos",
        back: "arrests",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "56hcefHRNw",
      },
      {
        front: "campaña",
        back: "campaign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hy6ZDHDuIr",
      },
      {
        front: "candidata",
        back: "candidate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yZ7YAnYgS8",
      },
      {
        front: "candidato",
        back: "candidate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4oU4lZKOJF",
      },
      {
        front: "candidatos",
        back: "candidates",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kwZ3OWX82A",
      },
      {
        front: "civil",
        back: "civil",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nex4CXOXI6",
      },
      {
        front: "civiles",
        back: "civilians",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qI1shvEsfm",
      },
      {
        front: "comunidad",
        back: "community",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zBxCsdsEM1",
      },
      {
        front: "conflicto",
        back: "conflict",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zO65jwqk60",
      },
      {
        front: "conflictos",
        back: "conflicts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hPMqtXp20B",
      },
      {
        front: "congreso",
        back: "congress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hafK1Vp1TZ",
      },
      {
        front: "constitución",
        back: "Constitution",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hUN7BcJOdv",
      },
      {
        front: "cooperación",
        back: "cooperation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "noWTSexznE",
      },
      {
        front: "corrupción",
        back: "corruption",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "55lco1kesj",
      },
      {
        front: "crimen",
        back: "crime",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZPZU34prST",
      },
      {
        front: "debate",
        back: "debate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2khPVOQJDB",
      },
      {
        front: "declaraciones",
        back: "statements",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tN6ML2dV0W",
      },
      {
        front: "declaración",
        back: "declaration",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DjiTINgyEh",
      },
      {
        front: "defensa",
        back: "defending",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NkC55GqPyu",
      },
      {
        front: "democracia",
        back: "democracy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8ItQDI4HX",
      },
      {
        front: "democrática",
        back: "democratic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XcN9MCrjw6",
      },
      {
        front: "democrático",
        back: "democratic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c56F3ysV3y",
      },
      {
        front: "demócrata",
        back: "democrat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A0gywKF4an",
      },
      {
        front: "derecho",
        back: "right",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5A00fXjMJZ",
      },
      {
        front: "derechos",
        back: "Rights",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TuG1oE6HHa",
      },
      {
        front: "dictadura",
        back: "dictatorship",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "04BmlRiQT0",
      },
      {
        front: "dictaduras",
        back: "dictatorships",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CCzCcj03D9",
      },
      {
        front: "discurso",
        back: "speech",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j40EPW1HrJ",
      },
      {
        front: "diálogo",
        back: "dialogue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kJCwRFGMzT",
      },
      {
        front: "déficit",
        back: "deficit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f862kVsZi3",
      },
      {
        front: "ejército",
        back: "army",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aC3CVHxbII",
      },
      {
        front: "elecciones",
        back: "elections",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FLmxoBm20n",
      },
      {
        front: "elección",
        back: "choice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OaYflZFLls",
      },
      {
        front: "electoral",
        back: "electoral",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GO8RBGt8lk",
      },
      {
        front: "electorales",
        back: "electoral",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ANa9bCHEpE",
      },
      {
        front: "embajador",
        back: "ambassador",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IgrjIN7Mk1",
      },
      {
        front: "embajadora",
        back: "ambassador",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hgkXNV333o",
      },
      {
        front: "estabilidad",
        back: "stability",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kSQivHHk9i",
      },
      {
        front: "estrategia",
        back: "strategy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4yyfsdoz5L",
      },
      {
        front: "federación",
        back: "federation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "66G7P7i1un",
      },
      {
        front: "federal",
        back: "federal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I1Dyol4uU9",
      },
      {
        front: "gobernador",
        back: "governor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DA7kv7geiz",
      },
      {
        front: "gobierno",
        back: "government",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N9ZuCdMpvu",
      },
      {
        front: "humano",
        back: "human",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DbZ2yGGJyP",
      },
      {
        front: "ilegal",
        back: "illegal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZCPnx0Bxvb",
      },
      {
        front: "imperio",
        back: "empire",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yCWdVpWGbA",
      },
      {
        front: "imperios",
        back: "empires",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GuVHqZUega",
      },
      {
        front: "impuesto",
        back: "tax",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xr9GUpWl4C",
      },
      {
        front: "impuestos",
        back: "taxes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5bb9H4kXJu",
      },
      {
        front: "independencia",
        back: "independence",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k6XGUZQCiI",
      },
      {
        front: "justicia",
        back: "Justice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VIjfkN3k7m",
      },
      {
        front: "legislación",
        back: "legislation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "clGUXfAH5F",
      },
      {
        front: "libertad",
        back: "Liberty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CgljoMWIld",
      },
      {
        front: "líder",
        back: "Leader",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lkFKQOnT8O",
      },
      {
        front: "líderes",
        back: "leaders",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R9eUwc31DR",
      },
      {
        front: "manifestaciones",
        back: "demonstrations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yAaojehaTz",
      },
      {
        front: "manifestación",
        back: "manifestation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pdW10zX643",
      },
      {
        front: "ministerio",
        back: "ministry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pDK2JE3EFk",
      },
      {
        front: "ministra",
        back: "minister",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fGCxAcXH6c",
      },
      {
        front: "ministro",
        back: "Minister",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MkxFwEDvin",
      },
      {
        front: "oposición",
        back: "opposition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wDWaBv8EOk",
      },
      {
        front: "organismo",
        back: "organism",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0eC2a2JJ79",
      },
      {
        front: "organismos",
        back: "organisms",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rVlZGu18s4",
      },
      {
        front: "organizaciones",
        back: "organizations",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9eyb57XMeM",
      },
      {
        front: "organización",
        back: "organization",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UFKjT1CfeY",
      },
      {
        front: "pobreza",
        back: "poverty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3kmhkkjM2X",
      },
      {
        front: "poder",
        back: "can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TcK5YZuvY1",
      },
      {
        front: "poderes",
        back: "powers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a74INRLhww",
      },
      {
        front: "política",
        back: "politics",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oVU1ArUyQp",
      },
      {
        front: "políticas",
        back: "policies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cWQatbdQWZ",
      },
      {
        front: "político",
        back: "political",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XQYTaq0ZA7",
      },
      {
        front: "políticos",
        back: "politicians",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8ttyk6Kh0e",
      },
      {
        front: "presidencia",
        back: "presidency",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r2KMZZAzFJ",
      },
      {
        front: "presidencial",
        back: "presidential",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4bUILvNf4Y",
      },
      {
        front: "presupuesto",
        back: "budget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cVR62qJn9V",
      },
      {
        front: "pública",
        back: "public",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0jvkyVY62G",
      },
      {
        front: "públicas",
        back: "public",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uA0IkZnKU3",
      },
      {
        front: "público",
        back: "public",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ubYzKQL99G",
      },
      {
        front: "públicos",
        back: "public",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xmbsLSLakq",
      },
      {
        front: "republicano",
        back: "republican",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "45gsrVEaQZ",
      },
      {
        front: "república",
        back: "republic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v4cIzJWWlj",
      },
      {
        front: "riqueza",
        back: "wealth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qznjaU3Ern",
      },
      {
        front: "riquezas",
        back: "riches",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3Oz46IduiQ",
      },
      {
        front: "seguridad",
        back: "safety",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WH5BAzWqsV",
      },
      {
        front: "senador",
        back: "senator",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4aW86Jkrnu",
      },
      {
        front: "senadores",
        back: "senators",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Z5EmFeWJOz",
      },
      {
        front: "social",
        back: "Social",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IPv9A8wJ6j",
      },
      {
        front: "socialista",
        back: "socialist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kluRgagj7h",
      },
      {
        front: "sociedad",
        back: "society",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XOuO912lV5",
      },
      {
        front: "violencia",
        back: "violence",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OhmrZU1Z9k",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "wuinen4FSR",
    title: "Unit 103",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "academia",
        back: "academy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0cPBsun4xQ",
      },
      {
        front: "academias",
        back: "academies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KoWf19pwwv",
      },
      {
        front: "acento",
        back: "accent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O7HIQm2sM0",
      },
      {
        front: "autor",
        back: "Author",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lFYOsyAq7Y",
      },
      {
        front: "autora",
        back: "author",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sdo6RsxCPd",
      },
      {
        front: "autoras",
        back: "authors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cs4W9uERmI",
      },
      {
        front: "biografía",
        back: "Biography",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xn08n1yhVs",
      },
      {
        front: "caminando",
        back: "walking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3loKH2OIeP",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinando",
        back: "cooking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZSE74g1D6U",
      },
      {
        front: "corriendo",
        back: "in a hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pMK6qMqccA",
      },
      {
        front: "corrigiendo",
        back: "correcting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tF4XTgLMzI",
      },
      {
        front: "eligiendo",
        back: "picking out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WODA4KnImz",
      },
      {
        front: "en este momento",
        back: "at this time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yOQm8IoQkp",
      },
      {
        front: "ficción",
        back: "fiction",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s9E1qdr6Sm",
      },
      {
        front: "heroína",
        back: "heroin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BVVOEbl1Ps",
      },
      {
        front: "heroínas",
        back: "heroines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dQ7awQGB4r",
      },
      {
        front: "héroe",
        back: "hero",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UJLs6JkbD0",
      },
      {
        front: "llamando",
        back: "calling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JmlgTT4PCP",
      },
      {
        front: "llamándolo",
        back: "calling him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BpAnW1y6iE",
      },
      {
        front: "línea",
        back: "line",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aaWsLoV3UI",
      },
      {
        front: "líneas",
        back: "lines",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gXuDw9EPZN",
      },
      {
        front: "multiplicar",
        back: "multiply",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zjCmRVEaw7",
      },
      {
        front: "multiplicarlos",
        back: "multiply them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iR6z3UcJ1u",
      },
      {
        front: "números",
        back: "numbers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GlLzZB9IzR",
      },
      {
        front: "respondiendo",
        back: "answering",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hc85sF4aAb",
      },
      {
        front: "siguiendo",
        back: "Following",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "562dV4ZwFm",
      },
      {
        front: "solo",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lykrkdT56T",
      },
      {
        front: "tomando",
        back: "taking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WrYK9DSmuW",
      },
      {
        front: "viendo",
        back: "watching",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eIgowFqd0F",
      },
      {
        front: "visitando",
        back: "visiting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xaR3dWGaND",
      },
      {
        front: "visitándolos",
        back: "visiting them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZyopE69MRX",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "wctmvcYRuV",
    title: "Unit 104",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "alguien",
        back: "someone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aEpEGngPwU",
      },
      {
        front: "amistad",
        back: "friendship",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y4NYqVyGA5",
      },
      {
        front: "audiencia",
        back: "audience",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fLHr6a6E3j",
      },
      {
        front: "caballero",
        back: "Knight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2EyS7TkDEW",
      },
      {
        front: "campesino",
        back: "farmer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kP4N1CZrzE",
      },
      {
        front: "campesinos",
        back: "farmers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7WPxjmlUXi",
      },
      {
        front: "ciudadana",
        back: "citizen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aHgJJNMrj9",
      },
      {
        front: "ciudadano",
        back: "citizen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kbJuoziFkR",
      },
      {
        front: "ciudadanos",
        back: "citizens",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NKpKeeNbJi",
      },
      {
        front: "con calma",
        back: "calmly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n5JGp6CRyC",
      },
      {
        front: "confiar",
        back: "rely",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rbSNWwqwHf",
      },
      {
        front: "costumbre",
        back: "custom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AH4CXWQPRs",
      },
      {
        front: "costumbres",
        back: "customs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bVEFMq3n6A",
      },
      {
        front: "doble",
        back: "double",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LApFyxkK5l",
      },
      {
        front: "enemigo",
        back: "enemy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LQYjPLDLtb",
      },
      {
        front: "enemigos",
        back: "enemies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "55RplEc2tQ",
      },
      {
        front: "feria",
        back: "fair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BGtlzgX1Y6",
      },
      {
        front: "gentes",
        back: "people",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9YHzKoSFD6",
      },
      {
        front: "humanidad",
        back: "humanity",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OXeaayLfcT",
      },
      {
        front: "individuo",
        back: "individual",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VVmxL9VUFm",
      },
      {
        front: "individuos",
        back: "individuals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PDzwqtOvDr",
      },
      {
        front: "matrimonio",
        back: "marriage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o0dBPCo5gl",
      },
      {
        front: "mil",
        back: "one thousand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LAE10QL6BP",
      },
      {
        front: "miles",
        back: "Thousands",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j1ayCOZCvK",
      },
      {
        front: "nadie",
        back: "no one",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cOiJtN8WYE",
      },
      {
        front: "ni",
        back: "neither",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fWODQH3T3F",
      },
      {
        front: "paciente",
        back: "patient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CSmj9eOw2n",
      },
      {
        front: "pareja",
        back: "couple",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yXEsn5vVES",
      },
      {
        front: "personalidad",
        back: "personality",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WtpfnrSrVT",
      },
      {
        front: "revolución",
        back: "revolution",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U5Y3A9R8ny",
      },
      {
        front: "sentirse",
        back: "feel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JkymAYrrm9",
      },
      {
        front: "sino",
        back: "otherwise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hBRputkhxI",
      },
      {
        front: "tercera",
        back: "third",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P1NkTARWBO",
      },
      {
        front: "tercero",
        back: "third",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SwhYyfZ6Ce",
      },
      {
        front: "testigo",
        back: "witness",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SyZYN9XGkX",
      },
      {
        front: "testigos",
        back: "witnesses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OW6W7ITpHP",
      },
      {
        front: "todos",
        back: "everyone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sdIZZNUXvz",
      },
      {
        front: "toneladas",
        back: "tons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4q4Y1qXKKG",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajador",
        back: "employee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dCXgfCcW76",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajadoras",
        back: "workers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mLag0aRTCf",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajadores",
        back: "workers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ALbQYk59cA",
      },
      {
        front: "turismos",
        back: "passenger cars",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hToh57C93f",
      },
      {
        front: "tímido",
        back: "shy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1aE9otdhMy",
      },
      {
        front: "vecina",
        back: "neighbor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vuKcmvFgiw",
      },
      {
        front: "vecino",
        back: "neighbour",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sXfVyl1VwP",
      },
      {
        front: "vecinos",
        back: "neighbours",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gUhp6w579m",
      },
      {
        front: "víctima",
        back: "victim",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pwg6nTtaVX",
      },
      {
        front: "víctimas",
        back: "victims",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2sNNSUX6dw",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ATqq3oDjUQ",
    title: "Unit 105",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ayuntamiento",
        back: "town hall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zOIYOFWYqe",
      },
      {
        front: "centro",
        back: "center",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cue2oBH50n",
      },
      {
        front: "colonia",
        back: "Suburb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x6VCKlBpfI",
      },
      {
        front: "colonias",
        back: "colonies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x60M5K1ZZx",
      },
      {
        front: "continente",
        back: "continent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C7d2UgvTWW",
      },
      {
        front: "continentes",
        back: "continents",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cPrZuPVVRs",
      },
      {
        front: "criar",
        back: "breed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vNxwGjkS4v",
      },
      {
        front: "cárcel",
        back: "jail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wUTWhsn8uz",
      },
      {
        front: "de",
        back: "from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bSOhKD0t4A",
      },
      {
        front: "desde",
        back: "since",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s5kKbmcRmI",
      },
      {
        front: "estrecho",
        back: "narrow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sJTDdrf6ES",
      },
      {
        front: "hacienda",
        back: "tax authorities",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ujcLBfvP6D",
      },
      {
        front: "hogar",
        back: "home",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c1wNlukUqD",
      },
      {
        front: "hogares",
        back: "homes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fEWKxjR03p",
      },
      {
        front: "instituciones",
        back: "institutions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A3Mw9A1Ba6",
      },
      {
        front: "institución",
        back: "institution",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yXGnUJA4nQ",
      },
      {
        front: "instituto",
        back: "Institute",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z967OpwwhC",
      },
      {
        front: "nación",
        back: "nation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "puJQTF1q1t",
      },
      {
        front: "oestes",
        back: "wests",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jbDXLJSoKZ",
      },
      {
        front: "palacio",
        back: "palace",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gmlgb1Gecl",
      },
      {
        front: "parecer",
        back: "seem",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G58czwvRS0",
      },
      {
        front: "pasado",
        back: "last",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f5ZoHsWU2W",
      },
      {
        front: "pasear",
        back: "sightseeing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LPd7hWsXbC",
      },
      {
        front: "patria",
        back: "homeland",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cCsrQCpdwZ",
      },
      {
        front: "pista",
        back: "clue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0V7YiaXm8l",
      },
      {
        front: "pistas",
        back: "tracks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "seeqhP5yrZ",
      },
      {
        front: "puerto",
        back: "port",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nr0UVO4Bq0",
      },
      {
        front: "terreno",
        back: "ground",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4cXiHtyWT2",
      },
      {
        front: "territorio",
        back: "territory",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qQ4jL4liXe",
      },
      {
        front: "torre",
        back: "tower",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GIbY4XIQbw",
      },
      {
        front: "torres",
        back: "towers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3WGNZu0HzA",
      },
      {
        front: "venir",
        back: "to come",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4kwCGL6t40",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "fmuatlAVDx",
    title: "Unit 106",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "atletas",
        back: "athletes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2T0fV9GNnr",
      },
      {
        front: "hacer",
        back: "to do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q1BEZBuWnw",
      },
      {
        front: "histórica",
        back: "historical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OSGmL1GNYT",
      },
      {
        front: "infancias",
        back: "childhoods",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NdBpIEU4n0",
      },
      {
        front: "los años",
        back: "the years",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SUGd0awm4X",
      },
      {
        front: "personajes",
        back: "characters",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6tgHnXuvgg",
      },
      {
        front: "período",
        back: "period",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dSByKMYZai",
      },
      {
        front: "público",
        back: "public",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UQ6sWBItqG",
      },
      {
        front: "torneos",
        back: "tournaments",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zORt1OStSf",
      },
      {
        front: "árbitro",
        back: "referee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IkZZSyKqWN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ikCvPh1Daw",
    title: "Unit 107",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aspiradora",
        back: "Vacuum cleaner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J9pbRgIvTT",
      },
      {
        front: "congelador",
        back: "freezer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qGok6UXFIv",
      },
      {
        front: "escalera",
        back: "ladder",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZfMZkMiHbM",
      },
      {
        front: "grifo",
        back: "tap",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TdA9EzqjFn",
      },
      {
        front: "lavavajillas",
        back: "dishwasher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vQrW4oDAMf",
      },
      {
        front: "me la",
        back: "me the",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NCXiwyyMWr",
      },
      {
        front: "me lo",
        back: "I got it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qVYUX3RlJu",
      },
      {
        front: "me los",
        back: "me them",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iCpGzqkrJo",
      },
      {
        front: "se lo",
        back: "I know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UO67m9bXZh",
      },
      {
        front: "te lo",
        back: "you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k65RkCMByR",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "wpxJDRM7dA",
    title: "Unit 108",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "arena",
        back: "sand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WOax96x3sZ",
      },
      {
        front: "aventura",
        back: "adventure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gCrX57BEq7",
      },
      {
        front: "gigante",
        back: "huge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WaMuVftBOj",
      },
      {
        front: "hacer",
        back: "to do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bGAPiA0WRQ",
      },
      {
        front: "invisible",
        back: "invisible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QuP8nq0Lrq",
      },
      {
        front: "mágico",
        back: "magical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1QDU4GVmSh",
      },
      {
        front: "poder",
        back: "can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "riBiHORI1C",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gXFpXmPdfB",
      },
      {
        front: "saber",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0qBg7eNCXy",
      },
      {
        front: "sabrías",
        back: "You'd know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8YD1LdnMVb",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "uwzR41VcaD",
    title: "Unit 109",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pronouns1",
        back: "pronouns1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U49eOEo6Va",
      },
      {
        front: "pronouns2",
        back: "pronouns2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uChPvwKvSH",
      },
      {
        front: "pronouns3",
        back: "pronouns3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ghymTAGgCA",
      },
      {
        front: "pronouns",
        back: "pronouns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lEtnC38Ms7",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "RoPaqSC4dy",
    title: "Unit 110",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "contestar",
        back: "answer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1ODloPcI41",
      },
      {
        front: "continuar",
        back: "continue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Zf8r9KNTcP",
      },
      {
        front: "correo",
        back: "mail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cQ8WtQwQVU",
      },
      {
        front: "llevar",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "veydB8Q4BA",
      },
      {
        front: "ratos",
        back: "rats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1IPCQRIXs2",
      },
      {
        front: "respuesta",
        back: "reply",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IKsUJPdWFH",
      },
      {
        front: "seguimos",
        back: "we continue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dHqQsbOCjm",
      },
      {
        front: "seguir",
        back: "continue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3ksWw9zwl8",
      },
      {
        front: "sigo",
        back: "I follow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lt9xuZuM9d",
      },
      {
        front: "sigues",
        back: "are you still",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pfYYUy45uu",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tcfjmJElke",
    title: "Unit 110",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cabaña",
        back: "cabin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2l9NegzGzY",
      },
      {
        front: "comienzo",
        back: "start",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EL1JkE79QZ",
      },
      {
        front: "desde que",
        back: "since",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "73ON8oXTuE",
      },
      {
        front: "despierto",
        back: "awake",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wdrg8ygwqG",
      },
      {
        front: "durar",
        back: "to last",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WdOe1FXrQ0",
      },
      {
        front: "en punto",
        back: "o'clock",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JoGgONpLSI",
      },
      {
        front: "extrañar",
        back: "miss",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "muVUhI9F3q",
      },
      {
        front: "hacer",
        back: "to do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BXAIXLJapj",
      },
      {
        front: "musical",
        back: "musical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lPWV1eqHQf",
      },
      {
        front: "sin parar",
        back: "non-stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tPeFAoPzwc",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "PfQ5ZDeksc",
    title: "Unit 110",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ayúdame",
        back: "Help me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Dd85quQ0t7",
      },
      {
        front: "dale",
        back: "Go ahead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TZb9WLUOOA",
      },
      {
        front: "dile",
        back: "tell him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kndo9lqyag",
      },
      {
        front: "equivocado",
        back: "wrong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w95ihVCNGT",
      },
      {
        front: "explícame",
        back: "explain to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b8FPLLpS8f",
      },
      {
        front: "explícamelo",
        back: "explain it to me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C6S9lb8BQg",
      },
      {
        front: "préstame",
        back: "Lend me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DdLDOkY2Q1",
      },
      {
        front: "préstamelo",
        back: "lend me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kQ36v6Wu8b",
      },
      {
        front: "pídele",
        back: "ask him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h8JJv2WW0H",
      },
      {
        front: "pídeselo",
        back: "ask him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hBXIt8S7lF",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0xe1x85iPI",
    title: "Unit 111",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "costumbre",
        back: "custom",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FDgDlYi8S3",
      },
      {
        front: "fuera",
        back: "outside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EAzomk1Trk",
      },
      {
        front: "se almuerza",
        back: "Have lunch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wIZknJc2Xc",
      },
      {
        front: "se desayuna",
        back: "have breakfast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XQ2GzZ5kJc",
      },
      {
        front: "se puede",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DbTiyNv4LC",
      },
      {
        front: "cenar",
        back: "you can have dinner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rBWhOgnc3T",
      },
      {
        front: "se puede ir",
        back: "you can go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oInXiLj0J7",
      },
      {
        front: "se trabaja",
        back: "you work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uSvsSdjxhx",
      },
      {
        front: "se usa",
        back: "it's used",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7nIeHInAPO",
      },
      {
        front: "se vive",
        back: "you live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y0gd7ryH9a",
      },
      {
        front: "tradicionales",
        back: "traditional",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SEnTDb21LN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "dolhmgVEZF",
    title: "Unit 112",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "asesino",
        back: "killer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HZvFtjEXKx",
      },
      {
        front: "daba",
        back: "gave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EFTkXRPKO5",
      },
      {
        front: "dar",
        back: "give",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xa3FwThe9Z",
      },
      {
        front: "de terror",
        back: "Horror",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wrOoU5MPyj",
      },
      {
        front: "el otro día",
        back: "the other day",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "odtp4f6Cd9",
      },
      {
        front: "esconderse",
        back: "hide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2HAsWb2r8Z",
      },
      {
        front: "grito",
        back: "scream",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "So9xmTq4cA",
      },
      {
        front: "oscuridad",
        back: "darkness",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DCFLdQCwe9",
      },
      {
        front: "pesadilla",
        back: "nightmare",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZW1RWz8RxF",
      },
      {
        front: "sombra",
        back: "shadow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rTC5gqQ4TV",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "SLtTUZzxoz",
    title: "Unit 112",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "buscar",
        back: "seek",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZQ3fPgYkte",
      },
      {
        front: "busqué",
        back: "I searched",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "neQKERoUoK",
      },
      {
        front: "crucé",
        back: "crossing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PzvlIUpQqe",
      },
      {
        front: "de vacaciones",
        back: "vacation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x6xTF6PxMy",
      },
      {
        front: "jugar",
        back: "play",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AWS3ZQs7YU",
      },
      {
        front: "jugué",
        back: "i played",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "he77G9k97a",
      },
      {
        front: "madrastra",
        back: "stepmother",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MvTUAR9xha",
      },
      {
        front: "padrastro",
        back: "stepfather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kNlyA9eJO0",
      },
      {
        front: "sobrino",
        back: "nephew",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OngPRXHyMT",
      },
      {
        front: "tiburón",
        back: "shark",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZtU8wHYFha",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "B2H2c7dnc3",
    title: "Unit 113",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pasttense71",
        back: "pasttense71",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XyQlRTpX83",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense72",
        back: "pasttense72",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NgqZ1omP3p",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense73",
        back: "pasttense73",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "azegJgZeRK",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense",
        back: "pasttense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3Jo4EwRRWs",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "bYowo1yedL",
    title: "Unit 114",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "auto",
        back: "auto",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IiGmQzfUUG",
      },
      {
        front: "cruces",
        back: "crosses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gK33zFP4YZ",
      },
      {
        front: "dobles",
        back: "double",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j8ifhuv9H1",
      },
      {
        front: "mira",
        back: "sight",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7Ywfma5nyV",
      },
      {
        front: "por",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5YZsW3WQRn",
      },
      {
        front: "prohibido",
        back: "forbidden",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yuPL95Q0go",
      },
      {
        front: "semáforo",
        back: "traffic lights",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yqTMcDIi68",
      },
      {
        front: "toma",
        back: "taking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5xeLaNuxY0",
      },
      {
        front: "tránsito",
        back: "transit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wNRXem9mhl",
      },
      {
        front: "ubicación",
        back: "Location",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VUBwAiYvJr",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "nlByampyRH",
    title: "Unit 114",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aspirina",
        back: "aspirin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XrokIp8Bmu",
      },
      {
        front: "fiebre",
        back: "fever",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fEyMGAtDUG",
      },
      {
        front: "garganta",
        back: "throat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GySRLQIsKF",
      },
      {
        front: "gripe",
        back: "flu",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SM2wayFeg7",
      },
      {
        front: "hombro",
        back: "shoulder",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kPYplWvCfA",
      },
      {
        front: "lastimarse",
        back: "injure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5VsZMJLvl2",
      },
      {
        front: "llame",
        back: "I called",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y73miQUeeR",
      },
      {
        front: "mucho",
        back: "a lot of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SVcFqDPwon",
      },
      {
        front: "rodilla",
        back: "knee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b9hv1NZLsO",
      },
      {
        front: "se preocupe",
        back: "worry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tetxuJ94J5",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "WHWiSgZirW",
    title: "Unit 115",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aprenda",
        back: "learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XxeNtfxdGH",
      },
      {
        front: "comamos",
        back: "let's eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DHONBMHJah",
      },
      {
        front: "comedia",
        back: "comedy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aoRfIMG1UB",
      },
      {
        front: "en vez de",
        back: "instead of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iQYFFdrLT2",
      },
      {
        front: "graduación",
        back: "graduation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dbbyPdAlWJ",
      },
      {
        front: "invite",
        back: "invite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Sy9TejQyU",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajes",
        back: "you work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fA6Dyltpsa",
      },
      {
        front: "turístico",
        back: "tourist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IgSWoyIFy6",
      },
      {
        front: "viajen",
        back: "travel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B6bmZL0Fg0",
      },
      {
        front: "vivan",
        back: "live",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ryp7IoG6VW",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "b3B5WlYZpq",
    title: "Unit 115",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "alojamiento",
        back: "accommodation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "01URJSzvjx",
      },
      {
        front: "caribe",
        back: "Caribbean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WqbhPZHjuL",
      },
      {
        front: "compremos",
        back: "let's buy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QV01mg5uoP",
      },
      {
        front: "decidamos",
        back: "let's decide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eyrW2C1EQh",
      },
      {
        front: "excursión",
        back: "excursion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bAAHlBO4Uw",
      },
      {
        front: "hostal",
        back: "lodging house",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PlnS17DGzU",
      },
      {
        front: "lujo",
        back: "luxury",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FWwboH5Yf9",
      },
      {
        front: "pasarla bien",
        back: "have fun",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j0ZHA84kyn",
      },
      {
        front: "veamos",
        back: "let's see",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OsJlT1lru6",
      },
      {
        front: "y si",
        back: "and yes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MlYFWtTcQQ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "GBnrb18rTi",
    title: "Unit 116",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aire acondicionado",
        back: "air conditioner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uB2ezP67bQ",
      },
      {
        front: "arreglar",
        back: "arrange",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BtHXsnoKn8",
      },
      {
        front: "cargador",
        back: "charger",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZBWrpxeVCU",
      },
      {
        front: "control remoto",
        back: "remote control",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EWSFvlicCg",
      },
      {
        front: "guardar",
        back: "save",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nkfsPSajx4",
      },
      {
        front: "mensaje de voz",
        back: "voicemail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kNwUGrngQJ",
      },
      {
        front: "red social",
        back: "social network",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ShOOJuvZqx",
      },
      {
        front: "reenviar",
        back: "Resend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fepiJjA2DM",
      },
      {
        front: "sin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "McKtbN6mja",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "unintentionally",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mBcYGjiHFR",
      },
      {
        front: "wifi",
        back: "Wifi",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s180S5W9O5",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "0R3excleKi",
    title: "Unit 116",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "arrogante",
        back: "arrogant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DGcWpzv9vB",
      },
      {
        front: "desempleado",
        back: "unemployed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cWGr0qffRK",
      },
      {
        front: "fotocopia",
        back: "photocopy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V8R5DKDDO9",
      },
      {
        front: "las afueras de la",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pf1fuZyIqA",
      },
      {
        front: "ciudad",
        back: "the outskirts of the city",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6psAygeQW2",
      },
      {
        front: "llevarse",
        back: "carry off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qCWldY6aVs",
      },
      {
        front: "molesto",
        back: "annoying",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JUHlqQt3p7",
      },
      {
        front: "primer piso",
        back: "first floor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4HRebtKo6e",
      },
      {
        front: "sala de reunión",
        back: "Conference room",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9aT2olSq3b",
      },
      {
        front: "satisfecho",
        back: "satisfied",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BzEZhHQOJb",
      },
      {
        front: "sincero",
        back: "sincere",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ApBiXwkxbO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "u2b3vM9gq4",
    title: "Unit 117",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mz2LsvXQ3b",
      },
      {
        front: "callado",
        back: "reserved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8njvGcWH7I",
      },
      {
        front: "conversador",
        back: "talkative",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y8zK7TOByo",
      },
      {
        front: "cuadro",
        back: "picture",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AafepnOmBX",
      },
      {
        front: "deprimido",
        back: "depressed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FpwDiiBGlc",
      },
      {
        front: "exposición",
        back: "exposition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R5QyTHLjFq",
      },
      {
        front: "extrovertido",
        back: "outgoing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iSMghg98mu",
      },
      {
        front: "fotografía",
        back: "Photography",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IokD3heeK7",
      },
      {
        front: "obra de arte",
        back: "artwork",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LZzsAOmmuk",
      },
      {
        front: "vestido",
        back: "dress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uDzuqUDNKN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "6SnRtBLjAR",
    title: "Unit 118",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aprendan",
        back: "learn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LiuIzT6fKt",
      },
      {
        front: "completar",
        back: "to complete",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOtsB8ht5Z",
      },
      {
        front: "director",
        back: "director",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nfcsMBgttH",
      },
      {
        front: "economía",
        back: "economy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9hJXv7SyUw",
      },
      {
        front: "escribas",
        back: "write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7N7XZc5yCU",
      },
      {
        front: "estudies",
        back: "study",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5O8CSviq3x",
      },
      {
        front: "hablen",
        back: "talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AUYlvSctbH",
      },
      {
        front: "leas",
        back: "read",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BirqwU4pAJ",
      },
      {
        front: "método",
        back: "method",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M3MeBoHdIF",
      },
      {
        front: "sociología",
        back: "sociology",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "de0wjHHwCO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Ktp1umneI4",
    title: "Unit 118",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "elegí",
        back: "I chose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KdXFqsAjL0",
      },
      {
        front: "eligió",
        back: "elected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xCrpdpXM7O",
      },
      {
        front: "entrada",
        back: "entrance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yDfBHszMZD",
      },
      {
        front: "plato principal",
        back: "main dish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0kbOfmmqPN",
      },
      {
        front: "preferí",
        back: "I preferred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bvVpm6gfXg",
      },
      {
        front: "prefirió",
        back: "preferred",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c9modpCSS1",
      },
      {
        front: "repetí",
        back: "I repeated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mFThCaSnCM",
      },
      {
        front: "repitió",
        back: "repeated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I6ejClidmU",
      },
      {
        front: "serví",
        back: "I served",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2a2pSFjId7",
      },
      {
        front: "sirvió",
        back: "served",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pH6dvN1iaP",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "thIpNzqqfC",
    title: "Unit 119",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "subj11",
        back: "subj11",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CB0evl0nsu",
      },
      {
        front: "subj12",
        back: "subj12",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "008r3L9NfT",
      },
      {
        front: "subj13",
        back: "subj13",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FSxX7rq2gl",
      },
      {
        front: "subj",
        back: "subj",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qPSA9B8u6X",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "JM6VX2C4G9",
    title: "Unit 120",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "a",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Az5lfSjNTq",
      },
      {
        front: "aumentar",
        back: "increase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GwK4bUoSTf",
      },
      {
        front: "avisar",
        back: "warn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x8Q6C3VyA4",
      },
      {
        front: "contar",
        back: "count",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j4Aq07wjcZ",
      },
      {
        front: "iba a",
        back: "was going to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JFf5QyRLQN",
      },
      {
        front: "iban a",
        back: "They went to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9Wp5m2gkFR",
      },
      {
        front: "nunca más",
        back: "never more",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ll01LN0qOK",
      },
      {
        front: "portarse",
        back: "behave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "luRZCNKtLq",
      },
      {
        front: "prometer",
        back: "pledge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vm1vSRYHgs",
      },
      {
        front: "sueldo",
        back: "salary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fh41hZXYYI",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "CAY6jKbIjU",
    title: "Unit 120",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "campeonato",
        back: "championship",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yF6LjsOZgf",
      },
      {
        front: "decidido",
        back: "decided",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rvUjwlVlFX",
      },
      {
        front: "desempleo",
        back: "unemployment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sgbzicHQCV",
      },
      {
        front: "enterado",
        back: "aware",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K1LUo779Go",
      },
      {
        front: "final",
        back: "final",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QmLWPy5Ya7",
      },
      {
        front: "liga",
        back: "league",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v1DvUW8xRr",
      },
      {
        front: "medida",
        back: "measure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XHniLK4aCx",
      },
      {
        front: "perdido",
        back: "lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yvkz3uihIg",
      },
      {
        front: "publicado",
        back: "published",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uSAzEQwUXg",
      },
      {
        front: "tomado",
        back: "taken",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jR78rwNUxU",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "LGbwD7W5Oz",
    title: "Unit 121",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "conseguir",
        back: "get",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5c4rDuPY4W",
      },
      {
        front: "dar igual",
        back: "don't care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n4GPPBdp6I",
      },
      {
        front: "divertido",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Raan0YeLMW",
      },
      {
        front: "había",
        back: "there was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vpIyaSPs4q",
      },
      {
        front: "habías",
        back: "you had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "01PMASnvH5",
      },
      {
        front: "invitado",
        back: "guest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KgEWN9Frgw",
      },
      {
        front: "olvidado",
        back: "forgotten",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9QuWPVC8BF",
      },
      {
        front: "prometido",
        back: "fiance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YsRqfqGkSU",
      },
      {
        front: "serie",
        back: "Serie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zQ8Sht57sx",
      },
      {
        front: "temporada",
        back: "season",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YZwhKWPceU",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "f9QXS5Zi6D",
    title: "Unit 122",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aburrirse",
        back: "get bored",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HXAM4VGn8Z",
      },
      {
        front: "anteriormente",
        back: "previously",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bSe0EtWV2f",
      },
      {
        front: "banda",
        back: "band",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nb26sRjKuX",
      },
      {
        front: "divertido",
        back: "funny",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SnimJWOsA7",
      },
      {
        front: "encendido",
        back: "switched on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "f1soLFFlm9",
      },
      {
        front: "fila",
        back: "line",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N0Turtl63V",
      },
      {
        front: "recomendado",
        back: "recommended",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DVRLm2en3R",
      },
      {
        front: "vendido",
        back: "sold out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nC7hjhL6Yj",
      },
      {
        front: "versión",
        back: "version",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W5rLe37Jig",
      },
      {
        front: "último",
        back: "latest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qcSCdBGIRl",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "z1agdSg3xz",
    title: "Unit 122",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "campeonas",
        back: "champions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WUyBBCimbh",
      },
      {
        front: "campeonato",
        back: "championship",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fAQZOZD1fL",
      },
      {
        front: "campeón",
        back: "champion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j5qhdOaH7e",
      },
      {
        front: "cancha",
        back: "court",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DiqRVlIXr2",
      },
      {
        front: "cuenta",
        back: "bill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5aJ1yu3udD",
      },
      {
        front: "de pie",
        back: "standing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jdf0i0dOGn",
      },
      {
        front: "descenso",
        back: "decline",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lPJf3jd6pw",
      },
      {
        front: "entrenamiento",
        back: "training",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m3GS6cKZyk",
      },
      {
        front: "futbolista",
        back: "soccer player",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oSSHgP2l6q",
      },
      {
        front: "gol",
        back: "goal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6dynqVTnUb",
      },
      {
        front: "goles",
        back: "goals",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UDq9sX45FS",
      },
      {
        front: "golfista",
        back: "golfer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iWhBgiuuSA",
      },
      {
        front: "había",
        back: "there was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IBw3rcYpVW",
      },
      {
        front: "haya",
        back: "is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6i4oewDIhj",
      },
      {
        front: "juntarse",
        back: "get together",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xtp4JxclO9",
      },
      {
        front: "liga",
        back: "league",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O42flQhdDJ",
      },
      {
        front: "tenista",
        back: "tennis player",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DpaI9wFl8C",
      },
      {
        front: "torneo",
        back: "tournament",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kOtK7ggZ81",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "3pCScVsZO6",
    title: "Unit 123",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ayúdala",
        back: "help her",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WB2OaaZHlU",
      },
      {
        front: "billete",
        back: "ticket",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vQuoD6tEuC",
      },
      {
        front: "cajero",
        back: "cashier",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CRBQod08Rr",
      },
      {
        front: "cambio",
        back: "change",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3O8C4E8ASH",
      },
      {
        front: "cuenta",
        back: "bill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MXOySsjAlL",
      },
      {
        front: "depositar",
        back: "to deposit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gtW2NqnKJV",
      },
      {
        front: "léalo",
        back: "read it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bJ29rNp92j",
      },
      {
        front: "moneda",
        back: "coin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eeGpceh3zA",
      },
      {
        front: "requisito",
        back: "requirement",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CguD5WPfc5",
      },
      {
        front: "sucursal",
        back: "branch office",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qh83tL3yBY",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "xB6uwe2vO9",
    title: "Unit 124",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "despejado",
        back: "clear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZoFWYztg0Y",
      },
      {
        front: "humedad",
        back: "humidity",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "quOiKal7qL",
      },
      {
        front: "llegar",
        back: "arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1dvGk0CTfW",
      },
      {
        front: "pronóstico",
        back: "forecast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oQDvja7NPo",
      },
      {
        front: "rayo",
        back: "lightning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EtVhVHVQ6T",
      },
      {
        front: "salir",
        back: "go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "05B2QcjEVH",
      },
      {
        front: "templado",
        back: "tempered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BJ0ZLewh2g",
      },
      {
        front: "tiempo",
        back: "weather",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7jbVx1pwTb",
      },
      {
        front: "tormenta eléctrica",
        back: "electric storm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lZ3CunzQJZ",
      },
      {
        front: "trueno",
        back: "thunder",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3mRY6gwPj8",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "R3mFSvAJAj",
    title: "Unit 124",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "subj21",
        back: "subj21",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lyp08uB4hB",
      },
      {
        front: "subj22",
        back: "subj22",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xYleMEvDKu",
      },
      {
        front: "subj23",
        back: "subj23",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e7dByQ3qTD",
      },
      {
        front: "subj",
        back: "subj",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "drVUTWWaU6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "HSunLUUCnW",
    title: "Unit 125",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bueno",
        back: "well",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XQMc6xnYuB",
      },
      {
        front: "en contra de",
        back: "against",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FGTMxsFPMQ",
      },
      {
        front: "en serio",
        back: "really",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w6cKOwDEg7",
      },
      {
        front: "enojarse",
        back: "get angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BpYrmKEEeQ",
      },
      {
        front: "equivocarse",
        back: "make a mistake",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FhDOgX4GqW",
      },
      {
        front: "lo que",
        back: "what",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sTYY98r8u5",
      },
      {
        front: "locura",
        back: "craziness",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XGJRRT3sBt",
      },
      {
        front: "opuesto",
        back: "opposite",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "221wjbDRYq",
      },
      {
        front: "sinceramente",
        back: "to be honest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WSCrFfZ7zQ",
      },
      {
        front: "tontería",
        back: "nuisance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nEWVspO14X",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "leNA1nJC4W",
    title: "Unit 125",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrazar",
        back: "hug",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kW9cY1LYW2",
      },
      {
        front: "ansioso",
        back: "anxious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TbjSXtxSF8",
      },
      {
        front: "divorciarse",
        back: "divorce",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bIZ18CBWKh",
      },
      {
        front: "enamorarse",
        back: "fell in love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LUhJBpiCa5",
      },
      {
        front: "luna de miel",
        back: "Honeymoon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XUnzZYZ4Kq",
      },
      {
        front: "para siempre",
        back: "forever",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nwHCjecMUU",
      },
      {
        front: "por amor",
        back: "for love",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jya2BiHJ7M",
      },
      {
        front: "por mi culpa",
        back: "because of me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tj7bRifEJz",
      },
      {
        front: "pulsera",
        back: "bracelet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "px2O4ZGKII",
      },
      {
        front: "voz",
        back: "voice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZgT1eHWnhu",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Cr6rTlInsR",
    title: "Unit 126",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "conferencia",
        back: "conference",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yeF82j9s9k",
      },
      {
        front: "contrato",
        back: "contract",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zoJOssvd65",
      },
      {
        front: "es bueno que",
        back: "It's good that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dfZ5tivhhM",
      },
      {
        front: "es mejor que",
        back: "is better than",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DY7PBiE9UL",
      },
      {
        front: "estar",
        back: "to be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "shtuhJtDkZ",
      },
      {
        front: "ir",
        back: "to go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hwbqLer6Ra",
      },
      {
        front: "por mi parte",
        back: "for me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nIsBDtqFmb",
      },
      {
        front: "preferir que",
        back: "prefer that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZGBmtYlUMT",
      },
      {
        front: "proponer",
        back: "propose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N8V6ohZP1F",
      },
      {
        front: "revisar",
        back: "check",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hailPlq7af",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "LKxmkbE9gV",
    title: "Unit 127",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "echar",
        back: "throw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gcZXl8jo9A",
      },
      {
        front: "entrenador",
        back: "coach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z7437xJFHt",
      },
      {
        front: "escúchalo",
        back: "listen to it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "htWft5C3ID",
      },
      {
        front: "grites",
        back: "scream",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ir7B1t1tiE",
      },
      {
        front: "lancen",
        back: "throw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1s4gWEUP7n",
      },
      {
        front: "pegar",
        back: "paste",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o4MmncNNSc",
      },
      {
        front: "penal",
        back: "penal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BsLdWwGVcQ",
      },
      {
        front: "portero",
        back: "goalie",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "q1sZd0PmiK",
      },
      {
        front: "pásame",
        back: "pass me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D8WjhLXiWI",
      },
      {
        front: "tírame",
        back: "throw me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "no8nWiEjCA",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "BeWdkUB5Ca",
    title: "Unit 128",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pasttense81",
        back: "pasttense81",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NZ78NPOfVV",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense82",
        back: "pasttense82",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e5Pjyk9Tu2",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense83",
        back: "pasttense83",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RPKdRcE2IA",
      },
      {
        front: "pasttense",
        back: "pasttense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wH6LRzV4qm",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "hHayO81oA2",
    title: "Unit 129",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "afeitador",
        back: "shaver",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kAy7eb7zyi",
      },
      {
        front: "afeitarse",
        back: "shave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ud5ltkq9qX",
      },
      {
        front: "cambiar",
        back: "change",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gyme414BpP",
      },
      {
        front: "corporal",
        back: "bodily",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uBt7uohF2y",
      },
      {
        front: "desodorante",
        back: "deodorant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CFl81X9QeD",
      },
      {
        front: "loción",
        back: "lotion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Y5YU2ceDj4",
      },
      {
        front: "peluquero",
        back: "hairdresser",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LrmOZdEdAO",
      },
      {
        front: "protector solar",
        back: "sunscreen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dMtHXMJDJ7",
      },
      {
        front: "rizado",
        back: "curly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b6lnQCsu3m",
      },
      {
        front: "secador de",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SesbjS73BC",
      },
      {
        front: "pelo",
        back: "hair dryer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S5JYweTH8h",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "YGqeIREmlb",
    title: "Unit 129",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aro",
        back: "ring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dtzBrbo8hC",
      },
      {
        front: "chaleco",
        back: "vest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XjNI7Gknlk",
      },
      {
        front: "colorido",
        back: "colorful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V0Gp14r5ty",
      },
      {
        front: "combinar",
        back: "combine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fKq7gVCvoZ",
      },
      {
        front: "lino",
        back: "linen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pBrD1jrp7l",
      },
      {
        front: "quedar",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J5HQt0MoXa",
      },
      {
        front: "raya",
        back: "stripe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CSQEhEpsI4",
      },
      {
        front: "saco",
        back: "coat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hzTF2Nbm5y",
      },
      {
        front: "suelto",
        back: "loose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "046bp4b6Bk",
      },
      {
        front: "zapatilla",
        back: "shoe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NMyDBkNnCm",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7LZOnz2Y5Q",
    title: "Unit 130",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "apenas",
        back: "barely",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yd61GEQ98b",
      },
      {
        front: "bombilla",
        back: "lightbulb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PY9ePPjGyl",
      },
      {
        front: "enseguida",
        back: "right away",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EJGINnipjS",
      },
      {
        front: "garantía",
        back: "warranty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MOlhKrG5z0",
      },
      {
        front: "prender",
        back: "turn on",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ywReJF4Fmz",
      },
      {
        front: "reparación",
        back: "repair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RjhOwaQP8Z",
      },
      {
        front: "se",
        back: "I know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1a7bUfiHvj",
      },
      {
        front: "se paga",
        back: "is paid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zC9zNvLVT1",
      },
      {
        front: "se puede",
        back: "It can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d7yX2ZACgG",
      },
      {
        front: "similares",
        back: "Similar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xrdkZHmEaL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "LKsDGeAUBh",
    title: "Unit 130",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "colonia",
        back: "Suburb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JT9S6PH9DB",
      },
      {
        front: "cosmético",
        back: "cosmetic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6An4qYrzXm",
      },
      {
        front: "formal",
        back: "formal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tgyh5mpWa2",
      },
      {
        front: "mostrar",
        back: "to show",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Gvurgu2OMl",
      },
      {
        front: "perla",
        back: "pearl",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9V8px6mc41",
      },
      {
        front: "regalártelo",
        back: "give it to you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y1vYutq60m",
      },
      {
        front: "salón de belleza",
        back: "beauty salon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cd8WZ66zMw",
      },
      {
        front: "sofisticado",
        back: "sophisticated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9hPM6g9jJC",
      },
      {
        front: "tacón",
        back: "heel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8pkeL21IEc",
      },
      {
        front: "unos cuantos",
        back: "some",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C3tFR2dkHN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ZHdDBHqJMf",
    title: "Unit 131",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cubierto",
        back: "covered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UwcP6RPm23",
      },
      {
        front: "mariscos",
        back: "seafood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZVjL4tcVBn",
      },
      {
        front: "poder",
        back: "can",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4kGN6KGcGi",
      },
      {
        front: "puede ser",
        back: "could be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mpu9H8Tx0c",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qqz352L1Cw",
      },
      {
        front: "sabor",
        back: "taste",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pf8FnXhdJO",
      },
      {
        front: "servilleta",
        back: "napkin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nXDfJmEsUs",
      },
      {
        front: "sería posible",
        back: "it would be possible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uE9Bovmj0G",
      },
      {
        front: "tocino",
        back: "bacon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pLDpoxGhHP",
      },
      {
        front: "traería",
        back: "bring",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3K7hIvilNz",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "c7rTyqb3B0",
    title: "Unit 131",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "atención",
        back: "attention",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QefFK6bjMg",
      },
      {
        front: "buscar",
        back: "seek",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3ladOY7NK4",
      },
      {
        front: "explicar",
        back: "explain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tNqlc3Y7uE",
      },
      {
        front: "llamar",
        back: "to call",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8HzeQmHOSt",
      },
      {
        front: "llegar",
        back: "arrive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2Xi7SYYwHP",
      },
      {
        front: "negocio",
        back: "deal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H8tr9UoMml",
      },
      {
        front: "ni siquiera",
        back: "not even",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YN7IJbA9D3",
      },
      {
        front: "pagar",
        back: "to pay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zNAbQalHEH",
      },
      {
        front: "queja",
        back: "complaint",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kow9RcUlM9",
      },
      {
        front: "supervisor",
        back: "supervisor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X4oIpeZZzf",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "xrQx7ClEjb",
    title: "Unit 132",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aceptable",
        back: "acceptable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6srooNDDlc",
      },
      {
        front: "atender",
        back: "attend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dgnmfNnWaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "gasto",
        back: "spent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3hGa5AkwIl",
      },
      {
        front: "lógicas",
        back: "logical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zj7OM6SqEr",
      },
      {
        front: "manchado",
        back: "stained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kwOxrNrdtb",
      },
      {
        front: "plazo",
        back: "term",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PiSukeCZN7",
      },
      {
        front: "promoción",
        back: "promotion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fp2ojEadhd",
      },
      {
        front: "quejarse",
        back: "to complain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jln1eKdw2a",
      },
      {
        front: "salir",
        back: "go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BxrQCRfCbB",
      },
      {
        front: "vencido",
        back: "defeated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yKFBRGBxrH",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ft6STL9VLo",
    title: "Unit 133",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ciudad natal",
        back: "native city",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3dBWMyB5UQ",
      },
      {
        front: "cumplir",
        back: "comply",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IGvQV2SBy7",
      },
      {
        front: "extranjero",
        back: "Foreign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TtzZPXSWnz",
      },
      {
        front: "mayor",
        back: "higher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "At45799UO5",
      },
      {
        front: "menor",
        back: "minor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "to4r5Sivve",
      },
      {
        front: "pariente",
        back: "relative",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AmPpAs57Hd",
      },
      {
        front: "sexto",
        back: "sixth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DGooJaszaZ",
      },
      {
        front: "un poco",
        back: "a little",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "80kgKy3Xu7",
      },
      {
        front: "valer la pena",
        back: "worth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GjKXuCaCkE",
      },
      {
        front: "visitado",
        back: "visited",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Tymppo2BPZ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "IGwy8T8d4I",
    title: "Unit 133",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "subj31",
        back: "subj31",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QmVGOhjZEU",
      },
      {
        front: "subj32",
        back: "subj32",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sCMxrUWr9e",
      },
      {
        front: "subj33",
        back: "subj33",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UxOVERGSWj",
      },
      {
        front: "subj",
        back: "subj",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zg0xbe4gSj",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "tiaR4KL50K",
    title: "Unit 134",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "arroyo",
        back: "stream",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "b7t3QoARCI",
      },
      {
        front: "atracción",
        back: "attraction",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PzYpbXLBoA",
      },
      {
        front: "bahía",
        back: "bay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YtawUP2mYr",
      },
      {
        front: "ballena",
        back: "whale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "imGescOwiw",
      },
      {
        front: "cultivo",
        back: "crop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7X8EhY5TaH",
      },
      {
        front: "delfín",
        back: "Dolphin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fOWiMGICOT",
      },
      {
        front: "desastre",
        back: "disaster",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sRZKHWkGWW",
      },
      {
        front: "esencial",
        back: "essential",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LckxLXRm1h",
      },
      {
        front: "marino",
        back: "Marine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j7ved1qdrU",
      },
      {
        front: "ola",
        back: "wave",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wOctQgID4u",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "2Teu0qyub4",
    title: "Unit 135",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "anterior",
        back: "former",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hqWMgwGRUA",
      },
      {
        front: "celebridad",
        back: "celebrity",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bnl83kCk97",
      },
      {
        front: "entrevistar",
        back: "to interview",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iXz2gdyYW5",
      },
      {
        front: "episodio",
        back: "episode",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rULZxughcj",
      },
      {
        front: "espectador",
        back: "viewer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xoItFmrlKA",
      },
      {
        front: "estreno",
        back: "premiere",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "alSaiw8HQs",
      },
      {
        front: "exhibición",
        back: "exhibition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DOXLIO9QIa",
      },
      {
        front: "presentador",
        back: "presenter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZssvUDb9tr",
      },
      {
        front: "retrato",
        back: "portrait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1kEAnnOf8p",
      },
      {
        front: "subtítulo",
        back: "caption",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ur2d6Wj6Dv",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Pj8VHtIwxH",
    title: "Unit 135",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "amanecer",
        back: "dawn",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U3qcSsTMC5",
      },
      {
        front: "aterrizar",
        back: "to land",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "axwPkPOo66",
      },
      {
        front: "bañarse",
        back: "bath",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tDxn94H4lY",
      },
      {
        front: "casi nunca",
        back: "rarely",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NPENtbReH7",
      },
      {
        front: "despegar",
        back: "take off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7t0q1gQrtT",
      },
      {
        front: "dormirse",
        back: "fall sleep",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h1x2rlYhoY",
      },
      {
        front: "embarcar",
        back: "embark",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rdcb7Rk0xD",
      },
      {
        front: "escala",
        back: "scale",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "phq2eiwhWT",
      },
      {
        front: "leyenda",
        back: "legend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FJbAeifOAQ",
      },
      {
        front: "viajero",
        back: "traveler",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zMEQqsMQ9s",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "cmLIVIGLvk",
    title: "Unit 136",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "admitir",
        back: "to admit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cFv9PdXZyE",
      },
      {
        front: "alcaldesas",
        back: "female mayors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DnTxOgIJC5",
      },
      {
        front: "discutir",
        back: "argue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LQyZDRYHfU",
      },
      {
        front: "económico",
        back: "economic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MqmRIOMR0R",
      },
      {
        front: "exactamente",
        back: "exactly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R7UmyewQbI",
      },
      {
        front: "intercambiar",
        back: "to exchange",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0liffdEYrE",
      },
      {
        front: "ministras",
        back: "ministers",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wnHobT9qSW",
      },
      {
        front: "podría ser",
        back: "could be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aokD827A7M",
      },
      {
        front: "punto",
        back: "point",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WxJCCgxcu2",
      },
      {
        front: "yo diría",
        back: "I would say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "POR1HIFvAq",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7ZOemsK1GK",
    title: "Unit 137",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cariñoso",
        back: "affectionate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gfdobvoAXd",
      },
      {
        front: "celoso",
        back: "jealous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YfPEnzSGHU",
      },
      {
        front: "es posible que",
        back: "It is possible that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "koHSO3c5vn",
      },
      {
        front: "furioso",
        back: "furious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2W2umoFwuz",
      },
      {
        front: "hacer una",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Rb0TlAa8ES",
      },
      {
        front: "broma",
        back: "make a joke",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L2jqXwMUkW",
      },
      {
        front: "nada más",
        back: "nothing more",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JimDoa8vvL",
      },
      {
        front: "poner",
        back: "place",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mx0EmH7ZLh",
      },
      {
        front: "salir",
        back: "go out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "30fy7VCN8C",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar",
        back: "drink",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gP3GBAkZUb",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar con",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MbKgbpbM7G",
      },
      {
        front: "calma",
        back: "take it easy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "noZpEwzwcY",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "sGDBXVA99S",
    title: "Unit 137",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a dónde",
        back: "where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "omNjcAfqkK",
      },
      {
        front: "carta de presentación",
        back: "presentation letter",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YDKyM7R3h6",
      },
      {
        front: "desde cuándo",
        back: "since when",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hff0WFThdw",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta dónde",
        back: "until where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9R8R3DVjpK",
      },
      {
        front: "ingeniería",
        back: "engineering",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ol5RfGYztB",
      },
      {
        front: "multinacional",
        back: "multinational",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eVW20BdgLa",
      },
      {
        front: "periodista",
        back: "journalist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iff9bQXErn",
      },
      {
        front: "por dónde",
        back: "where",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6a9enE4Yar",
      },
      {
        front: "renunciar",
        back: "resign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LGRC3p5ddt",
      },
      {
        front: "secretario",
        back: "secretary",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HCmbQrvYYH",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "xOHTJceAwM",
    title: "Unit 138",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "algún día",
        back: "someday",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zBxZI8VdtL",
      },
      {
        front: "cara a cara",
        back: "face to face",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZBdrWxBptK",
      },
      {
        front: "cuanto antes",
        back: "sooner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "n9UoohL65G",
      },
      {
        front: "decir",
        back: "say",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jDgFQL6CRh",
      },
      {
        front: "dudar",
        back: "dude",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "je9YF8davi",
      },
      {
        front: "dudar que",
        back: "doubt that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rMNeyrf40w",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar",
        back: "to talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YL9nvuhDLK",
      },
      {
        front: "perdonar",
        back: "forgive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3zxuTs8GzG",
      },
      {
        front: "querer",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hd1ZOE9heL",
      },
      {
        front: "sensato",
        back: "sensible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nX9DeFwLNL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "F32pZSC43b",
    title: "Unit 139",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "pronouns21",
        back: "pronouns21",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "axxJzuffc4",
      },
      {
        front: "pronouns22",
        back: "pronouns22",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XHxsoWXaUc",
      },
      {
        front: "pronouns23",
        back: "pronouns23",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qOUQwihDJH",
      },
      {
        front: "pronouns",
        back: "pronouns",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fyWyViCZjN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Elo10M9tDG",
    title: "Unit 139",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "dentro de",
        back: "within",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "39oeKwynP3",
      },
      {
        front: "embarazado",
        back: "pregnant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BLNm1JVO4q",
      },
      {
        front: "estricto",
        back: "strict",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bkI5psPHgW",
      },
      {
        front: "fallecer",
        back: "die",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ybRC60gmLa",
      },
      {
        front: "internar",
        back: "intern",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N0y0wHhpFE",
      },
      {
        front: "morir",
        back: "To die",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZWYvffSF9o",
      },
      {
        front: "nacer",
        back: "be born",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KfTMt7XpH6",
      },
      {
        front: "pechos",
        back: "breasts",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lN9CuDEfzN",
      },
      {
        front: "pesar",
        back: "weigh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cqF8NuAS3n",
      },
      {
        front: "urgentemente",
        back: "urgently",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4p9O3H6wf5",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "8eDwSWutFh",
    title: "Unit 140",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "comenzado",
        back: "started",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j0eX7ri0Pi",
      },
      {
        front: "considerar",
        back: "to consider",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JfhTukGLlA",
      },
      {
        front: "construcción",
        back: "building",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J3qXGoD3Q2",
      },
      {
        front: "dificultad",
        back: "difficulty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mN4FuMKunj",
      },
      {
        front: "en",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gZBckzqGZ6",
      },
      {
        front: "total",
        back: "total",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vkvJDRaWn5",
      },
      {
        front: "financiero",
        back: "financial",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "An5E9RKe6K",
      },
      {
        front: "industrias",
        back: "industries",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zgHuvBCVyv",
      },
      {
        front: "producir",
        back: "produce",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PNq7Th7Y9Q",
      },
      {
        front: "reunido",
        back: "gathered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Lnhn8PW5FD",
      },
      {
        front: "trimestre",
        back: "trimester",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RC4ZLCdF95",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "wD9i5sEPTT",
    title: "Unit 141",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "dar las gracias",
        back: "give the thanks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H6hqOVsKLF",
      },
      {
        front: "de nada",
        back: "you are welcome",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5IiLkTN0ap",
      },
      {
        front: "gracias a",
        back: "thanks to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ESytE8Zmvc",
      },
      {
        front: "gracias por",
        back: "thank you for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5FBYm4F1mt",
      },
      {
        front: "gusto",
        back: "taste",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ztuozJHrfD",
      },
      {
        front: "mil gracias",
        back: "thank you",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5wpbnAPuTv",
      },
      {
        front: "muchas gracias",
        back: "Thanks a lot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "S3uTBJDsYb",
      },
      {
        front: "no hay de qué",
        back: "you `re welcome",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PWQdHlhCWu",
      },
      {
        front: "no hay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HXxeeOk370",
      },
      {
        front: "problema",
        back: "No problem",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rIZ0lMJBgb",
      },
      {
        front: "ramo",
        back: "bouquet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iXedNwPuyL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "ubXSEkue3Q",
    title: "Unit 141",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "apurarse",
        back: "hurry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2WrmLSfK4V",
      },
      {
        front: "bombero",
        back: "fireman",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9uyhfixiYi",
      },
      {
        front: "cargar gasolina",
        back: "refuel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3RfjN6xnIk",
      },
      {
        front: "disminuir",
        back: "diminish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WStUTNIUeV",
      },
      {
        front: "humos",
        back: "fumes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6xZyiMSGqI",
      },
      {
        front: "parabrisas",
        back: "windshield",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p4RFg80Kyu",
      },
      {
        front: "por",
        back: "for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LGAJaEe8r4",
      },
      {
        front: "socorro",
        back: "Help",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AqjO0XT9ma",
      },
      {
        front: "tardar",
        back: "delay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AdmXGPZbht",
      },
      {
        front: "velocidades",
        back: "speeds",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EOBzcwt3sY",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Bv1jXhRF3a",
    title: "Unit 142",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "concentrarse",
        back: "concentrate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "P0ySfLHEMs",
      },
      {
        front: "correctamente",
        back: "correctly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MqvptOXdrW",
      },
      {
        front: "desaprobar",
        back: "disapprove",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XRS02ue1Vj",
      },
      {
        front: "duro",
        back: "Lasted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KDvW23gaR2",
      },
      {
        front: "experimento",
        back: "experiment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "j77Km7sOEW",
      },
      {
        front: "fuerte",
        back: "strong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "66C2qUu5jd",
      },
      {
        front: "laboratorios",
        back: "laboratories",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7TYKXEdxku",
      },
      {
        front: "lento",
        back: "slow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fVzemek0Nb",
      },
      {
        front: "promedios",
        back: "averages",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kNYrtPRZJg",
      },
      {
        front: "totalmente",
        back: "completely",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KFCu1KEZoD",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "4gh5JBOq66",
    title: "Unit 143",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "algunos de",
        back: "some of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1ftGkDBmWb",
      },
      {
        front: "arma",
        back: "weapon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VeORzEtdpZ",
      },
      {
        front: "atacar",
        back: "attack",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sSAltSLaxs",
      },
      {
        front: "bombas",
        back: "bombs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "L4pUxnpARg",
      },
      {
        front: "delincuente",
        back: "offender",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GAHTxRirO2",
      },
      {
        front: "explotar",
        back: "blow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zDWKMqBc4g",
      },
      {
        front: "la mitad de",
        back: "half of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0lQYMzz50E",
      },
      {
        front: "terrorista",
        back: "terrorist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EQLLLiRIpP",
      },
      {
        front: "un tercio de",
        back: "a third of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IwHIvKRQ9f",
      },
      {
        front: "uno de",
        back: "one of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a0zwVHQB1w",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "vJYwpGbFAZ",
    title: "Unit 144",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "avena",
        back: "oatmeal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TXgM0GEeev",
      },
      {
        front: "calentar",
        back: "to warm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "h2HHpolJdo",
      },
      {
        front: "cocinemos",
        back: "let's cook",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "flh9Fc4q4l",
      },
      {
        front: "despierte",
        back: "wake up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AzfHdmhyGZ",
      },
      {
        front: "huevos revueltos",
        back: "scrambled eggs",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oJco2VHBS7",
      },
      {
        front: "lasaña",
        back: "lasagna",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vEj7vxzncD",
      },
      {
        front: "merendar",
        back: "to snack",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R89d231V0A",
      },
      {
        front: "quiera",
        back: "want",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a4mgnHs84g",
      },
      {
        front: "recordar a",
        back: "will remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a2AhPGYk4p",
      },
      {
        front: "recuerde",
        back: "remember",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BIxD2gf89N",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jY1hd0Ykbz",
    title: "Unit 145",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bucear",
        back: "Diving",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3jBOBf7ZaD",
      },
      {
        front: "debe haber",
        back: "there must be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OCo3GE6MNZ",
      },
      {
        front: "debe haber sido",
        back: "must have been",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bMDN3pBBj3",
      },
      {
        front: "desafío",
        back: "challenge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c7XJD85ONr",
      },
      {
        front: "dolido",
        back: "hurt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Dm63Dzk67c",
      },
      {
        front: "doloroso",
        back: "painful",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PEELjZugmo",
      },
      {
        front: "justos",
        back: "fair",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gyLJznsGMH",
      },
      {
        front: "rodilla",
        back: "knee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lE0TxpYbIQ",
      },
      {
        front: "sucedido",
        back: "happened",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wOY3gBLJwF",
      },
      {
        front: "victoria",
        back: "victory",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dCpTZE8i3b",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "cXevSnOayH",
    title: "Unit 146",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "al revés",
        back: "upside down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "StCvI90DsU",
      },
      {
        front: "cuidar",
        back: "look after",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8ziZFEz8Fq",
      },
      {
        front: "disculparse",
        back: "apologize",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8BgT9TrVIB",
      },
      {
        front: "echar una mano",
        back: "give a helping hand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FotaIgFkNU",
      },
      {
        front: "es una",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C8fgagyn57",
      },
      {
        front: "pena que",
        back: "it's a pity that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2GXRaZfuAb",
      },
      {
        front: "limpiar",
        back: "clean up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Jxs2gVayvk",
      },
      {
        front: "mantel",
        back: "tablecloth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2DtarEkozm",
      },
      {
        front: "poner la mesa",
        back: "set the table",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bHyZZhrnnY",
      },
      {
        front: "qué mala",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HpID0IFIaN",
      },
      {
        front: "suerte",
        back: "What a bad luck",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QdvvGncnAo",
      },
      {
        front: "regar",
        back: "water",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4zp5BekoiG",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "2XuBteIpzR",
    title: "Unit 147",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "al aire libre",
        back: "outdoor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bskQsYrmnR",
      },
      {
        front: "desilusionado",
        back: "disappointed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hxa84T2mNl",
      },
      {
        front: "discusiones",
        back: "discussions",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N2Zf2mzdYI",
      },
      {
        front: "estuviera",
        back: "I was",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nwMO474jAT",
      },
      {
        front: "evidente",
        back: "evident",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iCrIMPmmo1",
      },
      {
        front: "fuera",
        back: "outside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IdjVQCiFuD",
      },
      {
        front: "fuéramos",
        back: "we were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "plUxxMi7Bk",
      },
      {
        front: "introvertido",
        back: "introvert",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t7mNkHQeOe",
      },
      {
        front: "ojalá",
        back: "I wish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kPDAlnKyku",
      },
      {
        front: "tuviera",
        back: "had",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SWM3GCig7U",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "aozO1uDumt",
    title: "Unit 147",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ambiente",
        back: "ambient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YZbqsUSEQ6",
      },
      {
        front: "condición",
        back: "condition",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W5RuTbooYj",
      },
      {
        front: "decidieran",
        back: "they decided",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "z5kLkSH0E1",
      },
      {
        front: "hablaran",
        back: "they will talk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BjisVPeFHJ",
      },
      {
        front: "humedad",
        back: "humidity",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ganUswSQWk",
      },
      {
        front: "llamara",
        back: "call to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iEehK7T84I",
      },
      {
        front: "medidas",
        back: "measures",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jpqWvuQlTX",
      },
      {
        front: "ruidoso",
        back: "noisy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5fKITpebqX",
      },
      {
        front: "ubicación",
        back: "Location",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wyg8ZGAUt6",
      },
      {
        front: "viera",
        back: "saw",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uOiZxbTfYH",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jhIiLrTJE1",
    title: "Unit 148",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "calabacín",
        back: "zucchini",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OvZIqtbkYm",
      },
      {
        front: "docena",
        back: "dozen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bcd3izJXGr",
      },
      {
        front: "espinaca",
        back: "spinach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uW0scYHyWk",
      },
      {
        front: "fuera",
        back: "outside",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wBBQ3ypsRr",
      },
      {
        front: "fuéramos",
        back: "we were",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BC4PeCdvQR",
      },
      {
        front: "guisante",
        back: "pea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SkOmsIgd16",
      },
      {
        front: "líquido",
        back: "liquid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oJPspqTLtj",
      },
      {
        front: "olla",
        back: "cooking pot",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0BVYO031VQ",
      },
      {
        front: "pimiento",
        back: "pepper",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "N7ldJrEMIi",
      },
      {
        front: "verdulería",
        back: "greengrocery",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tuVJvCJzgw",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "NPdfD4vF2F",
    title: "Unit 149",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "subj51",
        back: "subj51",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wnHmajrRCF",
      },
      {
        front: "subj52",
        back: "subj52",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZaI8unORlc",
      },
      {
        front: "subj53",
        back: "subj53",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k4hEB7XmLe",
      },
      {
        front: "subj",
        back: "subj",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zAXa3HVK5p",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "WY3HJYDbQT",
    title: "Unit 149",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adjuntar",
        back: "to attach",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iwMGtJRllf",
      },
      {
        front: "batería",
        back: "drums",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BW35zjkxe1",
      },
      {
        front: "buscador",
        back: "seeker",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SwYggJ6FX0",
      },
      {
        front: "celular",
        back: "mobile",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ABD8Zn6dUn",
      },
      {
        front: "estafar",
        back: "cheat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nS6pCYczah",
      },
      {
        front: "los de",
        back: "those of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QxzJLYBb5f",
      },
      {
        front: "nombre de usuario",
        back: "Username",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UtT13iQxXO",
      },
      {
        front: "rúter",
        back: "router",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vpD7kLIcNo",
      },
      {
        front: "seguridad",
        back: "safety",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Kc5kNSS4a0",
      },
      {
        front: "señal",
        back: "sign",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dGNU5euFvQ",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "8AK8GNTvpT",
    title: "Unit 150",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "antes de que",
        back: "before",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a3h89vEUU7",
      },
      {
        front: "aproximado",
        back: "approximate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zVAszy3AW4",
      },
      {
        front: "cortar",
        back: "cut",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uxe9GItbv0",
      },
      {
        front: "desenchufar",
        back: "unplug",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nekHE5kmjK",
      },
      {
        front: "electricista",
        back: "electrical technician",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yxY83G8BtQ",
      },
      {
        front: "gases",
        back: "gases",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5Oe1XUaoe4",
      },
      {
        front: "luz",
        back: "light",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jkjVpi4HnO",
      },
      {
        front: "plomero",
        back: "plumber",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eGUvigvdkV",
      },
      {
        front: "presupuesto",
        back: "budget",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Yv3viXzZkW",
      },
      {
        front: "pérdida",
        back: "lost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UgN6BgdLc5",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "l2zvdoQgKT",
    title: "Unit 151",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "atención médica",
        back: "medical care",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ilf85XBgFB",
      },
      {
        front: "inscribirse",
        back: "register",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Emqhh3mszR",
      },
      {
        front: "mayor de",
        back: "greater than",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oVz3nNRuWr",
      },
      {
        front: "menor de",
        back: "less than",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "euNQCupnlM",
      },
      {
        front: "médico",
        back: "medical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WE8p8AO63V",
      },
      {
        front: "obtener",
        back: "get",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AHKz6NISuG",
      },
      {
        front: "seguro",
        back: "sure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oTlpnIdt1Z",
      },
      {
        front: "seguro social",
        back: "social Security",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i1Cia8GPQl",
      },
      {
        front: "solicitar",
        back: "apply for",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xURVSUNrJ7",
      },
      {
        front: "tarifa",
        back: "fee",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nju29nIGrA",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "UhqU7Z3Cp8",
    title: "Unit 151",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bandeja",
        back: "tray",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lRKivQU9fO",
      },
      {
        front: "colgar",
        back: "hang",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Cd6HnNzUrk",
      },
      {
        front: "de alto",
        back: "High",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bzYsE71LbI",
      },
      {
        front: "de largo",
        back: "long",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OgECrVp6Iq",
      },
      {
        front: "de madera",
        back: "of wood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jnSMMcEEO3",
      },
      {
        front: "decorar",
        back: "decorate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2zhrEzp5eQ",
      },
      {
        front: "medir",
        back: "to size",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C5Q7iMjXCt",
      },
      {
        front: "metal",
        back: "metal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PvFWvyixcb",
      },
      {
        front: "persiana",
        back: "blind",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tQlz9r1ou4",
      },
      {
        front: "remodelar",
        back: "remodel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PEFFJt4jYO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Y654RjCySr",
    title: "Unit 152",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "atraer",
        back: "Attract",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Shtag3z6Yd",
      },
      {
        front: "día de los muertos",
        back: "Day of the Dead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OnsAwt3PxR",
      },
      {
        front: "encender",
        back: "light",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oLvS1sU5mL",
      },
      {
        front: "festejar",
        back: "celebrate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vj5n3qsiYU",
      },
      {
        front: "fiesta",
        back: "party",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wz7Tezl0yF",
      },
      {
        front: "fuegos artificiales",
        back: "Fireworks",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TsdY2FK85F",
      },
      {
        front: "janucá",
        back: "hanukkah",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3yl8fzjCJ4",
      },
      {
        front: "judío",
        back: "Jewish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UaRepFisZ5",
      },
      {
        front: "se",
        back: "I know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5xF9pRwmtR",
      },
      {
        front: "se festeja",
        back: "is celebrated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4WkTvJ2CFH",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "84q2Zcm7VS",
    title: "Unit 153",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "británica",
        back: "british",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g26EDYhZQG",
      },
      {
        front: "embajadores",
        back: "ambassadors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GjZnswhnzz",
      },
      {
        front: "joven",
        back: "young",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "k8CN9f7Pog",
      },
      {
        front: "monarquía",
        back: "monarchy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ypaWO6oOBw",
      },
      {
        front: "organizarse",
        back: "get organized",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W7LZtYLpV8",
      },
      {
        front: "partido",
        back: "match",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R4XO0l7db4",
      },
      {
        front: "primer ministro",
        back: "Prime Minister",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "H8WDT4eXc8",
      },
      {
        front: "protestar",
        back: "to protest",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ngi4RF4VGb",
      },
      {
        front: "publicarse",
        back: "be published",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aJ8UNBwDDb",
      },
      {
        front: "sudamericano",
        back: "South American",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SnTnVBPRxD",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "1Y6aE2LKK5",
    title: "Unit 153",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a continuación",
        back: "then",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6bjN5EkY8J",
      },
      {
        front: "aparecer",
        back: "Appear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0BaYnGx6FP",
      },
      {
        front: "apodo",
        back: "Nickname",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7ILIVRtFcl",
      },
      {
        front: "comedia",
        back: "comedy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dXFOhWctE6",
      },
      {
        front: "diseñador",
        back: "designer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TvVTI7YpuL",
      },
      {
        front: "estilista",
        back: "stylist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GdHFCpDt4T",
      },
      {
        front: "peinado",
        back: "hairstyle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "221Uynak8i",
      },
      {
        front: "presentar",
        back: "present",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "24RjBJ6OqX",
      },
      {
        front: "secreto",
        back: "secret",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IFsWWCnvLU",
      },
      {
        front: "volviendo al",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GoDAl62cHU",
      },
      {
        front: "tema",
        back: "Back to the topic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8F8c5gB2N6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "EBkUMUyTnd",
    title: "Unit 154",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "ahorra",
        back: "save",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V7qvO51M5u",
      },
      {
        front: "comercial",
        back: "commercial",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v3492EmiJe",
      },
      {
        front: "cómpralo",
        back: "buy it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "x0b8XpGx7m",
      },
      {
        front: "cómprelo",
        back: "buy it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XC6XsRqMdW",
      },
      {
        front: "encuentre",
        back: "find",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "089xHgYRXi",
      },
      {
        front: "fenomenal",
        back: "phenomenal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VvYoow5bRF",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta",
        back: "until",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xm9mPA4bD4",
      },
      {
        front: "novedad",
        back: "novelty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Il3dhRtxaH",
      },
      {
        front: "solo",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5RVDsXys2e",
      },
      {
        front: "suscribirse",
        back: "to subscribe",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U5loNzEoJW",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "opKnB6DNTZ",
    title: "Unit 155",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "passive1",
        back: "passive1",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KWtdsyzqsH",
      },
      {
        front: "passive2",
        back: "passive2",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6hYLZlLsHt",
      },
      {
        front: "passive3",
        back: "passive3",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aMG87BBOkU",
      },
      {
        front: "passive",
        back: "passive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tvRt0FBOXV",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "8nnG9ytgSA",
    title: "Unit 155",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "arruinar",
        back: "spoil",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5fq0viyGgM",
      },
      {
        front: "cereal",
        back: "cereal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FNILHIqpcu",
      },
      {
        front: "crecer",
        back: "grow up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KrBAV2MfX7",
      },
      {
        front: "cultivar",
        back: "cultivate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bes1janRmz",
      },
      {
        front: "frutal",
        back: "fruity",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QdWocSOGXI",
      },
      {
        front: "helada",
        back: "frost",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X0Z7ZoK3Zl",
      },
      {
        front: "llovido",
        back: "rained",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OP6nUcEPqt",
      },
      {
        front: "plantar",
        back: "plant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rEQwTemHOy",
      },
      {
        front: "terrenos",
        back: "land",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zg5XZq1aGS",
      },
      {
        front: "trigo",
        back: "wheat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DPsJTTeRpD",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "SZDdWKeTu9",
    title: "Unit 156",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "democracias",
        back: "democracies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qsiXRipXrH",
      },
      {
        front: "dictaduras",
        back: "dictatorships",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i5b0cCSFgt",
      },
      {
        front: "ecología",
        back: "ecology",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5ZOaMDXoo1",
      },
      {
        front: "educación",
        back: "education",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eZ6RyFCAOY",
      },
      {
        front: "esperanzas",
        back: "hopes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Sk6rc8Z1TK",
      },
      {
        front: "estabilidad",
        back: "stability",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FiiG8dfIXm",
      },
      {
        front: "haber",
        back: "to have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DKRDD7Pc7h",
      },
      {
        front: "investigar",
        back: "investigate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SPO8g1bYtn",
      },
      {
        front: "noticiero",
        back: "news",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VdqvLouCZ9",
      },
      {
        front: "pobreza",
        back: "poverty",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1GcxvSapVN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "NLmlWZiUUk",
    title: "Unit 157",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "armar",
        back: "to assemble",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RHfBoaKW1G",
      },
      {
        front: "carpa",
        back: "large tent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UwHEKUyt3u",
      },
      {
        front: "llevar",
        back: "wear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "royAJNzvwG",
      },
      {
        front: "mochilero",
        back: "backpacker",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3XEpjXkzCa",
      },
      {
        front: "punto de encuentro",
        back: "meeting point",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cZ8tFY3hsz",
      },
      {
        front: "senderismo",
        back: "trekking",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tBcUEjkSBA",
      },
      {
        front: "sí",
        back: "Yeah",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dLQb9ziuZM",
      },
      {
        front: "sí o sí",
        back: "Yes or yes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t4XggQdh8r",
      },
      {
        front: "yo no",
        back: "I do not",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tevHVEfdin",
      },
      {
        front: "yo sí",
        back: "I do",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wDJKtu1qQO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "sPbcakuAIp",
    title: "Unit 157",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "batiendo",
        back: "beating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gSa7WzhIQm",
      },
      {
        front: "calabaza",
        back: "pumpkin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o1sHy5df17",
      },
      {
        front: "cantando",
        back: "singing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MIyKST7VWx",
      },
      {
        front: "clara",
        back: "clear",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sWTJFRsJ7d",
      },
      {
        front: "hervir",
        back: "to boil",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vEpShaoOSl",
      },
      {
        front: "hirviendo",
        back: "boiling",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "BOFG35O70h",
      },
      {
        front: "leche descremada",
        back: "skim milk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ve13KvkESg",
      },
      {
        front: "participante",
        back: "competitor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "a2JkhoUtj5",
      },
      {
        front: "programa de cocina",
        back: "Cooking show",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AkaDzXcwV3",
      },
      {
        front: "saber",
        back: "know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lfYIYK92Ky",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "f5TralGh0r",
    title: "Unit 157",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "administración",
        back: "administration",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oELo9q0LdU",
      },
      {
        front: "aparentemente",
        back: "apparently",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0o08Btpudi",
      },
      {
        front: "astronauta",
        back: "astronaut",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9ngJ3AHZ0R",
      },
      {
        front: "colaborar",
        back: "to collaborate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R71hnQTjZO",
      },
      {
        front: "detective",
        back: "detective",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "clbg67kLlT",
      },
      {
        front: "dirigir",
        back: "lead",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ffScKOqNE2",
      },
      {
        front: "estar a cargo",
        back: "be in charge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZMqecViMuN",
      },
      {
        front: "lo interesante",
        back: "the interesting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VD6V8EeiEt",
      },
      {
        front: "lo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jzxxGMPr39",
      },
      {
        front: "más importante",
        back: "the most important",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "R4v582DnMd",
      },
      {
        front: "se supone que",
        back: "be supposed to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I2NJQf7PDr",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "C1ZNmIF33b",
    title: "Unit 158",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bigote",
        back: "mustache",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ArK4a82z4M",
      },
      {
        front: "en voz baja",
        back: "quietly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7cYVFsqLpI",
      },
      {
        front: "lo es",
        back: "it is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C3xkFFHvaN",
      },
      {
        front: "lo está",
        back: "it is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5GTwF8j5Br",
      },
      {
        front: "mellizo",
        back: "twin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "neVEk5gflO",
      },
      {
        front: "ni",
        back: "neither",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "skx78ey02f",
      },
      {
        front: "parecer",
        back: "seem",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wze3VeGLMg",
      },
      {
        front: "pianista",
        back: "Pianist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fGAztcw4Kb",
      },
      {
        front: "soportar",
        back: "put up with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hUSA159aA6",
      },
      {
        front: "séptimo",
        back: "seventh",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Peim2oal5Q",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "PJgfT4xADl",
    title: "Unit 159",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adolescencia",
        back: "adolescence",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LNzY0uCOFO",
      },
      {
        front: "brevemente",
        back: "briefly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wRU4nYE7qj",
      },
      {
        front: "comportamientos",
        back: "behaviors",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "lnMzXLdC9P",
      },
      {
        front: "controlar",
        back: "check",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9DvuSvSn3e",
      },
      {
        front: "familiares",
        back: "relatives",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qM4bR1hcYa",
      },
      {
        front: "meterse en problemas",
        back: "get into trouble",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "02P5nhskZ3",
      },
      {
        front: "reunión",
        back: "meeting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cgIgnoH1vn",
      },
      {
        front: "todos",
        back: "everyone",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CouwaKkcJg",
      },
      {
        front: "trabajara",
        back: "will work",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rWPiNglJu5",
      },
      {
        front: "¿no crees?",
        back: "don't you think?",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nu0E0ndocg",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "hRuc6wwhTn",
    title: "Unit 159",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "subj61",
        back: "subj61",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Oa9NgXtUhs",
      },
      {
        front: "subj62",
        back: "subj62",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kcW8YWqORv",
      },
      {
        front: "subj63",
        back: "subj63",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J7SiClNwrq",
      },
      {
        front: "subj",
        back: "subj",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wjEfroxBqL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "dg52hQpCTJ",
    title: "Unit 160",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acostado",
        back: "lying down",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4qgWzt43rL",
      },
      {
        front: "comiera",
        back: "eat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3gKaRA6cDc",
      },
      {
        front: "diabético",
        back: "diabetic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PSxtxCQl0f",
      },
      {
        front: "fibra",
        back: "fiber",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fNXIwRTOKb",
      },
      {
        front: "gota",
        back: "gout",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "iX3NUU4EDk",
      },
      {
        front: "muñeca",
        back: "wrist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "d2GXlOt2lz",
      },
      {
        front: "primeros auxilios",
        back: "first aid",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZX03CYSEBD",
      },
      {
        front: "tobillo",
        back: "ankle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sv5BmOgmmU",
      },
      {
        front: "urgencia",
        back: "urgency",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UXBVW4oXrC",
      },
      {
        front: "vitamina",
        back: "vitamin",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qjPJbABpvI",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "kg2gfeZkc4",
    title: "Unit 161",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "esconder",
        back: "hide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "D5BryPSTZ8",
      },
      {
        front: "estatua",
        back: "statue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wcuEn9PuM6",
      },
      {
        front: "inevitable",
        back: "inevitable",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2bFVdcGMRa",
      },
      {
        front: "mil millones",
        back: "billion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LB0mP08PQ3",
      },
      {
        front: "muchacho",
        back: "young guy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C7K1IVr56R",
      },
      {
        front: "no puedo creer que",
        back: "I can not believe that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w8tbiR7B1k",
      },
      {
        front: "pista",
        back: "clue",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ugwR2sE0Jq",
      },
      {
        front: "princesa",
        back: "princess",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aL6y2NVyjK",
      },
      {
        front: "príncipes",
        back: "princes",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vZfDn5HgCv",
      },
      {
        front: "robar",
        back: "Steal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4LwrL3WR5q",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7ULXaK05sr",
    title: "Unit 161",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "calzoncillos",
        back: "underpants",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GQ2KK6W1ih",
      },
      {
        front: "casco",
        back: "helmet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SL0pBtEFOu",
      },
      {
        front: "corte de pelo",
        back: "haircut",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DnvzSOqXMM",
      },
      {
        front: "derramar",
        back: "to spill",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PGgIhVBzxH",
      },
      {
        front: "en serio",
        back: "really",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "32IbX9TG9u",
      },
      {
        front: "maletero",
        back: "trunk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "siP3caZfyJ",
      },
      {
        front: "no me digas",
        back: "do not tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YGsG7deL1J",
      },
      {
        front: "no puede ser",
        back: "can not be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UyCMPxuAzX",
      },
      {
        front: "peinarse",
        back: "to comb",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8V3YWury9L",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar el",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "glvyUMOaW5",
      },
      {
        front: "pelo",
        back: "Pull the leg",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0kCV3HCxIp",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "HglQJLyUuA",
    title: "Unit 162",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cartón",
        back: "paperboard",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W8Pqbbofy3",
      },
      {
        front: "grado",
        back: "degree",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Abn70gRzZB",
      },
      {
        front: "guardería",
        back: "kindergarten",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ddH8R1oRWK",
      },
      {
        front: "jardín de infantes",
        back: "Kinder garden",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "55TmDzb0Ih",
      },
      {
        front: "llorar",
        back: "cry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JaY0MFN3f5",
      },
      {
        front: "noveno",
        back: "nineth",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "l48DDzEAXn",
      },
      {
        front: "odiar que...",
        back: "hate that...",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y9JaewHH1B",
      },
      {
        front: "pronunciar",
        back: "to pronounce",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o4NeI24TNQ",
      },
      {
        front: "qué raro que",
        back: "how strange that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V4i1UCbWWN",
      },
      {
        front: "rectángulo",
        back: "rectangle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8xg1PmdcuG",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Hxib5iYRSo",
    title: "Unit 163",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "asiático",
        back: "Asian",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "796O67JeAX",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudante",
        back: "assistant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OuBYEXAeQO",
      },
      {
        front: "de tiempo parcial",
        back: "part time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M63MVOW0f9",
      },
      {
        front: "estadía",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8mKYHEupUn",
      },
      {
        front: "guiar",
        back: "guide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Va1AX4kA6R",
      },
      {
        front: "químico",
        back: "chemical",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QdKs5qrAag",
      },
      {
        front: "ser",
        back: "to be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vnywRELp8K",
      },
      {
        front: "sudeste",
        back: "southeast",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YFPIOscB1j",
      },
      {
        front: "tener",
        back: "have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J0woNzkzrI",
      },
      {
        front: "valle",
        back: "Valley",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bMVI4LU0iT",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "8WKnUhaCmE",
    title: "Unit 164",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cambiarse de",
        back: "change from",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ASQpNst2UE",
      },
      {
        front: "chisme",
        back: "gossip",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jg3ZpyEfnO",
      },
      {
        front: "como",
        back: "What",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sYbFr9J1Ip",
      },
      {
        front: "dar pena",
        back: "feel sorry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w386w8aKk4",
      },
      {
        front: "hablar mal de",
        back: "speak ill of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "anObRRAPxy",
      },
      {
        front: "ir",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m8RHbaryXM",
      },
      {
        front: "a pasear",
        back: "go for a walk",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8zA2sq5vov",
      },
      {
        front: "juzgar",
        back: "judge",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PbSvM9x87g",
      },
      {
        front: "salir de viaje",
        back: "jet off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "A2TgCZxGkY",
      },
      {
        front: "suegra",
        back: "mother in law",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qUR9ZJVy6J",
      },
      {
        front: "superar",
        back: "live through",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FwkMICw3iw",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "a3YQecinAz",
    title: "Unit 165",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "absurdo",
        back: "absurd",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eU18J3a2Ta",
      },
      {
        front: "alarma",
        back: "alarm",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ptlr9Uuza7",
      },
      {
        front: "confidencial",
        back: "confidential",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KLi0D6wBZ2",
      },
      {
        front: "fotocopiadora",
        back: "photocopier",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Eum2Dpogo3",
      },
      {
        front: "fotocopiar",
        back: "photocopy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "buSS4hMZag",
      },
      {
        front: "personal",
        back: "staff",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g52rTfy1s7",
      },
      {
        front: "propuesta",
        back: "proposal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UEpW9s3PMw",
      },
      {
        front: "si mal no recuerdo",
        back: "if I remember correctly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "YAfbaT1uEJ",
      },
      {
        front: "subdirector",
        back: "vice principal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "beJUgeP6He",
      },
      {
        front: "todo el día",
        back: "all day",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MxMR5pI6CG",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "kC4XqstZFk",
    title: "Unit 165",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acercarse",
        back: "getting closer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "hj3yxtZb0j",
      },
      {
        front: "asustarse",
        back: "get scared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "irq7VCLwdI",
      },
      {
        front: "espera",
        back: "wait",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0FCwzDjeTh",
      },
      {
        front: "gata",
        back: "cat",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TfSf73wlTK",
      },
      {
        front: "gatas",
        back: "cats",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PpTq4nMTaj",
      },
      {
        front: "lo",
        back: "it",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TOixi419Eb",
      },
      {
        front: "lobo",
        back: "wolf",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cviYLOkUOu",
      },
      {
        front: "mosca",
        back: "fly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "amRCgX6SYH",
      },
      {
        front: "orilla",
        back: "bank",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1KCRDQzrTr",
      },
      {
        front: "oíste que",
        back: "did you hear that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9p0LriUI0O",
      },
      {
        front: "permitir",
        back: "let",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SP236qXLYn",
      },
      {
        front: "picar",
        back: "sting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6DGb6lkHFI",
      },
      {
        front: "tortuga",
        back: "turtle",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qaauPORP8B",
      },
      {
        front: "tortugas",
        back: "turtles",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1qNiY4yAA3",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "quk7J9KZSs",
    title: "Unit 166",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "avergonzado",
        back: "ashamed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "OFlLrVOqHu",
      },
      {
        front: "debí haber",
        back: "I should have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Xd1M5dVNtJ",
      },
      {
        front: "entrenar",
        back: "train",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sA0pi2HX62",
      },
      {
        front: "fallar",
        back: "fail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "gX8bj9sx3t",
      },
      {
        front: "fan",
        back: "fan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ho070pCQZw",
      },
      {
        front: "lamentar",
        back: "to regret",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e8ilYrfFDc",
      },
      {
        front: "motivación",
        back: "motivation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "r35FoFuDqA",
      },
      {
        front: "semifinal",
        back: "semifinal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UYKEaISFzj",
      },
      {
        front: "trofeo",
        back: "trophy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7CpIaPTcL8",
      },
      {
        front: "una vez más",
        back: "one more time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aLfTfLsZF0",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "q416IiclYC",
    title: "Unit 166",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a principios de",
        back: "at the beginning of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RVqt27Hlu6",
      },
      {
        front: "apenado",
        back: "sorry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UOBQD0aFM6",
      },
      {
        front: "de toda la vida",
        back: "lifelong",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m2aj5BUfe2",
      },
      {
        front: "editor",
        back: "editor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "s4a1HmS0cx",
      },
      {
        front: "forma",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CFleAzt6rd",
      },
      {
        front: "de ser",
        back: "way of being",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "e1TVuxhDAL",
      },
      {
        front: "imaginarse",
        back: "imagine",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ge1ClkoHna",
      },
      {
        front: "memoria",
        back: "memory",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xqtTW55AXL",
      },
      {
        front: "puntualmente",
        back: "promptly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MLAAOtqj8h",
      },
      {
        front: "rumor",
        back: "rumor",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vrdm7dlgL5",
      },
      {
        front: "tacaño",
        back: "mean",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MUFIU5mS6j",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "V21tDpUmyx",
    title: "Unit 167",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "a distancia",
        back: "from distance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZBANmxxvPj",
      },
      {
        front: "analizar",
        back: "analyze",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QVn4Wf3ZjN",
      },
      {
        front: "aprendizaje",
        back: "learning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "v8l5NBbEIf",
      },
      {
        front: "astrología",
        back: "astrology",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "df2nHcLLeV",
      },
      {
        front: "comenzar",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nRcFw2OdQm",
      },
      {
        front: "a",
        back: "begin to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V9X22k5Ibz",
      },
      {
        front: "comenzar por",
        back: "start with",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DNEwgEd2sj",
      },
      {
        front: "intensivo",
        back: "intensive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "B3p3tVca4b",
      },
      {
        front: "modo de ver",
        back: "way of seeing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1GYQppT9jJ",
      },
      {
        front: "pensar de",
        back: "to think of",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nzr6AgFlBp",
      },
      {
        front: "veo",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Si4IN3q4L",
      },
      {
        front: "que",
        back: "I see that",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "AmRvL6pzTf",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "7x6T1rPUl7",
    title: "Unit 167",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "atrasado",
        back: "late",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TYV15AUqPq",
      },
      {
        front: "cualquier",
        back: "any",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PZHYWbApKB",
      },
      {
        front: "es que",
        back: "the thing is",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mr9Couw62i",
      },
      {
        front: "estresar",
        back: "to stress",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0pUdT7KVLs",
      },
      {
        front: "forma",
        back: "form",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QbeVvc6SO9",
      },
      {
        front: "imprescindible",
        back: "essential",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "p49j0enjnr",
      },
      {
        front: "ocurrírsele",
        back: "occur to him",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wpgaRb272h",
      },
      {
        front: "perdóname",
        back: "forgive me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EnmTPZBfmd",
      },
      {
        front: "solucionar",
        back: "sort out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ld4w6zjJ72",
      },
      {
        front: "tranquilizar",
        back: "reassure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "JEAYJYQa3w",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "jpHSLzCiYG",
    title: "Unit 168",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "angustiado",
        back: "distressed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mHnt3Bmfe2",
      },
      {
        front: "ayudara",
        back: "help to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mHXPx8o93u",
      },
      {
        front: "limpieza",
        back: "cleaning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t6FJgfwlSk",
      },
      {
        front: "madrugar",
        back: "get up early",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XrI5EEK5qh",
      },
      {
        front: "preparado",
        back: "prepared",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "QGpy4UIzCk",
      },
      {
        front: "proponer matrimonio",
        back: "propose marriage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EOWB9gJdZU",
      },
      {
        front: "sentimental",
        back: "sentimental",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vEl1E5ANXP",
      },
      {
        front: "tener planeado",
        back: "have planned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ezeyyJ6kFM",
      },
      {
        front: "toda la",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Lu9C6SNsw5",
      },
      {
        front: "mañana",
        back: "all morning",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ouITBHVd3o",
      },
      {
        front: "viviera",
        back: "lived",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "trDY2NOWGO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "y4pLZhYcHO",
    title: "Unit 168",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "analgésico",
        back: "analgesic",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "96auQM2tkj",
      },
      {
        front: "bronquitis",
        back: "bronchitis",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9vUNTQlvvC",
      },
      {
        front: "contagiarse",
        back: "catch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cDLI2OF1vG",
      },
      {
        front: "debería haber",
        back: "there should be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "dZ8nQslmWj",
      },
      {
        front: "muleta",
        back: "crutch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aceNNASufx",
      },
      {
        front: "podría haber",
        back: "could have",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G4GOgTjeIQ",
      },
      {
        front: "termómetro",
        back: "thermometer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZkbEaYPrgH",
      },
      {
        front: "torcer",
        back: "twist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zghZVNlCKe",
      },
      {
        front: "traumatólogo",
        back: "traumatologist",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0b3BdSNjWL",
      },
      {
        front: "únicamente",
        back: "only",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jGPuPBClhM",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Zf1US7rwIB",
    title: "Unit 169",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "cada",
        back: "each",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Mu2026c666",
      },
      {
        front: "constante",
        back: "constant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "efbY4AW5wH",
      },
      {
        front: "conteste",
        back: "answer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PLlZQNz24h",
      },
      {
        front: "criticar",
        back: "criticize",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3EA5LdxCX2",
      },
      {
        front: "disculpado",
        back: "excused",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xJfmbDoAuy",
      },
      {
        front: "distraído",
        back: "distracted",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V9TyjOrXhQ",
      },
      {
        front: "hacer enojar",
        back: "make angry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9o0YdITo3F",
      },
      {
        front: "poner de",
        back: "put off",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IQ1nxWro6P",
      },
      {
        front: "quieto",
        back: "still",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "g0wqGp7BAR",
      },
      {
        front: "regañar",
        back: "Quarrel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kWNJB0kIgz",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "i93qaT8sYM",
    title: "Unit 169",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "abrelatas",
        back: "can opener",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HXJB6j3xZL",
      },
      {
        front: "almendra",
        back: "almond",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "XnujTQyPVe",
      },
      {
        front: "batidora",
        back: "blender",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aEM4clA9Xh",
      },
      {
        front: "frambuesa",
        back: "raspberry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mXCsxZJ225",
      },
      {
        front: "igual que",
        back: "like",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sqsw6fq7DO",
      },
      {
        front: "legumbre",
        back: "legume",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "shs3RuHbE9",
      },
      {
        front: "licuadora",
        back: "blender",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vdhj3M9LWv",
      },
      {
        front: "nutritivo",
        back: "nutritious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U5FkDAJwZa",
      },
      {
        front: "picadora",
        back: "chopper",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "cr6UpHMTEW",
      },
      {
        front: "picar",
        back: "sting",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "LMNuZZ8peW",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "25966iRANs",
    title: "Unit 170",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "albergue",
        back: "hostel",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8mrGDZm5PV",
      },
      {
        front: "alojarse",
        back: "to stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "C5pLl6hQQD",
      },
      {
        front: "así",
        back: "So",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Nz9hgcyV8o",
      },
      {
        front: "chico",
        back: "guy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7kJzuuj0KN",
      },
      {
        front: "comodidades",
        back: "mod cons",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "V9eSsAziBk",
      },
      {
        front: "cubierto",
        back: "covered",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UfyYNH1t6W",
      },
      {
        front: "dicho sea de paso",
        back: "by the way",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MFajynl9me",
      },
      {
        front: "inmenso",
        back: "immense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "M2h4EiPPF8",
      },
      {
        front: "lujoso",
        back: "luxurious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "05xnqk92Hm",
      },
      {
        front: "no está nada mal",
        back: "it's not bad at all",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qyyXMnhpqt",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "fpu2vghTEv",
    title: "Unit 170",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "acuerdo",
        back: "agreement",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7rQoV8yKkX",
      },
      {
        front: "aumentara",
        back: "will increase",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uAdcqZR36b",
      },
      {
        front: "defender",
        back: "defend",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZDwhkFBRIQ",
      },
      {
        front: "discriminación",
        back: "discrimination",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "adU1jkhdqB",
      },
      {
        front: "fundamental",
        back: "fundamental",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "X7I2WBMm5s",
      },
      {
        front: "imprescindible",
        back: "essential",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jMnfWM8VPw",
      },
      {
        front: "inmigrante",
        back: "immigrant",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W4yP4zw6cp",
      },
      {
        front: "líder",
        back: "Leader",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "liy6cb5UmD",
      },
      {
        front: "no tener",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RI062efdFh",
      },
      {
        front: "por qué",
        back: "not have why",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HwJwSAYGEt",
      },
      {
        front: "voto",
        back: "vote",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DUqK5Nu2sO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "spcMVQFwOv",
    title: "Unit 171",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "afortunado",
        back: "lucky",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9SUYdQmvgL",
      },
      {
        front: "cariño",
        back: "affection",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J0AQZH96c2",
      },
      {
        front: "convivir",
        back: "live together",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "yeKvn7djPE",
      },
      {
        front: "en familia",
        back: "in family",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "o0HOwtVT4h",
      },
      {
        front: "inesperadamente",
        back: "unexpectedly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qrS14RDBJm",
      },
      {
        front: "inesperado",
        back: "unexpected",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2jVyGvl0WZ",
      },
      {
        front: "organizador de bodas",
        back: "wedding planner",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E3Gr1A60ja",
      },
      {
        front: "según",
        back: "according to",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FQnvLuHSU0",
      },
      {
        front: "tenso",
        back: "tense",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nNasXvYM4y",
      },
      {
        front: "tratar",
        back: "try",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZNj3nQoENL",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "iWHwB2faOz",
    title: "Unit 171",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "animarse",
        back: "Buck up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZDJdbGrfGA",
      },
      {
        front: "atascado",
        back: "stuck",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "UXWHJiy4aI",
      },
      {
        front: "atravesar",
        back: "cross",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2ZeRB9KFJL",
      },
      {
        front: "avanzar",
        back: "advance",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7mi9nlYOSk",
      },
      {
        front: "descomponer",
        back: "decompose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DqviGMlJJb",
      },
      {
        front: "detenerse",
        back: "stop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "c8xb5r513O",
      },
      {
        front: "grúa",
        back: "crane",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1MYAtaVonI",
      },
      {
        front: "pantano",
        back: "swamp",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0S9Z73Q6Am",
      },
      {
        front: "remolcar",
        back: "tow",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ACPiuevfim",
      },
      {
        front: "taller",
        back: "workshop",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "y5F9KldyCp",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "8rQLkbNcog",
    title: "Unit 172",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adelanto",
        back: "advancement",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Ong6lJCSOc",
      },
      {
        front: "agente inmobiliario",
        back: "real estate agent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TUZ688EDYP",
      },
      {
        front: "alcanzar",
        back: "attain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "TPTRqBQOA9",
      },
      {
        front: "dúplex",
        back: "duplex",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fNP8Gtphe4",
      },
      {
        front: "en",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ex63XtMc0A",
      },
      {
        front: "alquiler",
        back: "for rent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "40J43MmbAE",
      },
      {
        front: "hipoteca",
        back: "mortgage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "SY2W9WIwxA",
      },
      {
        front: "mudarse",
        back: "move",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U4XAddQWKp",
      },
      {
        front: "propiedad",
        back: "property",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3GFB6l5apz",
      },
      {
        front: "ático",
        back: "penthouse",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CQzcxzIvbr",
      },
      {
        front: "ía",
        back: "went",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bPMkcbNEyR",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "VM4zpwQRW7",
    title: "Unit 172",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "castigar",
        back: "punish",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "flzOc42pF2",
      },
      {
        front: "de otra manera",
        back: "otherwise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ZIl9LiN6bJ",
      },
      {
        front: "fantasía",
        back: "fantasy",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IWkQ3bgT2w",
      },
      {
        front: "habría",
        back: "there would be",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sT7Z4IUQue",
      },
      {
        front: "niñez",
        back: "childhood",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3LRYay9O1Q",
      },
      {
        front: "obediente",
        back: "obedient",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pzMn7nj0fo",
      },
      {
        front: "pasar el rato",
        back: "hang out",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6gpJITYxD7",
      },
      {
        front: "prohibir",
        back: "ban",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "4sj02UaJFU",
      },
      {
        front: "travieso",
        back: "mischievous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wib6z7C7jY",
      },
      {
        front: "época",
        back: "epoch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rMVGC7eFDK",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "YK7eG49okJ",
    title: "Unit 173",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bautismo",
        back: "baptism",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oYmXgmOncp",
      },
      {
        front: "claro que sí",
        back: "of course",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "VuYc5jAmfp",
      },
      {
        front: "clase",
        back: "class",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eLn5vvVtOk",
      },
      {
        front: "darse prisa",
        back: "hurry up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NNGJlF9ETy",
      },
      {
        front: "lo lamento",
        back: "sorry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zfqihyiNVM",
      },
      {
        front: "partida",
        back: "departure",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GbmfQrRnE9",
      },
      {
        front: "quedar",
        back: "stay",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "EkqF05p2G9",
      },
      {
        front: "recoger",
        back: "pick up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "W8h7UPuk1U",
      },
      {
        front: "siempre que",
        back: "as long as",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sg0z2tNhaW",
      },
      {
        front: "yerno",
        back: "son in law",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "m76uIM1CYN",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "lU1I9N6fcv",
    title: "Unit 173",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "casamiento",
        back: "marriage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rfBIVFlrZB",
      },
      {
        front: "convención",
        back: "convention",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PYnOYhTJ8g",
      },
      {
        front: "decidido",
        back: "decided",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eQaQWaobBp",
      },
      {
        front: "entretener",
        back: "entertain",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xrnKLOu4lw",
      },
      {
        front: "entretenido",
        back: "entertaining",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "isVJLa7uOC",
      },
      {
        front: "inaugurado",
        back: "inaugurated",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "GfOozIG2fP",
      },
      {
        front: "inaugurar",
        back: "inaugurate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sLrZI4RLTl",
      },
      {
        front: "planificado",
        back: "planned",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oklFGgwq3m",
      },
      {
        front: "planificar",
        back: "to plan",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "9OwgOF8TdJ",
      },
      {
        front: "qué bien",
        back: "how good",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6dYJ9pWrCr",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "4XE3FNhw60",
    title: "Unit 174",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "asesoramiento",
        back: "advice",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oKiYGIGvii",
      },
      {
        front: "capacitar",
        back: "train",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "05PiFpjqbU",
      },
      {
        front: "compañero",
        back: "companion",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wTmiikYYeo",
      },
      {
        front: "competente",
        back: "competent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "eawa0CAF26",
      },
      {
        front: "consejero",
        back: "adviser",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5XQlSnrdkL",
      },
      {
        front: "doctorado",
        back: "doctorate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "kYjNlTOTET",
      },
      {
        front: "estudios",
        back: "studies",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xZobsQp29P",
      },
      {
        front: "puesto",
        back: "Market Stall",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0TCMFrFfGz",
      },
      {
        front: "qué tal",
        back: "how's it going",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "K15PJEJYt1",
      },
      {
        front: "tesis",
        back: "thesis",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "pZtUMLDLtC",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "OYXDp7nbcq",
    title: "Unit 174",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "atento",
        back: "attentive",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vhagehm1LL",
      },
      {
        front: "chau",
        back: "bye",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T93qw2cVPE",
      },
      {
        front: "de mi parte",
        back: "from my part",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2snasx5Lak",
      },
      {
        front: "función",
        back: "function",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8FXwNtLsML",
      },
      {
        front: "gafas",
        back: "glasses",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "fC3iOwMPC6",
      },
      {
        front: "hasta pronto",
        back: "see you soon",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Fk7R4oc9Ad",
      },
      {
        front: "nuera",
        back: "daughter in law",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qWmnnUmlWW",
      },
      {
        front: "recepción",
        back: "reception",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5te6H0GAtP",
      },
      {
        front: "saludos",
        back: "regards",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ml46p5B42K",
      },
      {
        front: "trillizo",
        back: "triplet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "T8pgIJmPRF",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "9SOi3NSvk9",
    title: "Unit 175",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "bronce",
        back: "bronze",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "84J87RHJyF",
      },
      {
        front: "como mínimo",
        back: "As minimum",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "PjSUDWehuP",
      },
      {
        front: "de ancho",
        back: "Wide",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ajgJYwiTqD",
      },
      {
        front: "flojo",
        back: "loose",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wg9mtbwdTn",
      },
      {
        front: "iluminación",
        back: "illumination",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Bo1UVZbFcZ",
      },
      {
        front: "interruptor",
        back: "switch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "WjpMmmgYex",
      },
      {
        front: "lavadero",
        back: "laundry",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "sixoFezQV1",
      },
      {
        front: "mármol",
        back: "marble",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Iz02qNrOA6",
      },
      {
        front: "pulgada",
        back: "inch",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "oLM5cyV5Lk",
      },
      {
        front: "repare",
        back: "I fixed",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "DycsU6eTiI",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "Jz4N7xxE1y",
    title: "Unit 175",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "adaptarse",
        back: "adapt",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6F1caicP3x",
      },
      {
        front: "detalle",
        back: "detail",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "aOlAvYCv4T",
      },
      {
        front: "empleador",
        back: "employer",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "mffK39PSPg",
      },
      {
        front: "formación",
        back: "training",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "qETOr25l7k",
      },
      {
        front: "gestionar",
        back: "manage",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "HQaOIs4HIl",
      },
      {
        front: "graduarse",
        back: "graduate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1hRPnrZt2K",
      },
      {
        front: "investigador",
        back: "investigator",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "O4ZawhNBdC",
      },
      {
        front: "previo",
        back: "previous",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "vN7VgyJ7hV",
      },
      {
        front: "redactar",
        back: "write",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MCJZCRA4m9",
      },
      {
        front: "requerir",
        back: "require",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2COal41fA6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "j7uEkTVfh0",
    title: "Unit 176",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "confesar",
        back: "to confess",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "8Zo6ryWEvV",
      },
      {
        front: "darse por vencido",
        back: "give up",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "NeLGlAo7Lo",
      },
      {
        front: "despido",
        back: "dismissal",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "KM5WICyMFp",
      },
      {
        front: "fijo",
        back: "permanent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0vOUXwVWzw",
      },
      {
        front: "hora extra",
        back: "extra hour",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "jCakcqLKRN",
      },
      {
        front: "incompetente",
        back: "incompetent",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Vrp7uGlT95",
      },
      {
        front: "indemnización",
        back: "compensation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xjzTvRywm1",
      },
      {
        front: "supersticioso",
        back: "superstitious",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "nocXoM2heo",
      },
      {
        front: "susceptible",
        back: "susceptible",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "Wt82bnOkoe",
      },
      {
        front: "traer suerte",
        back: "bring luck",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "CVHkMdAOo6",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "cwG9fskVVE",
    title: "Unit 176",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "calentamiento",
        back: "heating",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "MGA0b0saTq",
      },
      {
        front: "de lo que",
        back: "of what",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "0Z83kdDkwU",
      },
      {
        front: "global",
        back: "global",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "2fzsg8cmql",
      },
      {
        front: "impacto",
        back: "impact",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "t2bhzvW5hl",
      },
      {
        front: "mayor",
        back: "higher",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "J4WKY8FyIN",
      },
      {
        front: "por",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "E2jQ3SFaIL",
      },
      {
        front: "otro lado",
        back: "Secondly",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "5Hb7Zm2imn",
      },
      {
        front: "por un lado",
        back: "on the one hand",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "w0qDLyzlBZ",
      },
      {
        front: "sobrepoblación",
        back: "overpopulation",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "I8THG4jpXH",
      },
      {
        front: "superior",
        back: "superior",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RO6Xe2Y0cU",
      },
      {
        front: "urbano",
        back: "urban",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bYn8fqwZgO",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "fjdPktJKoc",
    title: "Unit 177",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aquí tiene",
        back: "here you go",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i7Pt4Dtggs",
      },
      {
        front: "audición",
        back: "hearing",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "FJATF1qvFR",
      },
      {
        front: "gran",
        back: "big",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "bsXPQsJHbQ",
      },
      {
        front: "guion",
        back: "script",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "i7Jx59DgG6",
      },
      {
        front: "inauguración",
        back: "opening",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "G9iuo8pRB7",
      },
      {
        front: "inversión",
        back: "investment",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "wMEtN4vF7Q",
      },
      {
        front: "negociar",
        back: "negotiate",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "RXAJnNCIGo",
      },
      {
        front: "que",
        back: "what",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "rEDXDNA1X1",
      },
      {
        front: "tarjeta",
        back: "card",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "zwaLH35pLW",
      },
      {
        front: "tomar por sorpresa",
        back: "take by surprise",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "6sxIU6F5h2",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: "H7KVQcw0g7",
    title: "Unit 177",
    cards: [
      {
        front: "aún no",
        back: "not yet",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U9U1pnjRDw",
      },
      {
        front: "botiquín",
        back: "first aid kit",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "uxWHlWdFVs",
      },
      {
        front: "cambiar de idea",
        back: "change of idea",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "IxveyOfOss",
      },
      {
        front: "ganar tiempo",
        back: "gain time",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "ARPNhez8yF",
      },
      {
        front: "guardado",
        back: "saved",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "7tsNKVPR8t",
      },
      {
        front: "me dices",
        back: "you tell me",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "1CJkDn27iK",
      },
      {
        front: "pasar",
        back: "happen",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "3pTl5YNetF",
      },
      {
        front: "que yo sepa",
        back: "far as I know",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "U5PwxE2lKQ",
      },
      {
        front: "recorrido",
        back: "tour",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "tgeCPzraSu",
      },
      {
        front: "tener confianza",
        back: "have confidence",
        guess: "unquizzed",
        hint: "",
        id: "xQNVZsPHq3",
      },
    ],
  },
];
